TeraBox Privacy Policy

TeraBox Privacy Policy

What information is collected and for what purpose

Provision of personal information to third parties

Sharing data with other users

We may share your information with third parties

How we protect and store your information

Where we store and process your information

How you control and access your information

{{ $t('termsOfServicePrivacyPolicy.age.title') }}

Change

Contact Us

TeraBox Privacy Policy

Released on April 18, 2023

Effective from April 18, 2023

Thank you for using TeraBox. TeraBox is provided to you by Flextech Inc. (hereinafter referred to as "Flextech", "we", or "us"). We are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets out how we collect, store, process, share and use your information when you access our website, software, and services (the "Services").

We only collect and use your personal information for legal, legitimate, and necessary purposes. Specifically, we collect and process your personal information to provide you with our services and functions. If you use other people's personal information to access our services and functions, please ensure that you have been authorized to do so, and we reserve the right to verify if such personal information is legally used at any time.

We will ask for your separate consent in specific circumstances in strict accordance with laws and regulations. In addition to this Privacy Policy, we may also explain our rules for processing your personal information through notifications on pages of the product, pop-up prompts, push notifications, and so forth. The processing of personal information for each service or function is subject to specific rules, which have the same effect as this Privacy Policy.

Please note: Your authorization or consent is not required in advance for the collection, use, sharing, transfer, or disclosure of your personal information when such information is:

directly related to national security and national defense security;

necessary for the conclusion and performance of a contract to which you are one of the parties;

necessary for the performance of statutory duties or obligations;

necessary to respond to public health emergencies or to protect the life, health, and property of a natural person in emergencies;

directly related to the investigation, prosecution, trial, or execution of sentence of a crime;

necessary to safeguard the life, property, and other major legitimate rights and interests of you or other individuals under the condition that your consent is difficult to obtain;

disclosed by you to the public or by other legal means (the information is collected in accordance with laws and regulations to a reasonable extent);

legally disclosed through channels such as legitimate news, government notice (the information is collected in accordance with laws and regulations to a reasonable extent);

necessary to publish news, carry out supervision by public opinion, and so on in the public interest (the information is collected to a reasonable extent);

necessary for an academic research institution to conduct statistical or academic research in the public interest (personal information in the results of academic research or descriptions is de-identified before it is revealed to the public);

otherwise required by applicable laws and regulations.

What information is collected and for what purpose

The table below lists the types of information you submit to us when you use the Services and the purposes for which we may use that information. We collect and use the following information to deliver, optimize, protect, and promote the Services.

| Type of Information | Purpose of Collection |
| --- | --- |
| Account information: We collect information such as the email address and phone number that you provide to us when you perform operations such as registering for an account (if you log in with an SNS account, then we will receive your nickname and SNS profile image), and link such information with your account. | We may use this information to identify you as the account owner and to keep your account secure. We may collect this information when you log in to your account. |
| User data: It is data that you store on TeraBox, such as files, documents, photos, videos, and audio ("user data"). | We may store, process, and transfer user data and relevant information to ensure proper operations for the Services and enable you to collaborate with others and work across devices and Services. User data includes the information, size, upload date and time, and usage of your configuration files. |
| Usage information: It is information about how the Services are used, including operations performed in your account such as editing, viewing, creating, and moving files or folders. | We can use this information to provide, improve, and promote the Services and protect TeraBox users. |
| Device information: This refers to information about the device used to access the Services and may include IP address, browser, and device information, web pages visited prior to accessing TeraBox, identifiers tied to the device, and location information depending on the device settings. | We may use this information to optimize and protect the Services. |
| Cookies: Cookies are small pieces of text that are sent to your browser by the website when you visit TeraBox. You can set your browser not to accept cookies, though this may affect the functionality of the Services. | We may use cookies and similar technologies to deliver, optimize, protect, and promote the Services. Cookies allow us to remember your username between logins, to better understand how you use the Services, and to improve the Services on the basis of this information. The third-party service providers we work with may also use cookies and similar technologies. |
| Contact information: You may share your data and information through the Share function of TeraBox or the contacts, mobile phone numbers, and email addresses (including those for Facebook and Twitter) on your phone. Such information is sensitive personal information. If you refuse to provide it, you cannot use the above-mentioned functions but can normally use other TeraBox functions and related services. | You can choose to allow TeraBox to access your contact information to facilitate certain operations, such as sharing your data, cooperating with others to process your data, sending messages, and sending emails to invite others to use TeraBox. The above functions are available after you have granted us permission to access your contacts. We store this information on our server for you to use. Before sharing any data, please think through if the recipient is trustworthy. In addition, in order to ensure that prudent decisions are made, we recommend that you check the privacy statements of SNS or third-party service providers to learn how they process your information. |
| Clipboard: When you register a Terabox account using someone's invitation code, access file links shared by other users, add friends through passwords, or obtain membership services through redemption codes, we will read your clipboard information. | We will access the clipboard information to assist you in opening the file corresponding to the link, identify the user corresponding to the password and invitation code, or redeem membership services for you. We will never read your clipboard for any other purpose. |

You can create a TeraBox account using your mobile phone number and complete your account information.

In the event that it is required by laws and regulations, necessary for us to provide the product or the Services, or based on your demand to enhance the security of your account, you must provide your real name, identity document number, and facial recognition information for account authentication to use some Terabox services or to meet your further needs. In order to verify that the information you provide is accurate and complete, or ensure the security of your account, we may compare the real-name information you provide to Terabox with that registered at institutions permitted by laws and regulations or authorized by government agencies.

The above information is collected for the purpose of reliably and securely providing the Services and for legitimate business purposes. We or our partners will request your consent prior to processing your information for any other purpose beyond those specifically stated.

You agree that we can aggregate, integrate, identify, analyze, portray, or further process the personal information actively or passively provided by you in the Services through the technology of us or our trustees to form a variety of label information with different degrees of granularity that reflect your operation habits, interests, or credit (hereinafter referred to as "label information"). We will use label information for automated decision-making in specific scenarios and applications, so as to send you personalized information and/or marketing information.

You have the right to refuse the automated decision-making service implemented by us. You may contact us through the contact information in this Policy or require us to stop by using the relevant functional switch in the Services. Additionally, if there are applicable national or regional regulations or regulatory requirements prohibiting automated decision-making, we will follow them as required.

We may use your Account Data for marketing purposes and send you information about TeraBox's new products, upgrades and other marketing material from time to time. You can opt out of receiving marketing material at any time by clicking the 'unsubscribe' link in any emails you receive.

Provision of personal information to third parties

We will not reveal your personal information to any third party without your prior consent, except under any of the following circumstances:

(a) We are required to cooperate with national or regional governmental organizations or their agents in the performance of their duties or obligations under applicable laws and regulations, which may preclude such performance if your consent is required;

(b) Where there is a substantial risk to a person's life or property;

(c) Where there is a particular need to improve public health or promote the healthy development of youth.

For the sharing, transfer, or disclosure of your personal information under the above exceptional circumstances, we will log the basis for processing relevant information, the scope of information being processed, the information on the recipient, and so forth as enumerated below based on the principles of minimization and necessity to protect your legitimate rights and interests.

(1) Names and contact details of the data controller and data protection officer;

(2) Purpose of data processing;

(3) Descriptions of the data subject type and the personal data type;

(4) The type of recipient to whom the personal data has been or will be disclosed (including a recipient in a third country or international organization);

(5) Records of transfer of personal data to a third country or international organization and records of appropriate safeguards;

(6) Expected time to delete different types of data;

(7) General description of technical and organizational security measures.

Sharing data with other users

When you use the Teamwork or Share functions of TeraBox, the Services display your nickname, device information, email address, and usage information to users that you cooperate with, or information that you permit to share. This allows you to be updated on information about the team that you will join and enable other users to share files and folders with you.

We may share your information with third parties

We may work with certain trusted third parties (such as customer support or IT service providers) that can help us better deliver, optimize, protect, and promote the Services. These third parties may have access to your information to perform tasks on our behalf, during which we remain responsible for the third parties' handling of your information in accordance with our requirements.

We may share infrastructure, systems, and technology with Flextech affiliates to deliver, optimize, protect, and promote the Services. These affiliates will use your information in conjunction with us and the information you have listed in the "What information is collected and for what purpose" section for the purposes described therein. We will be responsible for granting these companies access to your information.

You may choose to connect to your TeraBox account through a third-party service. By connecting to a service of this kind, you allow the third parties and us to exchange the information listed in the "What information is collected and for what purpose" section of this Privacy Policy so that the third parties and we can deliver, optimize, protect, and promote their services. In these cases, the use of your information will be governed by the privacy policies and terms of service of the third parties whose services you choose to connect through.

We will establish an output mechanism for cross-border data transfer with reference to the requirements of the GDPR and update it as required. Our processing of personal data will depend on the fundamental principles of the GDPR, the consent of valid data subjects, or other legitimate reasons. Apart from that, additional mechanisms will be put in place to protect data and meet the substantive requirements of the GDPR for data processing.

How we protect and store your information

We have a team dedicated to keeping your information secure and testing for vulnerabilities. In addition to two-factor authentication, encryption of files at rest, and alerts when new devices and apps link to your accounts, we continue to work hard to ensure the security of your information. We deploy automated technology to detect abusive behavior and content that could harm you, other users, or the Services.

After you have signed up for a TeraBox account, we retain the information you store in the Services for as long as your account exists or as long as necessary to provide you with the Services. If you want to delete your account, please send an email to [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) with such a request and we will delete your account within 30 days after receiving your request. However, 1) we will not delete your account information until we have verified your user identity; 2) such deletion of information from our servers and backup storage may be delayed; 3) we may retain this information if necessary to fulfill our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or exercise our rights under the Contract.

We will store your personal information for the period required for providing the Services. However, in the event that laws and regulations require otherwise, you agree to keep the information for a longer term, it is necessary to ensure the security and quality of the Services, the information is required to settle disputes, or it is technically intractable to process the information as required, we will extend the retention period as per laws and agreement or to a reasonable extent after the expiration of the aforesaid period.

When the retention period expires, we will delete your personal information or de-identify it in accordance with laws and regulations.

We will collect, use, store, and transfer your information based on the principle of "minimization", and inform you of the purpose and scope of use of the information by means of user agreement, privacy policy, rules, pop-up notifications, notices, and so on.

We attach great importance to information security. We have a dedicated team to develop and employ a variety of security technologies and programs. We carry out security background checks on personnel in charge of security management and those in critical security positions. We have established a complete information security management system and internal mechanisms for handling security events and more. We take appropriate security measures and technical means in line with industry standards to store and protect your personal information, so as to prevent your information from being lost or accessed, disclosed, used, damaged, or revealed without authorization. All reasonable and feasible measures are being taken for protecting your personal information. In addition, we use encryption technology to ensure the confidentiality of data and apply trusted protection mechanisms to prevent malicious attacks on data.

We train and assess our employees in terms of data security awareness and security abilities to enhance their comprehension of the importance of protecting personal information. We authenticate the identity of employees who process personal information and control their access, sign nondisclosure agreements with our employees and partners who have access to your personal information, and clarify job responsibilities and code of conduct, so that only authorized personnel can access personal information. In the event of any violation of the nondisclosure agreements, the employment will be terminated immediately with the violator held accountable by law. Moreover, there are also confidentiality requirements that relevant personnel must follow when they leave their posts.

We kindly remind you that the Internet is not absolutely secure. Hence, you should carefully protect your personal information when you interact with other users through third-party social software, emails, SMS, and other services integrated into TeraBox under the condition that you are uncertain whether your information is completely encrypted during transfer.

Also, we appreciate your understanding that due to the technical restrictions, rapid development, and various latent and malicious attacks pertaining to the Internet industry, we may not be able to keep your information secure a hundred percent even though we make every effort to enhance our security measures. Hence, the system and communication network based on which you use our product and/or the Services may encounter security problems in other processes beyond our control.

Our security management system regards the disclosure, damage, or loss of personal information as the most serious security event. Once it occurs, our highest-level emergency plan will be implemented with multiple departments dealing with the event as one emergency response team.

We formulate an emergency plan for network security events to promptly respond to system vulnerabilities, computer viruses, cyber-attacks, network intrusions, and other security risks. In case of an event endangering network security, we will immediately carry out the plan, take remedial actions, and report to competent authorities as required.

The disclosure, damage, and loss of personal information are regarded as the most serious security events. Accordingly, we organize members of working groups to perform security plan drills on a regular basis to avoid such events. In the event that such events do occur, we will carry out the emergency plan as a top priority and form an emergency response team to trace the cause and mitigate losses in the shortest time possible.

In case of a personal information security event, we will, as required by laws and regulations, inform you of the basic information about the security event and its possible impact, the measures we have taken or will take, recommendations on actively preventing and mitigating risks for you, and remedial measures for you. We will inform you of event-related information in a timely manner through our notifications or the contact information you have provided to us including SMS, phone number, and email address. If it is difficult to inform our users one by one, we will make announcements in a reasonable and effective way. Meanwhile, we will report the disposal of the personal information security event in accordance with the requirements of regulatory authorities. We appreciate your understanding that according to laws and regulations, if measures taken by us can effectively avoid the harm caused by disclosure, tampering, and loss of information, we may choose not to notify you of a personal information security event unless a regulatory authority requires us to do so.

We refer to the requirements of the GDPR, select appropriate measures for technical security protection based on the nature, scope, background, and purpose of data processing, as well as the risks to individuals, and regularly test and evaluate the measures to maintain their effectiveness.

If data is accidentally disclosed, we will notify affected people as soon as possible and report to competent authorities within 72 hours. If it is impossible to report it within 72 hours, the reason for the delay will be clarified.

We take appropriate technical and organizational measures to achieve our data protection objectives, such as the principle of data minimization and the integration of necessary safeguards into data processing to protect the rights of data subjects and make sure any data processed is necessary for a specific purpose by default.

Where we store and process your information

While providing the Services, we may store, process, and transfer your information in Japan, and you agree to provide your information. Your information may also be stored on the local device used to access the Services.

How you control and access your information

In accordance with the laws, regulations, standards, and established practices of the relevant country and region, we guarantee that you can exercise the following rights for your personal information. If you have any questions or claims about the exercise of rights, you may contact us at [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com). You can view, change, download, delete, or share your information from your TeraBox account.

1\. The right of access

If you wish to know the extent to which your personal information is collected, saved, and shared by TeraBox or the purpose of processing such information, you can contact us for details.

2\. The right of rectification and supplementation

If you find any error in your personal information processed by us, you have the right to rectify the error or add the missing information. After your identity has been verified, you can submit your rectification or supplementation application to us by means of feedback and error reporting or through the aforementioned contact information. We will reply to you as soon as possible after receiving your application.

3\. The right of erasure

You may request us to delete your personal information in the following circumstances:

Our processing of your personal information is in violation of laws and regulations or the agreement with you;

Our processing purpose has been met, cannot be met, or is no longer necessary;

We have stopped providing the product or the Services, or the retention period has expired;

You have decided to withdraw your consent;

Other circumstances required by laws and administrative regulations.

When you delete information from the Services, we may not immediately delete the corresponding information from our backup system, but will delete it after the backup has been updated. We appreciate your acknowledgment and understanding that if the retention period has not yet expired as required by laws and administrative regulations or set forth in this Privacy Policy, or it is technically difficult to delete your personal information, we will stop processing the information other than storing it and taking necessary security protection measures for it.

4\. The right of withdrawal of consent

The implementation of each service or function requires some basic personal information. For any additional collection and use of your personal information, you may give or withdraw your consent at any time.

You can directly disable access to the contacts, photos, camera, and so on in the system of your device, change the scope of consent, or withdraw your authorization.

Following your withdrawal of consent, we cannot continue to provide you with the service involved, and will no longer use the relevant personal information. However, your decision to withdraw your consent will not affect our processing of your personal information previously conducted on the basis of your consent.

5\. The right of account deletion

You may delete the account that you have created. You can delete your account in TeraBox at:

\[Account Avatar\] - \[Menu\] - \[Settings\] - \[Security Center\] - \[Account Deletion\].

Once you have deleted your account, you will not be able to use the Services of TearBox, so please think it through before deletion. For the sake of protecting the legitimate rights and interests of you or other users, we will determine whether to accept your deletion request based on your usage. For example, if you have unused Premium benefits or any data in your account, we will not accept your request immediately. Unless otherwise required by laws and regulations, we will stop providing you with the product and the Services, and delete your personal information according to your requirements after your account has been deleted.

6\. The right of copy and data portability

You have the right to copy your personal information collected by us. On the premise that it is required by laws and regulations, in compliance with the instructions and conditions stipulated by competent authorities, and technically feasible, you may request us to transfer your personal information to another designated subject.

In your exercise of the said rights of personal information subjects, we will update third parties on the relevant information in a timely manner to ensure that the above-mentioned rights are exercised in accordance with laws and regulations, regulatory requirements, and technical feasibility.

If your request is manifestly unjustified or beyond necessity, especially when such request is repetitive, we may:

(a) charge a reasonable fee based on the administrative costs of information provision, communication, or corresponding actions; or

(b) refuse to act on the request.

You can control your retained personal information ("the retained personal information") and decide how it is collected, used, and shared in accordance with the Japan Act on the Protection of Personal Information (APPI). For example, you may

a. request disclosure of the retained personal information that identifies you

b. request corrections, additions, or deletions to the retained personal information when the content of the information that identifies you is not true

c. immediately delete or stop using the retained personal information, if the information was obtained unlawfully by us or if we are using the information in an unlawful manner

d. immediately stop providing the retained personal information if we unlawfully provide the information to a third party

Change

In the event of a reorganization, merger, or acquisition of Flextech or the sale of our assets, your information may be transferred to the surviving entity, acquirer, or successor of the transaction. We will notify you of any such transaction (for example, by a message to the email address associated with your account) and outline your choices in that event.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time. We will release the latest version of it on TeraBox's website if a revision is made. We will notify you if any such revision materially affects your rights.

Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about TeraBox, the Services, or your privacy, please feel free to contact us at [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com).

TeraBoxプライバシーポリシー

TeraBoxプライバシーポリシー

どのような情報がどのような目的で収集されるか

個人情報の第三者への提供について

他のユーザーとのデータの共有

当社は、お客様の情報を第三者と共有することがあります。s

お客様の情報の保護と保存について

当社がお客様の情報を保管し処理する場所

お客様の情報の管理およびアクセス方法

{{ $t('termsOfServicePrivacyPolicy.age.title') }}

変更

お問い合わせ

TeraBoxプライバシーポリシー

投稿日：2023年4月18日

発行日：2023年4月18日

TeraBoxをご利用いただき、ありがとうございます。TeraBoxは、フレックステック株式会社（以下、「フレックステック」または「当社」といいます）が提供するサービスです。当社は、お客様のプライバシーを保護することに努めています。このプライバシーポリシーは、お客様が当社のウェブサイト、ソフトウェア、サービス（以下総称して「サービス」といいます）にアクセスする際に、当社がお客様の情報をどのように収集、保管、処理、共有、使用するかを定めたものです。

当社は、合法的、適法かつ必要な目的のためにのみ、お客様の個人情報を収集し、使用します。具体的には、当社は、お客様に当社のサービスを提供するために、お客様の個人情報を収集し、処理します。

当社は、法令に従い、特定の状況において、別途お客様の同意を求めることがあります。当社は、本プライバシーポリシーに加えて、サービス上での通知、ポップアップ通知、プッシュ通知等を通じて、お客様の個人情報の処理に関する当社の規則について説明することがあります。各サービスにおける個人情報の処理について別途当社がルールを設ける場合、当該ルールは本プライバシーポリシーに優先して適用されます。

どのような情報がどのような目的で収集されるか

以下の表は、お客様が本サービスを利用する際に当社に提出する情報の種類と、当社がその情報を利用する目的を示しています。当社は、本サービスを提供し、最適化し、保護し、促進するために、以下の情報を収集し、利用します。

| 情報カテゴリ | 収集目的 |
| --- | --- |
| アカウント情報： アカウント登録時に必要となるメールアドレス等に関する情報（ＳＮＳ等を利用して登録する場合、当該ＳＮＳ上のニックネーム及びアイコン） | お客様のアカウント権限の照合及びアカウント保護のため。お客様がアカウントにログインした時、当社は左記情報を収集等します。 |
| ユーザーマテリアル： TeraBoxにお客様が保存するファイル、ドキュメント、写真、ビデオ、音楽等に関するデータ | 当社が本サービスの適切な運用を行うため。お客様が他のユーザーと連携し、また、ご利用の複数の端末及びサービスにてご利用いただけるように保存、処理及び送信するため。これにはお客様のプロフィール情報、ファイルサイズ、並びにアップロード及び利用の日時などの関連情報を含みます。 |
| 利用情報： ファイルまたはフォルダの編集、閲覧、制作、移動、利用など、本サービスの利用状況に関する情報 | 本サービスの提供、改善、促進及びユーザーの保護のため。 |
| デバイス情報： IPアドレス、ブラウザ、デバイス情報、TeraBox訪問前にアクセスしたWebページに関する情報、端末識別子、位置情報（ご利用のデバイスの設定に応じる）など、端末から発せられる、または端末に関する情報 | 本サービスの改善及び保全のため。 |
| Cookie（またはCookieに類似する技術）： TeraBoxにアクセスしたときにウェブサイトからブラウザに送信されたテキストの一部に関する情報。お客様は、ブラウザの設定によりクッキーを受け入れないようにすることができますが、これによって本サービスの機能に制限を与える可能性があります。 | 本サービスの提供、改善、保全及びプロモーションのため。Cookieによって、お客様のユーザー名を記憶し、本サービス使用状況を理解することで、本サービスの改善を実現します。当社が提携する第三者のサービスプロバイダーとの間でこの情報を共有して利用する場合もあります。 |
| 連絡先情報：シェア機能を利用して、端末内のデータやアドレス帳に記録されている連絡先（携帯電話番号やメールアドレス）に関する情報（以下「連絡先情報」といいます。）を、特定または不特定のSNS上の友人（Facebook、Twitterなど）と共有することができます。連絡先情報はユーザーにとって機密性の高い情報ですので、ユーザーがこの情報の提供を拒否しても、上記のシェア機能を使用できなくなるだけで、TeraBoxやその他の関連サービスの機能の利用は制限されません。 | ユーザーは、TeraBoxによる連絡先情報へのアクセスを許可するかどうかをご自身の判断で決定することができますが、アクセスを許可した場合、ユーザーはE-mailを送信することで、データを他のユーザーと共同して処理したり、メッセージを送信したり、また友人をTeraBoxのサービスに招待したりすることができるようになるなど、より快適に機能を利用できるようになります。この場合、ユーザーからの許可を得て当社は当該情報を当社のサーバー内に保管し、ユーザーによるサービスの利便性向上のために使用します。シェア機能を利用する場合、事前にメッセージの受信者が適切な相手であるかどうかを十分に検討してください。  <br>同時に、慎重な意思決定のために、ご利用のSNSまたは第三者が提供するサービスのプライバシー情報の取扱い方法を示した指針等をご確認の上、ユーザーの情報がどのように扱われるかを事前に理解してから利用することをお勧めします。 |
| クリップボード：他のユーザーの招待コードを使用してTeraboxアカウントを登録し、他のユーザーが共有したファイルリンクにアクセスしたり、パスワードを使用して友達を追加したり、兑换コードを使用して会员サービスを取得したりする場合、私たちはクリップボードの情報を読み取ります | 私たちはクリップボードの情報にアクセスして、リンクに対応するファイルを開くお手伝いをし、パスワードや招待コードに対応するユーザーを識別したり、会員サービスをお客様のために交換したりします。私たちは他の目的でクリップボードを読み取ることは決してありません。 |

お客様は、携帯電話番号を使ってTeraBoxのアカウントを作成することができます。法令に基づく場合、当社が製品またはサービスを提供するために必要な場合、またはアカウントのセキュリティを強化するためにお客様のご要望に基づく場合、お客様はTeraBoxの一部のサービスを利用するため、またはお客様のさらなるニーズに応えるために、アカウント認証のために本人確認のために必要な資料、情報を追加で提供する必要が生じる場合があります。

上記の情報は、本サービスを確実かつ安全に提供するため、および正当な事業目的のために収集されます。当社または当社のパートナーは、具体的に記載された目的以外の目的でお客様の情報を処理する場合は事前に、お客様の同意を得た上で当該処理を行います。

お客様は、当社が、本サービスにおいてお客様から能動的または受動的に提供された個人情報を、当社または当社の業務委託先の処理により集約、統合、特定、分析、描写、またはさらに加工して、お客様の操作習慣、興味または信用を反映した粒度の異なる様々なラベル情報（以下「ラベル情報」という）を形成することに同意するものとします。当社は、ラベル情報を、特定のシナリオおよびアプリケーションにおいて、お客様にパーソナライズされた情報および/またはマーケティング情報を自動的に判別して送信するために使用します。

お客様は、本ポリシーに記載された連絡先を通じて当社に連絡するか、または本サービスの関連する機能スイッチを使用して当社に上記の方法による使用の停止を要求することができます。

適用される法令により、お客様にパーソナライズされた情報および/またはマーケティング情報を自動的に判別して送信することが禁止または規制される場合、当社は必要に応じてそれらに従います。

当社は、お客様のアカウントデータをマーケティング目的で使用し、TeraBoxの新製品、アップグレード、その他のマーケティング資料に関する情報を随時お客様に送信することになります。お客様は、受信したメールに記載されている「配信停止」リンクをクリックすることで、いつでもマーケティング資料の受信を停止することができます。

個人情報の第三者への提供について

当社は、以下に定める場合を除いて、お客様からの事前の許可と同意を得ない限り、お客様の個人情報を第三者と共有または、第三者に提供することはありません。

（a）適用される法律、規制、法的手続きに基づく場合または法令に基づく行政機関、司法機関から個人情報の開示の要求があった場合であって、事前にお客様からの許可を得ることが困難な場合。;

（b）人の生命、身体又は財産の保護のために必要がある場合であって、事前にお客様からの許可を得ることが困難な場合。

（c）公衆衛生の向上または児童の健全な育成の推進のために特に必要がある場合であって、事前にお客様の同意を得ることが困難である場合。

上記の例外的な状況下でお客様の個人情報を共有、移転または開示する場合、当社は、お客様の正当な権利および利益を保護するために、共有、移転または開示する個人情報の範囲は必要最小限の範囲にとどめ、以下に列挙する関連情報の処理根拠、処理する情報の範囲、受取人に関する情報等を記録いたします。

(1) データ管理者およびデータ保護責任者の氏名および連絡先

(2) データ処理の目的

(3) データ主体の種類および個人データの種類の記述

(4) 個人データが開示された、または開示される予定の受領者の種類（第三国または国際機関の受領者を含む）

(5) 第三国または国際機関に個人データを移転した記録および適切な保護措置の記録

(6) 異なる種類のデータの削除予定時間

(7) 技術的および組織的安全対策の一般的記述。

他のユーザーとのデータの共有

お客様が当社が提供するチームコラボレーション機能またはファイル共有機能を使用する場合、お客様とコラボレーションするユーザー又は、お客様がファイル共有をすることを許可した他のユーザーに対して、お客様のニックネーム、端末の種類、電子メールアドレス、およびサービスの使用状況が表示されることがあります。これは、お客様が参加しているチームとの同期や、お客様が許可した他のユーザーとのファイルやフォルダーの共有のための利便性の向上を目的としています。

当社は、お客様の情報を第三者と共有することがあります。

当社は、カスタマーサポートやITサービスの提供者などの第三者のパートナー企業に、業務の処理を委託することがあります。これらの業務委託によって本サービスを提供、改善、保全またはプロモーションを実施するために、パートナー企業がお客様の情報を使用することがありますが、この場合、当社は、パートナー企業によるお客様の情報の利用行為に対して責任を負います。

当社は、本サービスの提供、改善、保全及びプロモーションのため、当社の関連企業とインフラ、システム及びテクノロジーを共有することがあります。これらの関連企業は、当社と共同して、上記「収集情報とその目的」に記載の目的に従って使用します。当社は、これらの関連企業において、お客様の情報が安全かつ適切に使用されることを保証し、これに対して責任を負います。

お客様は、第三者のサービスを介して、お客様のTeraBoxアカウントを接続することもできます。このようなサービスを介して接続することにより、お客様は当社及び第三者に対し、サービスの提供、改善、保全及びプロモーションの目的で、「収集情報とその目的」に記載されているお客様の情報を交換することを許可します。この場合、お客様の情報の使用は、お客様が接続することを選択した第三者のサービスに関して定められたプライバシーポリシーおよびサービスの条件に従って取り扱われることになります。

お客様は、適用される法令、規則、法手続きまたは政府決定に従うことが合理的に必要であると当社が判断する限りにおいて、または人の生命または身体に対する重大な、若しくは深刻な被害が生じることを防ぐ目的で、第三者に対しお客様の情報を開示することに合意します。

当社は、収集情報の処理を当社のグループ企業を含む外国にある第三者に委託することがあります。当該外国の個人情報保護制度は、日本とは異なる場合がありますが、当社は、法令上許容される場合を除いては、日本の個人情報保護法上求められる基準に適合する体制を整備している者に対してのみ、収集情報を提供し、かつ、当該適合体制が継続的に維持されるよう、必要な措置を講じております。当社は厳重に法律に沿ってデータを海外に送信する際の安全性に関して評価・遵守し、お客様の個人情報を保護します。また委託先との間で個人情報保護契約の締結又は、グループに共通して適用される内規等により、委託先が日本の個人情報保護水準と同等の措置を講じることを義務付けます。

当社は、当該必要な措置に関する情報を、お客様からの求めに応じて提供することとしておりますので、ご希望のお客様は、「連絡先」記載の担当窓口までお問い合わせください。

当社は、GDPRの要件を参照して、国境を越えたデータ転送のための出力メカニズムを確立し、必要に応じてそれを更新します。当社の個人データの処理は、GDPRの基本原則、有効なデータ対象者の同意、またはその他の正当な理由によって決まります。それとは別に、データを保護し、データ処理に関するGDPRの実質的な要件を満たすために、追加のメカニズムが導入されます。

お客様の情報の保護と保存について

当社は、お客様の情報を安全に保ち、脆弱性をテストするために専門チームを編成しています。二要素認証、ファイルの暗号化、新しいデバイスやアプリケーションがお客様のアカウントにリンクした際のアラートに加え、当社はお客様の情報の安全性を確保するために努力を続けています。当社は、自動化された技術を導入し、お客様、他のユーザー、または本サービスに害を及ぼす可能性のある不正行為やコンテンツを検出しています。

お客様がTeraBoxアカウントを登録した後、当社はお客様が本サービスに保存した情報を、お客様のアカウントが存在する限り、またはお客様に本サービスを提供するために必要な限り、保持します。お客様がアカウントの削除を希望される場合、その旨を記載したメールを [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) 宛てに送信するか、「お客様の情報の管理およびアクセス方法」に記載の方法でアカウントの削除を申請してください。お客様のリクエストを受信後、30日以内にアカウントを削除します。

当社は、本サービスを提供するために必要な期間、お客様の個人情報を保管します。ただし、法令に別段の定めがある場合、お客様の同意がある場合、本サービスの安全性および品質を確保するために必要な場合、紛争解決のために必要な場合、または技術的に必要な処理が困難な場合には、法令および合意に従って、または前述の期間満了後に合理的な範囲で保管期間を延長します。 保存期間が満了した場合、当社は、法令に従い、お客様の個人情報を削除し、または個人情報の識別を解除します。

当社は、セキュリティ管理担当者、セキュリティ上重要なポジションにある者のセキュリティ経歴調査を実施しています。情報セキュリティ管理体制を整備し、セキュリティ事象などに対応する社内体制を構築しています。当社は、お客様の個人情報を保管・保護するために、業界標準に沿った適切なセキュリティ対策と技術的手段を講じ、お客様の情報の紛失や不正アクセス、開示、使用、損傷、漏洩を防止しています。お客様の個人情報を保護するために、合理的かつ実行可能なすべての措置を講じています。また、データの機密性を確保するために暗号化技術を使用し、データへの悪意のある攻撃を防ぐために信頼できる保護メカニズムを適用しています。 個人情報保護の重要性を理解するため、従業員に対して情報セキュリティ意識およびセキュリティ能力の教育・評価を実施しています。個人情報を取り扱う従業員の本人確認とアクセス管理、個人情報にアクセスできる従業員やパートナーとの秘密保持契約の締結、職務責任と行動規範の明確化などを行い、権限を与えられた者だけが個人情報にアクセスできるようにしています。当社の従業員は、退職後も引き続き守秘義務を負います。 インターネットは絶対に安全というわけではありません。したがって、TeraBoxに統合された第三者のソーシャルソフトウェア、Eメール、SMSなどのサービスを通じて他のユーザーと交流する際、あなたの情報が完全に暗号化されているかどうかが不明な場合は、あなたの個人情報を慎重に保護する必要があります。 また、インターネット業界における技術的な制約、急速な発展、様々な潜在的・悪意ある攻撃により、当社がセキュリティ対策の強化に努めても、お客様の情報を100％安全に保つことができない可能性があることをご理解くださいますようお願いいたします。したがって、お客様が当社製品および/またはサービスを利用するシステムおよび通信ネットワークは、当社が制御できない別のプロセスでセキュリティ上の問題が発生する可能性があります。当社のセキュリティ管理体制では、個人情報の漏洩、毀損、紛失を最も重要なセキュリティ事象と位置づけています。このような事態が発生した場合、複数の部門が一つの緊急対応チームとなり、最高レベルの緊急対応計画を実施します。システムの脆弱性、コンピューターウイルス、サイバー攻撃、ネットワーク侵入などのセキュリティリスクに迅速に対応するため、ネットワークセキュリティ事象の緊急対応計画を策定しています。ネットワークセキュリティに脅威を与える事象が発生した場合、直ちに計画を実行し、是正措置を講じるとともに、必要に応じて監督官庁に報告します。

個人情報の漏えい、破壊、紛失は、セキュリティ上最も重大な事象と位置づけています。そのため、定期的にセキュリティ対策訓練を実施し、その回避に努めています。万が一、このような事態が発生した場合には、緊急対策を最優先に実施し、緊急対策本部を設置して原因究明と被害拡大の防止措置を最優先で行います。個人情報のセキュリティ事象が発生した場合、セキュリティ事象の基本情報及び想定される影響、当社が講じた又は講じる予定の対策、お客様に対するリスクの積極的な予防及び軽減のための外に関する情報や改善策を、サービス上での通知またはSMS、電話番号、電子メールアドレスなどお客様が当社に提供した連絡先を通じて、適時にお知らせします。

また、お客様に個別にお知らせすることが困難な場合は、当社のウェブサイト上での掲示など合理的かつ効果的な方法で告知を行います。

当社は、GDPRの要件を参照し、データ処理の性質、範囲、背景、目的、および個人に対するリスクに基づいて技術的なセキュリティ保護のための適切な措置を選択し、その有効性を維持するために定期的に措置をテストし評価します。 データが誤って開示された場合、影響を受ける人々にできるだけ早く通知し、72時間以内に監督官庁に報告します。72時間以内に報告することが不可能な場合は、その理由を明らかにします。 当社は、データの最小化の原則や、データ主体の権利を保護するために必要な保護措置をデータ処理に組み込むなど、データ保護の目的を達成するために適切な技術的・組織的措置をとり、処理されるデータがデフォルトで特定の目的のために必要であることを確認します。

当社がお客様の情報を保管し処理する場所

本サービスを提供する間、当社はお客様の情報を日本国内で保存、処理、転送することがあり、お客様は、お客様の情報を提供することに同意します。また、お客様の情報は、本サービスにアクセスするために使用されるローカルデバイスに保存される場合があります。

お客様の情報の管理およびアクセス方法

当社は、関連する国および地域の法令、基準および確立された慣行に従って、お客様がご自身の個人情報に関して以下の権利を行使できることを保証します。権利の行使に関してご質問やクレームがある場合は、[helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com)までご連絡ください。お客様は、TeraBoxのアカウントから、ご自身の情報を閲覧、変更、ダウンロード、削除、共有することができます。

1\. アクセス権 お客様がご自身の個人情報がTeraBoxによってどの程度収集、保存、共有されているか、またはそのような情報の処理目的について知りたい場合は、当社にご連絡ください。

2\. 修正・補完の権利 当社が処理したお客様の個人情報に誤りがあった場合、お客様はその誤りを修正し、または不足している情報を追加する権利を有します。ご本人であることが確認された後、フィードバックやエラー報告、または前述の連絡先を通じて、修正または補完の申請を当社に提出することができます。当社は申請を受領後、速やかに対応いたします。

3\. 消去権 お客様は、以下の場合に、ご自身の個人情報を消去するよう当社に要求することができます。

a. 当社によるお客様の個人情報の処理が法令またはお客様との契約に違反している場合

b. 当社の処理目的が達成された場合、達成できない場合、またはもはや必要でない場合

c. 当社が製品またはサービスの提供を停止した場合、または保存期間が終了した場合

d. お客様が当社による個人情報の収集や利用等に関する同意を撤回することにした場合

e. その他法令および行政法規で要求される場合

お客様が本サービスから情報を削除した場合、当社はバックアップシステムから該当する情報を直ちに削除しないことがありますが、バックアップが更新された後に削除します。法令や行政規則で定められた、または本プライバシーポリシーで定められた保存期間が経過していない場合、または技術的にお客様の個人情報を削除することが困難な場合は、情報の保存とそれに必要なセキュリティ保護措置以外の処理を停止します。

4\. 同意撤回権 各サービスや機能の実施には、いくつかの基本的な個人情報が必要です。お客様の個人情報の追加的な収集と使用については、お客様はいつでも同意を与えたり撤回したりすることができます。 お客様は、お客様のデバイスのシステム内の連絡先、写真、カメラなどへのアクセスを直接無効にしたり、同意の範囲を変更したり、お客様の承認を撤回したりすることができます。 お客様が同意を撤回された場合、当社は当該サービスを継続して提供することができず、当該個人情報を利用することはありません。ただし、お客様が同意を撤回することを決定しても、お客様の同意に基づき過去に行われた当社の個人情報の処理には影響しません。

5\. アカウント削除の権利 お客様は、作成したアカウントを削除することができます。アカウントの削除は、TeraBoxより以下の操作をすることで行えます。

\[アカウントアバター\]-\[メニュー\]-\[設定\]-\[セキュリティセンター\]-\[アカウント削除\]

アカウントを削除すると、TeraBoxのサービスを利用できなくなりますので、削除する際は十分ご注意ください。法令に別段の定めがある場合を除き、当社は、お客様のアカウントが削除された後、お客様の要求に従って、製品およびサービスの提供を停止し、お客様の個人情報を削除します。ただし、1）当社は、リクエストの送信者がお客様本人であることを確認するまで、お客様のアカウント情報を削除しません。2）当社のサーバーおよびバックアップストレージからの当該情報の削除は遅れることがあります。3）当社は、当社の法的義務の履行、紛争の解決、または契約に基づく当社の権利行使のために必要な場合には、当該情報を保持することがあります。

6\. 複写権およびデータポータビリティ お客様は、当社が収集したお客様の個人情報を複製する権利を有します。お客様は、法令に基づく場合、監督官庁の指示・条件に従う場合、および技術的に可能である場合を前提として、お客様の個人情報を他の指定された主体に移転するよう当社に要求することができます。 お客様が個人情報主体の前記権利を行使する場合、当社は、法令、規制要件及び技術的実現可能性に従って前記権利が行使されるように、適切な措置を講じます。 お客様の請求が明らかに不当または必要を超える場合、特にそのような請求が繰り返される場合、当社は当該請求を拒否または、情報提供、連絡などの対応に要する管理コストに基づき、合理的な料金を請求することができるものとします。

お客様は、ご自身の保有する個人情報（以下「保有個人情報」といいます）を管理し、日本国の個人情報保護法に従い、その収集、利用および共同利用の方法を決定することができます。例えば、お客様は以下のことが可能です。

a. お客様が識別される保有個人データの開示を請求すること。

b. 保有個人データの内容が事実でない場合に、訂正、追加または削除を請求すること。

c. 当社が不正に入手したものである場合、または不正に使用されている場合は、直ちに当該保有個人情報の削除または利用停止を請求すること。

d. 当社が不正に第三者へ個人情報を提供した場合、直ちに当該個人情報の提供の停止を請求すること。

変更

当社の組織再編、合併、買収または当社資産の売却が行われた場合、お客様の情報は取引の存続企業、買収者または後継者に譲渡される可能性があります。当社は、そのような取引についてお客様に通知し（例えば、お客様のアカウントに関連付けられた電子メールアドレスへのメッセージ）、その際のお客様の選択肢の概要を説明します。

本プライバシーポリシーは、適宜変更されることがあります。変更された場合は、TeraBoxのウェブサイト上で最新版を公開します。また、お客様の権利に重大な影響を及ぼすような変更があった場合には、お客様に通知いたします。

お問い合わせ

TeraBox、本サービス、お客様のプライバシーに関するご質問やご不明な点がございましたら、[helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) までお気軽にお問い合わせください。

TeraBox นโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัว

TeraBox นโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัว

เนื้อหาและวัตถุประสงค์ในการรวบรวมข้อมูล

ให้ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลแก่บุคคลที่สาม

แบ่งปันกับผู้ใช้รายอื่น

เราอาจแบ่งปันข้อมูลของคุณกับบุคคลที่สาม

เราปกป้องและจัดเก็บข้อมูลของคุณอย่างไร

เราจัดเก็บและประมวลผลข้อมูลของคุณที่ไหน

คุณควบคุมและเข้าถึงข้อมูลของคุณได้อย่างไร

{{ $t('termsOfServicePrivacyPolicy.age.title') }}

การเปลี่ยน

ติดต่อเรา:

TeraBox นโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัว

วันที่ประกาศ: วันที่ 18 เมษายน 2566

วันที่มีผล: วันที่ 18 เมษายน 2566

ขอบคุณที่คุณใช้ TeraBox TeraBox ให้บริการแก่คุณโดย Flextech Inc. ("Flextech" หรือ "เรา") เรามุ่งมั่นที่จะปกป้องความเป็นส่วนตัวของคุณ นโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวนี้กำหนดวิธีที่เรารวบรวม จัดเก็บ ประมวลผล แบ่งปันและใช้ข้อมูลของคุณเมื่อคุณใช้เว็บไซต์ ซอฟต์แวร์และบริการ ("บริการ") ของเรา

เราจะรวบรวมและใช้ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณตามหลักกฎหมาย ความยุติธรรม และความจำเป็น โดยเฉพาะอย่างยิ่ง เรารวบรวมและประมวลผลข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณเพื่อจัดหาฟังก์ชันธุรกิจที่เกี่ยวข้องให้กับคุณ ในฟังก์ชันที่เกี่ยวข้อง หากคุณให้ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของผู้อื่น โปรดตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าคุณได้รับอนุญาตจากบุคคลที่เกี่ยวข้อง เราขอสงวนสิทธิ์ในการตรวจสอบแหล่งที่มาทางกฎหมายของข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลดังกล่าวได้ตลอดเวลา

เราจะปฏิบัติตามข้อกำหนดของกฎหมายและข้อบังคับอย่างเคร่งครัด และขอความยินยอมจากคุณเพียงอย่างเดียวภายใต้สถานการณ์เฉพาะ นอกจากนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวนี้แล้ว เรายังอาจอธิบายให้คุณทราบถึงกฎของเราสำหรับการประมวลผลข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณผ่านการแจ้งเตือนในหน้าผลิตภัณฑ์ หน้าต่างป๊อปอัป การพุชข้อมูล ฯลฯ กฎเฉพาะจะมีผลบังคับใช้สำหรับการประมวลผลข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เกี่ยวข้องกับเฉพาะฟังก์ชันธุรกิจ กฎเฉพาะจะมีผลเช่นเดียวกับนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวนี้

โปรดทราบ: ในสถานการณ์ต่อไปนี้ การรวบรวม การใช้ การแบ่งปัน การถ่ายโอน และการเปิดเผยข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลสู่สาธารณะไม่จำเป็นต้องมีการอนุญาตและยินยอมล่วงหน้าจากคุณ:

เกี่ยวข้องโดยตรงกับความมั่นคงของชาติและความมั่นคงในการป้องกันประเทศ

จำเป็นสำหรับการสรุปและการปฏิบัติตามสัญญาที่บุคคลนั้นเป็นคู่สัญญา

จำเป็นสำหรับการปฏิบัติหน้าที่ตามกฎหมายหรือภาระผูกพัน

จำเป็นต่อการตอบสนองต่อเหตุฉุกเฉินด้านสาธารณสุข หรือเพื่อปกป้องชีวิต สุขภาพ และความปลอดภัยของทรัพย์สินของบุคคลธรรมดาในสถานการณ์ฉุกเฉิน

เกี่ยวข้องโดยตรงกับการสืบสวนคดีอาญา การฟ้องร้อง การพิจารณาคดีและการบังคับคดี

เพื่อปกป้องชีวิตส่วนตัว ทรัพย์สิน และสิทธิ์ทางกฎหมายที่สำคัญอื่นๆ ของคุณหรืออื่นๆ แต่เป็นการยากที่จะได้รับความยินยอมจากบุคคลนั้น

รวบรวมข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่คุณเปิดเผยต่อสาธารณะหรือได้รับการเปิดเผยตามกฎหมายด้วยตนเองภายในขอบเขตที่เหมาะสมตามบทบัญญัติของกฎหมายและข้อบังคับ

รวบรวมข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณในขอบเขตที่เหมาะสมจากข้อมูลที่เปิดเผยตามกฎหมายตามบทบัญญัติของกฎหมายและข้อบังคับช่องทางต่าง ๆ เช่น รายงานข่าวทางกฎหมาย การเปิดเผยข้อมูลของภาครัฐ ฯลฯ

ดำเนินการรายงานข่าว การกำกับดูแลความคิดเห็นสาธารณะ และการกระทำอื่น ๆ เพื่อผลประโยชน์สาธารณะ และประมวลผลข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลภายในขอบเขตที่เหมาะสม

สถาบันการวิจัยเชิงวิชาการจำเป็นต้องดำเนินการวิจัยเชิงสถิติหรือเชิงวิชาการตามความสนใจของสาธารณะ และเมื่อให้ผลการวิจัยเชิงวิชาการหรือคำอธิบายแก่โลกภายนอก ให้ยกเลิกการระบุข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่อยู่ในผลลัพธ์

สถานการณ์อื่น ๆ ที่กำหนดโดยกฎหมายและข้อบังคับที่เกี่ยวข้อง

เนื้อหาและวัตถุประสงค์ในการรวบรวมข้อมูล

ตารางด้านล่างระบุประเภทของข้อมูลที่คุณส่งให้เราเมื่อใช้บริการเหล่านี้ รวมทั้งวัตถุประสงค์ที่เราสามารถใช้ข้อมูลเหล่านี้ เรารวบรวมและใช้ข้อมูลต่อไปนี้เพื่อจัดหา เพิ่มประสิทธิภาพ ปกป้องและส่งเสริมการบริการของเรา

| ประเภทข้อมูล | วัตถุประสงค์ของการรวบรวม |
| --- | --- |
| ข้อมูลบัญชี เราจะรวบรวมข้อมูล เช่น ที่อยู่อีเมล หมายเลขโทรศัพท์ ฯลฯ ที่คุณให้กับเราเมื่อคุณดำเนินการบางอย่าง (เช่น การลงทะเบียนบัญชี) (หากคุณเข้าสู่ระบบหรือเข้าสู่ระบบด้วยบัญชี SNS เราจะได้รับชื่อเล่นของคุณและข้อมูลรูปโปรไฟล์ SNS ) และเชื่อมโยงข้อมูลเหล่านี้กับบัญชีของคุณ | เราสามารถใช้ข้อมูลนี้เพื่อระบุว่าคุณเป็นเจ้าของบัญชีและเพื่อรักษาบัญชีของคุณให้ปลอดภัย เราอาจรวบรวมข้อมูลเหล่านี้เมื่อคุณลงชื่อเข้าใช้บัญชีของคุณ |
| ข้อมูลผู้ใช้ เนื้อหาที่คุณจัดเก็บไว้ใน TeraBox เช่น ไฟล์ เอกสาร ภาพถ่าย วิดีโอ และเสียง (“ข้อมูลผู้ใช้”) | เราอาจจัดเก็บ ประมวลผล และส่งข้อมูลผู้ใช้และข้อมูลที่เกี่ยวข้องเพื่อให้แน่ใจว่าการทำงานบริการเป็นไปอย่างเหมาะสม และเพื่อให้คุณสามารถทำงานร่วมกับผู้อื่นและทำงานในอุปกรณ์และบริการต่าง ๆ ได้ ข้อมูลที่เกี่ยวข้องนี้รวมถึงข้อมูลไฟล์การกำหนดค่า ขนาดไฟล์ วันที่และเวลาที่อัปโหลดรวมทั้งกิจกรรมการใช้งานของคุณ |
| ข้อมูลการใช้งาน ข้อมูลเกี่ยวกับวิธีการใช้บริการ รวมถึงการดำเนินการภายในบัญชี เช่น การแก้ไข การดู การสร้างและการย้ายไฟล์หรือแฟ้ม | เราอาจใช้ข้อมูลนี้เพื่อจัดหา ปรับปรุง และส่งเสริมการบริการ และเพื่อปกป้องผู้ใช้ TeraBox |
| ข้อมูลอุปกรณ์ ข้อมูลเกี่ยวกับอุปกรณ์ที่ใช้ในการเข้าถึงการบริการ เช่น ที่อยู่ IP ข้อมูลเบราว์เซอร์และอุปกรณ์ หน้าเว็บที่เข้าชมก่อนเข้าถึง TeraBox ตัวระบุที่เกี่ยวข้องกับอุปกรณ์ รวมทั้งข้อมูลตำแหน่งขึ้นอยู่กับการตั้งค่าอุปกรณ์ | เราสามารถใช้ข้อมูลเหล่านี้เพื่อปรับปรุงและปกป้องการบริการของเรา |
| คุกกี้ เมื่อคุณเข้าชม TeraBox ข้อความเล็ก ๆ ที่ส่งไปยังเบราว์เซอร์ของคุณโดยเว็บไซต์ คุณสามารถตั้งค่าเบราว์เซอร์ไม่ให้ยอมรับคุกกี้ แต่สิ่งนี้อาจส่งผลต่อฟังก์ชันของการบริการ | เราอาจใช้คุกกี้และเทคโนโลยีที่คล้ายกันเพื่อจัดหา ปรับปรุง ปกป้อง และส่งเสริมการบริการ คุกกี้ช่วยให้เราจดจำชื่อผู้ใช้ของคุณ ทำความเข้าใจการใช้บริการของคุณ และปรับปรุงการบริการตามข้อมูลเหล่านี้ ผู้ให้บริการบุคคลที่สามที่เราทำงานร่วมกันอาจใช้คุกกี้และเทคโนโลยีที่คล้ายกัน |
| วิธีการติดต่อ คุณสามารถใช้ฟังก์ชันการแบ่งปันของ TeraBox เพื่อแบ่งปันข้อมูลของคุณกับผู้ติดต่อในรายชื่อผู้ติดต่อของโทรศัพท์ หมายเลขโทรศัพท์ ที่อยู่อีเมล (เช่น Facebook Twitter) ข้อมูลรายชื่อผู้ติดต่อเป็นข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่ละเอียดอ่อน การปฏิเสธที่จะให้ข้อมูลนี้จะทำให้คุณไม่สามารถใช้ฟังก์ชันข้างต้นได้ แต่จะไม่ส่งผลต่อการใช้ของฟังก์ชันอื่น ๆ และบริการที่เกี่ยวข้องตามปกติของ TeraBox ของคุณ | คุณอาจเลือกที่จะอนุญาตให้ TeraBox เข้าถึงข้อมูลติดต่อของคุณเพื่ออำนวยความสะดวกในการดำเนินการบางอย่าง เช่น การแบ่งปันและการทำงานร่วมกับผู้อื่นในข้อมูลของคุณ การส่งข้อความ และการเชิญผู้อื่นให้ใช้บริการ TeraBox โดยการส่งอีเมล การดำเนินการนี้กำหนดให้คุณต้องเปิดใช้งานสิทธิ์ในรายชื่อผู้ติดต่อ เราจะจัดเก็บข้อมูลนี้ไว้บนเซิร์ฟเวอร์ของเราเพื่อการใช้งานของคุณ โปรดพิจารณาความน่าเชื่อถือของผู้รับข้อความก่อนแบ่งปัน ในเวลาเดียวกัน เราขอแนะนำให้คุณตรวจสอบคำชี้แจงสิทธิส่วนบุคคลของโซเชียลเน็ตเวิร์กหรือผู้ให้บริการบุคคลที่สาม เพื่อทำความเข้าใจวิธีที่พวกเขาจัดการข้อมูลของคุณ เพื่อทำการตัดสินใจอย่างรอบคอบ |
| คลิปบอร์ด เมื่อคุณลงทะเบียนบัญชี Terabox โดยใช้รหัสเชิญของคนอื่น ๆ เข้าถึงลิงก์ไฟล์ที่ผู้ใช้อื่น ๆ แชร์ หรือเพิ่มเพื่อนผ่านรหัสผ่านหรือรับบริการสมาชิกผ่านรหัสการแลกเปลี่ยน เราจะอ่านข้อมูลคลิปบอร์ดของคุณ | เราจะเข้าถึงข้อมูลในคลิปบอร์ดเพื่อช่วยคุณเปิดไฟล์ที่ตรงกับลิงค์ ระบุผู้ใช้ที่ตรงกับรหัสผ่านและรหัสเชิญ หรือแลกรับบริการสมาชิกให้คุณ เราจะไม่อ่านคลิปบอร์ดของคุณด้วยวัตถุประสงค์อื่นใดๆ เด็ดขาด |

คุณสามารถสร้างบัญชี TeraBox ผ่านหมายเลขโทรศัพท์และกรอกข้อมูลบัญชีของคุณ

เพื่อให้เป็นไปตามข้อกำหนดบังคับของกฎหมายและข้อบังคับ เพื่อจัดหาผลิตภัณฑ์หรือบริการ หรือตามความต้องการของคุณสำหรับการปกป้องบัญชีขั้นสูง เมื่อคุณใช้บริการบางอย่างของ TeraBox หรือคุณมีความจำเป็นเพิ่มเติม คุณต้องระบุชื่อจริง หมายเลขประจำตัวประชาชน และข้อมูลใบหน้าเพื่อทำการยืนยันบัญชีให้เสร็จสมบูรณ์ เพื่อตรวจสอบความถูกต้องและครบถ้วนของข้อมูลที่คุณให้ หรือเพื่อปกป้องความปลอดภัยของบัญชีของคุณ เราอาจเปรียบเทียบและตรวจสอบข้อมูลชื่อจริงที่คุณให้กับ TeraBox กับข้อมูลที่สอดคล้องกัน ซึ่งเก็บรักษาไว้โดยสถาบันทางกฎหมายและข้อบังคับอนุญาตหรือได้รับอนุญาตจากหน่วยงานรัฐบาล

ข้อมูลข้างต้นถูกรวบรวมเพื่อการให้บริการที่เชื่อถือได้ ปลอดภัยและเพื่อวัตถุประสงค์ทางธุรกิจที่ถูกต้องตามกฎหมาย เราหรือพันธมิตรของเราจะขอความยินยอมล่วงหน้าจากคุณก่อนประมวลผลข้อมูลของคุณเพื่อวัตถุประสงค์อื่น

คุณตกลงว่าเราจะรวบรวม ระบุ วิเคราะห์ จัดทำโปรไฟล์หรือประมวลผลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่คุณให้ไว้ในบริการนี้ทั้งในเชิงรุกหรือเชิงรับผ่านเทคโนโลยีของเราเองหรือเทคโนโลยีของบุคคลที่ได้รับมอบหมาย และสร้างข้อมูลแท็กประเภทต่าง ๆ และรายละเอียดต่าง ๆ ที่สามารถสะท้อนพฤติกรรม งานอดิเรก หรือสถานะเครดิตของคุณ (ต่อไปนี้จะเรียกว่า "ข้อมูลแท็ก") ฯลฯ เราจะใช้ข้อมูลแท็กสำหรับสถานการณ์และวัตถุประสงค์เฉพาะเพื่อทำการตัดสินใจโดยอัตโนมัติ และส่งข้อมูลการแสดงผลส่วนบุคคลและ/หรือข้อมูลการตลาดเชิงพาณิชย์ให้กับคุณ

คุณมีสิทธิ์ที่จะปฏิเสธบริการทางเทคนิคสำหรับการตัดสินใจโดยอัตโนมัติของเรา คุณสามารถติดต่อเราผ่านข้อมูลติดต่อที่เผยแพร่ในข้อตกลงนี้หรือผ่านสวิตช์ที่เกี่ยวข้องในบริการผลิตภัณฑ์ขอให้เราหยุด ในขณะเดียวกัน ตามกฎหมายและข้อบังคับหรือข้อกำหนดด้านกฎระเบียบของประเทศหรือภูมิภาคที่เกี่ยวข้องว่าด้วยการห้ามการตัดสินใจโดยอัตโนมัติ เราจะดำเนินการตามที่กำหนด

เราอาจใช้ข้อมูลบัญชีของคุณเพื่อวัตถุประสงค์การตลาด และอาจส่งข้อมูลเกี่ยวกับผลิตภัณฑ์ใหม่ การอัปเกรด และวัสดุการตลาดอื่นๆ จาก TeraBox ให้คุณเป็นครั้งคราว คุณสามารถเลือกที่จะไม่รับวัสดุการตลาดได้ทุกเมื่อ โดยการคลิกลิงก์ "ยกเลิกการสมัครสมาชิก" ในอีเมลที่คุณได้รับ

ให้ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลแก่บุคคลที่สาม

เราจะไม่ให้ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลแก่บุคคลที่สามโดยไม่ได้รับความยินยอมล่วงหน้าจากคุณ เว้นแต่จำเป็นสำหรับสถานการณ์ต่อไปนี้:

(a) เราต้องร่วมมือกับประเทศหรือองค์กรปกครองส่วนท้องถิ่นหรือตัวแทน เพื่อปฏิบัติหน้าที่หรือภาระผูกพันภายใต้กฎหมายและข้อบังคับที่เกี่ยวข้อง ซึ่งอาจยกเว้นได้ หากจำเป็นต้องได้รับความยินยอมจากคุณ

(b) มีอันตรายร้ายแรงต่อชีวิตหรือทรัพย์สินของบุคคล

(c) จำเป็นอย่างยิ่งที่จะต้องปรับปรุงสาธารณสุขหรือส่งเสริมการพัฒนาที่ดีของเยาวชน

สำหรับการแบ่งปัน ถ่ายโอน หรือเปิดเผยข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณภายใต้ข้อยกเว้นข้างต้น เราจะบันทึกพื้นฐานสำหรับการประมวลผลข้อมูลที่เกี่ยวข้อง ขอบเขตของข้อมูลการประมวลผล และข้อมูลของผู้รับ ฯลฯ รวมถึงสิ่งต่อไปนี้ และปฏิบัติตามหลักการขั้นต่ำและความจำเป็นในการปกป้องสิทธิ์ทางกฎหมายของคุณ

(1) ชื่อและรายละเอียดการติดต่อของผู้ควบคุมข้อมูลและเจ้าหน้าที่คุ้มครองข้อมูล

(2) วัตถุประสงค์ของการประมวลผลข้อมูล

(3) คำอธิบายประเภทของเจ้าของข้อมูลและประเภทของข้อมูลส่วนบุคคล

(4) ประเภทของผู้รับ (รวมถึงผู้รับที่อยู่ในประเทศที่สามหรือองค์กรระหว่างประเทศ) ที่ได้รับหรือจะเปิดเผยข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลนั้น

(5) บันทึกการถ่ายโอนข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลไปยังประเทศที่สามหรือองค์กรระหว่างประเทศและบันทึกการป้องกันที่เหมาะสม

(6) กำหนดเวลาโดยประมาณสำหรับการลบข้อมูลประเภทต่าง ๆ

(7) คำอธิบายทั่วไปของมาตรการรักษาความปลอดภัยทางเทคนิคและองค์กร

แบ่งปันกับผู้ใช้รายอื่น

เมื่อคุณใช้ฟังก์ชันการทำงานร่วมกันเป็นทีมหรือการแบ่งปันไฟล์ที่ TeraBox ให้บริการ การบริการของเราจะแสดงชื่อเล่น อุปกรณ์ ที่อยู่อีเมล และข้อมูลการใช้งานของคุณแก่ผู้ใช้รายอื่นที่ร่วมมือกับคุณหรือเลือกที่จะแบ่งปันกับคุณตามสิทธิ์ของคุณ สิ่งนี้จะช่วยให้คุณซิงค์กับทีมที่คุณต้องการเข้าร่วมและช่วยให้ผู้ใช้รายอื่นแบ่งปันไฟล์และแฟ้มกับคุณ

เราอาจแบ่งปันข้อมูลของคุณกับบุคคลที่สาม

เราอาจใช้บุคคลที่สามที่เชื่อถือได้บางราย (เช่น การสนับสนุนลูกค้าและผู้ให้บริการด้าน IT) เพื่อช่วยให้เราสามารถจัดหา เพิ่มประสิทธิภาพ ปกป้อง และส่งเสริมการบริการของเราได้ดียิ่งขึ้น บุคคลที่สามเหล่านี้อาจเข้าถึงข้อมูลของคุณ เพื่อทำงานในนามของเรา เรายังคงรับผิดชอบต่อการประมวลผลข้อมูลของคุณโดยบุคคลที่สามตามคำแนะนำของเรา

เราอาจแบ่งปันโครงสร้างพื้นฐาน ระบบ และเทคโนโลยีกับบริษัทในเครือของ Flextech เพื่อจัดหา ปรับปรุง ปกป้อง และส่งเสริมบริการเหล่านี้ บริษัทในเครือเหล่านี้จะใช้ข้อมูลของคุณร่วมกับเรา และจะใช้ข้อมูลที่คุณระบุไว้ในส่วน "เนื้อหาและวัตถุประสงค์ในการรวบรวมข้อมูล" เพื่อวัตถุประสงค์ที่อธิบายไว้ในนั้น เราจะรับผิดชอบในการอนุญาตให้บริษัทเหล่านี้ใช้ข้อมูลของคุณ

คุณสามารถเลือกที่จะเชื่อมต่อกับบัญชี TeraBox ผ่านการบริการของบุคคลที่สาม โดยการเชื่อมต่อกับการบริการดังกล่าว คุณอนุญาตให้บุคคลที่สามเหล่านี้และเราแลกเปลี่ยนข้อมูลที่กำหนดไว้ในส่วน "เนื้อหาและวัตถุประสงค์ในการรวบรวมข้อมูล" ของนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวนี้ เพื่อให้บุคคลที่สามแเหล่านี้ละเราสามารถจัดหา ปรับปรุง ปกป้อง และส่งเสริมให้กับบริการของพวกเขา ในกรณีเหล่านี้ การใช้ข้อมูลของคุณจะถูกควบคุมโดยนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวและข้อกำหนดในการให้บริการของบริการของบุคคลที่สามที่คุณเลือกที่จะเชื่อมต่อ

เราจะสร้างกลไกการส่งออกสำหรับการถ่ายโอนข้อมูลข้ามพรมแดนโดยอ้างอิงตามข้อกำหนดของ GDPR และอัปเดตกลไกข้ามพรมแดนในเวลาที่เหมาะสมตามข้อกำหนดของ GDPR การประมวลผลข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลใด ๆ จะเป็นไปตามบทบัญญัติของหลักการพื้นฐานของ GDPR โดยได้รับความยินยอมจากเจ้าของข้อมูลที่ถูกต้องหรือเป็นไปตามเหตุผลทางกฎหมายอื่น ๆ นอกจากนี้ จะมีการจัดตั้งกลไกเพิ่มเติมเพื่อปกป้องข้อมูลให้เป็นไปตามข้อกำหนดที่สำคัญของ GDPR สำหรับการประมวลผลข้อมูล

เราปกป้องและจัดเก็บข้อมูลของคุณอย่างไร

เรามีทีมงานที่ทุ่มเทในการรักษาข้อมูลของคุณให้ปลอดภัยและทดสอบช่องโหว่ต่าง ๆ นอกเหนือจากการรับรองความถูกต้องแบบสองปัจจัย การเข้ารหัสไฟล์ที่ไม่ได้ใช้งาน และการแจ้งเตือนเมื่อมีอุปกรณ์และแอปใหม่เชื่อมโยงบัญชีของคุณแล้ว เรายังคงทำงานอย่างเต็มที่เพื่อให้ข้อมูลของคุณปลอดภัย เราใช้เทคโนโลยีอัตโนมัติเพื่อตรวจจับพฤติกรรมและเนื้อหาที่ไม่เหมาะสมซึ่งอาจเป็นอันตรายต่อการบริการของเรา คุณหรือผู้ใช้รายอื่น ๆ

เมื่อคุณลงชื่อสมัครใช้บัญชี TeraBox เราจะเก็บรักษาข้อมูลที่คุณจัดเก็บไว้ในการบริการของเราตราบเท่าที่บัญชีของคุณยังมีอยู่ หรือเราต้องการให้การบริการแก่คุณ หากคุณต้องการลบบัญชีของคุณ โปรดส่งอีเมลมาที่ [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) เพื่อลบข้อมูลของคุณ เราจะดำเนินการดังกล่าวให้สำเร็จภายใน 30 วันหลังจากได้รับคำขอของคุณ อย่างไรก็ตาม หาก: (1) เราจะไม่ลบหรือลบข้อมูลบัญชีของคุณก่อนที่จะยืนยันตัวตนผู้ใช้ของคุณ (2) การลบเซิร์ฟเวอร์และที่เก็บข้อมูลสำรองของเราอาจล่าช้า (3) เราอาจเก็บข้อมูลนี้ไว้หากจำเป็นเพื่อปฏิบัติตามภาระผูกพันทางกฎหมาย ระงับข้อพิพาท หรือบังคับใช้สิทธิ์ของเราภายใต้สัญญา

เราจะเก็บรักษาข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณภายในระยะเวลาที่กำหนดในการให้บริการ อย่างไรก็ตาม กฎหมายและระเบียบข้อบังคับมีข้อกำหนดอื่นเกี่ยวกับระยะเวลาเก็บรักษา คุณตกลงที่จะคงระยะเวลานานขึ้น รับประกันความปลอดภัยและคุณภาพของบริการ บรรลุวัตถุประสงค์ของการระงับข้อพิพาท หรือบรรลุผลได้ยากในทางเทคนิค ฯลฯ หลังจากระยะเวลาการจัดเก็บดังกล่าวสิ้นสุดลง เราจะขยายระยะเวลาการจัดเก็บตามกฎหมาย ตามข้อตกลง หรือภายในขอบเขตที่เหมาะสม

เมื่อหมดระยะเวลาการเก็บรักษาแล้ว เราจะลบข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณหรือไม่เปิดเผยชื่อตามกฎหมาย

เราจะรวบรวม ใช้ จัดเก็บและส่งข้อมูลผู้ใช้ตามหลักการของ "การย่อ" และแจ้งให้คุณทราบถึงวัตถุประสงค์และขอบเขตของการใช้ข้อมูลที่เกี่ยวข้องผ่านข้อตกลงผู้ใช้และนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัว ตลอดจนกฎที่เกี่ยวข้อง หน้าต่างป๊อปอัป การแจ้งเตือน ฯลฯ

เราให้ความสำคัญกับความปลอดภัยของข้อมูลเป็นอย่างมาก เราได้จัดตั้งทีมงานเฉพาะที่รับผิดชอบในการพัฒนาและประยุกต์ใช้เทคโนโลยีและกระบวนการรักษาความปลอดภัยต่าง ๆ ฯลฯ เราจะดำเนินการตรวจสอบประวัติความปลอดภัยเกี่ยวกับผู้นำด้านการจัดการความปลอดภัยและบุคลากรในตำแหน่งความปลอดภัยที่สำคัญ เราได้สร้างระบบการจัดการความปลอดภัยของข้อมูลที่มั่นคงและกลไกการจัดการเหตุการณ์ความปลอดภัยภายใน ฯลฯ เราจะใช้มาตรการรักษาความปลอดภัยตามมาตรฐานอุตสาหกรรมที่เหมาะสมและวิธีการทางเทคนิคในการจัดเก็บและปกป้องข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณ เพื่อป้องกันไม่ให้ข้อมูลของคุณสูญหาย การเข้าถึงโดยไม่ได้รับอนุญาต การเปิดเผยต่อสาธารณะ การใช้งาน ความเสียหาย การสูญหาย หรือการรั่วไหล เราจะใช้มาตรการที่เหมาะสมและเป็นไปได้ทั้งหมดเพื่อปกป้องข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณ เราจะใช้เทคโนโลยีการเข้ารหัสเพื่อให้มั่นใจถึงการรักษาความลับของข้อมูล เราจะใช้กลไกการป้องกันที่เชื่อถือได้เพื่อป้องกันข้อมูลจากการโจมตีที่เป็นอันตราย

เราจะดำเนินการฝึกอบรมการรับรู้ด้านความปลอดภัยของข้อมูลและการฝึกอบรมและประเมินความสามารถในการรักษาความปลอดภัยสำหรับพนักงาน เพื่อเสริมสร้างความตระหนักของพนักงานเกี่ยวกับความสำคัญของการปกป้องข้อมูลส่วนบุคคล เราจะดำเนินการตรวจสอบตัวตนและควบคุมอำนาจสำหรับพนักงานที่จัดการข้อมูลส่วนบุคคล และจะลงนามในข้อตกลงการรักษาความลับกับพนักงานและคู่ค้าที่สามารถเข้าถึงข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณเพื่อชี้แจงความรับผิดชอบในงานและแนวทางปฏิบัติเพื่อให้แน่ใจว่าเฉพาะบุคลากรที่ได้รับอนุญาตเท่านั้นที่สามารถเข้าถึงข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลได้ หากมีการฝ่าฝืนข้อตกลงการรักษาความลับ ความร่วมมือกับบริษัทจะสิ้นสุดลงทันที และจะถูกสอบสวนตามความรับผิดชอบทางกฎหมายที่เกี่ยวข้อง นอกจากนี้ บุคลากรที่สามารถเข้าถึงข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลจะต้องรักษาความลับเมื่อออกจากตำแหน่ง

เราเตือนคุณว่าอินเทอร์เน็ตไม่ใช่สภาพแวดล้อมที่ปลอดภัยอย่างแน่นอน เมื่อคุณโต้ตอบกับผู้ใช้รายอื่นผ่านซอฟต์แวร์โซเชียลของบุคคลที่สาม อีเมล SMS ฯลฯ ที่ฝังอยู่ใน TeraBox เกี่ยวกับตำแหน่งทางภูมิศาสตร์ของคุณหรือตำแหน่งที่อยู่ของข้อมูลการติดตาม คุณจะไม่ได้ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าซอฟต์แวร์ของบุคคลที่สามจะส่งผลกระทบต่อข้อมูล ไม่ว่าการส่งข้อมูลจะถูกเข้ารหัสอย่างสมบูรณ์ โปรดใส่ใจเพื่อความปลอดภัยของข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณ

นอกจากนี้ เรายังขอให้คุณเข้าใจว่าเนื่องจากข้อจำกัดและการพัฒนาอย่างรวดเร็วของเทคโนโลยีในอุตสาหกรรมอินเทอร์เน็ต ตลอดจนวิธีการโจมตีที่เป็นอันตรายต่าง ๆ ที่อาจเกิดขึ้น แม้ว่าเราจะพยายามอย่างดีที่สุดเพื่อเสริมสร้างมาตรการรักษาความปลอดภัย ก็ไม่สามารถรับประกันความปลอดภัยของข้อมูลได้ 100% เสมอไป โปรดเข้าใจว่าระบบและเครือข่ายการสื่อสารที่คุณใช้เมื่อใช้ผลิตภัณฑ์และ/หรือบริการของเราอาจมีปัญหาด้านความปลอดภัยในลิงก์อื่นที่อยู่นอกเหนือการควบคุมของเรา

ตามระบบการจัดการความปลอดภัยของเรา การรั่วไหล ความเสียหาย หรือการสูญหายของข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลถูกระบุว่าเป็นเหตุการณ์ด้านความปลอดภัยที่ร้ายแรงที่สุด เมื่อเกิดขึ้น แผนฉุกเฉินระดับสูงสุดของบริษัทจะเปิดใช้งาน และทีมรับมือเหตุฉุกเฉินร่วมจะถูกจัดตั้งขึ้นโดยหลายแผนกเพื่อจัดการ

เราจะจัดทำแผนฉุกเฉินสำหรับเหตุการณ์ด้านความปลอดภัยเครือข่ายเพื่อจัดการกับความเสี่ยงด้านความปลอดภัยต่าง ๆ เช่น ช่องโหว่ของระบบ ไวรัสคอมพิวเตอร์ การโจมตีเครือข่าย และการบุกรุกเครือข่ายในเวลาที่เหมาะสม ในกรณีที่เกิดเหตุการณ์ที่เป็นอันตรายต่อความปลอดภัยของเครือข่าย เราจะเปิดใช้งานแผนฉุกเฉินทันที ใช้มาตรการแก้ไขที่เกี่ยวข้อง และรายงานไปยังหน่วยงานที่เกี่ยวข้องตามระเบียบข้อบังคับ

การรั่วไหล ความเสียหาย และการสูญหายของข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลเป็นเหตุการณ์ด้านความปลอดภัยที่สำคัญในระดับบริษัท เราจะรับผิดชอบในการจัดทีมของคณะทำงานเป็นประจำเพื่อดำเนินการฝึกซ้อมด้านความปลอดภัยเพื่อป้องกันไม่ให้เหตุการณ์ด้านความปลอดภัยดังกล่าวเกิดขึ้น ในกรณีที่เกิดเหตุการณ์ไม่คาดฝัน เราจะเปิดใช้งานแผนฉุกเฉินตามลำดับความสำคัญสูงสุด จัดตั้งทีมรับมือเหตุฉุกเฉิน ติดตามสาเหตุ และลดการสูญเสียในเวลาที่สั้นที่สุด

หลังจากโชคร้ายเกิดเหตุการณ์ด้านความปลอดภัยข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลขึ้น เราจะปฏิบัติตามข้อกำหนดของกฎหมายและข้อบังคับ และแจ้งให้คุณทราบโดยทันทีเกี่ยวกับสถานการณ์พื้นฐานและผลกระทบที่อาจเกิดขึ้นจากเหตุการณ์ด้านความปลอดภัย มาตรการจัดการที่เราดำเนินการหรือจะดำเนินการ คำแนะนำเกี่ยวกับความเสี่ยงที่สามารถป้องกันและลดความเสี่ยงได้ด้วยตนเอง มาตรการแก้ไขสำหรับคุณ ฯลฯ เราจะแจ้งให้คุณทราบทันทีเกี่ยวกับสถานการณ์ที่เกี่ยวข้องกับงานผ่านวิธีการติดต่อที่คุณจองไว้ เช่น การแจ้งเตือนในสถานที่ การแจ้งเตือนทางข้อความ โทรศัพท์และอีเมล ฯลฯ เมื่อเป็นเรื่องยากที่จะแจ้งให้ทราบ เราจะใช้วิธีที่เหมาะสมและมีประสิทธิภาพในการประกาศ ในเวลาเดียวกัน เราจะรายงานการจัดการเหตุการณ์ด้านความปลอดภัยของข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลอย่างแข็งขันตามข้อกำหนดของหน่วยงานกำกับดูแล โปรดเข้าใจว่า ตามกฎหมายและระเบียบข้อบังคับ หากมาตรการที่เราดำเนินการสามารถป้องกันการรั่วไหลของข้อมูล การดัดแปลง หรือการสูญเสียที่ก่อให้เกิดอันตรายได้อย่างมีประสิทธิภาพ เราอาจเลือกที่จะไม่แจ้งให้คุณทราบเกี่ยวกับเหตุการณ์ด้านความปลอดภัยของข้อมูลส่วนบุคคล เว้นแต่แผนกกำกับดูแลจะกำหนดให้มีการแจ้งเตือนถึงคุณ

เราจะอ้างถึงข้อกำหนดของ GDPR เลือกมาตรการป้องกันความปลอดภัยทางเทคนิคที่เหมาะสมตามลักษณะ ขอบเขต ภูมิหลังและวัตถุประสงค์ของการประมวลผลข้อมูล และความเสี่ยงต่อบุคคล และดำเนินการทดสอบและประเมินผลอย่างสม่ำเสมอเพื่อรักษาประสิทธิภาพของมาตรการที่ดำเนินการ

เมื่อเกิดการรั่วไหลของข้อมูล เราจะแจ้งให้ผู้เกี่ยวข้องที่ได้รับผลกระทบจากข้อมูลที่รั่วไหลโดยเร็วที่สุด และภายใน 72 ชั่วโมง เราจะรายงานไปยังหน่วยงานที่มีอำนาจที่เกี่ยวข้อง เมื่อไม่สามารถรายงานได้ภายใน 72 ชั่วโมง จะมีการอธิบายเหตุผลที่รายงานล่าช้า

เราใช้มาตรการทางเทคนิคและองค์กรที่เหมาะสมเพื่อให้บรรลุวัตถุประสงค์ในการปกป้องข้อมูล เช่น การลดขนาดข้อมูลและการรวมการป้องกันที่จำเป็นในการประมวลผลข้อมูล เพื่อปกป้องสิทธิ์ของเจ้าของข้อมูล และโดยค่าเริ่มต้น เพื่อให้แน่ใจว่าข้อมูลที่ประมวลผลเพื่อวัตถุประสงค์เฉพาะนั้นเป็นสิ่งที่จำเป็น

เราจัดเก็บและประมวลผลข้อมูลของคุณที่ไหน

ขณะให้บริการ เราอาจจัดเก็บ ประมวลผล และอัปโหลดข้อมูลของคุณในญี่ปุ่นโดยได้รับความยินยอมจากคุณในการให้ข้อมูลของคุณ ข้อมูลของคุณอาจถูกจัดเก็บไว้ในอุปกรณ์ที่ใช้ในการเข้าถึงการบริการ

คุณควบคุมและเข้าถึงข้อมูลของคุณได้อย่างไร

ตามกฎหมาย ระเบียบข้อบังคับ มาตรฐาน และหลักปฏิบัติทั่วไปของประเทศและภูมิภาคที่เกี่ยวข้อง เรารับประกันว่าคุณสามารถใช้สิทธิ์ต่อไปนี้เกี่ยวกับข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณ หากคุณมีคำถามหรือข้อเรียกร้องใด ๆ เกี่ยวกับการใช้สิทธิ์คุณยังสามารถติดต่อเราผ่านทาง [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) คุณสามารถดู เปลี่ยนแปลง ดาวน์โหลด ลบหรือแบ่งปันข้อมูลของคุณจากบัญชี TeraBox

1\. สิทธิ์ในการเข้าถึง

เมื่อคุณต้องการทราบขอบเขตของการได้รับ การจัดเก็บ การแบ่งปัน ฯลฯ ของข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณหรือวัตถุประสงค์ในการประมวลผลข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณของ TeraBox คุณสามารถติดต่อเราเพื่อรับเนื้อหาที่เกี่ยวข้องได้

2\. สิทธิ์ในการแก้ไขและเพิ่มเติม

เมื่อคุณพบว่าข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เราประมวลผลเกี่ยวกับคุณไม่ถูกต้อง คุณมีสิทธิ์แก้ไขข้อมูลที่ไม่ถูกต้องหรือไม่สมบูรณ์ หลังจากยืนยันตัวตนของคุณแล้ว คุณสามารถส่งคำขอแก้ไขหรือเสริมให้เราผ่านข้อเสนอแนะและการรายงานข้อผิดพลาดหรือข้อมูลการติดต่อดังกล่าวข้างต้น หลังจากที่เราได้รับคำขอของคุณแล้ว เราจะให้ข้อเสนอแนะแก่คุณโดยเร็วที่สุด

3\. สิทธิ์ในการลบ

ในกรณีต่อไปนี้ คุณสามารถขอให้เราลบข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณได้:

หากเราประมวลผลข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณโดยละเมิดกฎหมายและข้อบังคับหรือข้อตกลงของเรากับคุณ

หากบรรลุวัตถุประสงค์ในการประมวลผลของเรา ไม่สามารถทำได้หรือไม่มีความจำเป็นอีกต่อไปในการบรรลุวัตถุประสงค์ในการประมวลผล

หากเราหยุดให้ผลิตภัณฑ์หรือบริการ หรือระยะเวลาการเก็บรักษาหมดอายุ

หากคุณเพิกถอนความยินยอมของคุณ

สถานการณ์อื่น ๆ ที่กำหนดโดยกฎหมายและข้อบังคับการบริหาร

หลังจากที่คุณลบข้อมูลออกจากบริการของเรา เราอาจไม่ลบข้อมูลที่เกี่ยวข้องในระบบสำรองทันที แต่จะลบข้อมูลเมื่อมีการอัปเดตข้อมูลสำรอง โปรดทราบและเข้าใจว่า หากระยะเวลาการเก็บรักษาที่กำหนดโดยกฎหมายและข้อบังคับด้านการบริหารหรือที่อธิบายไว้ในนโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวนี้ยังไม่หมดอายุ หรือหากเป็นการยากที่จะลบข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลในทางเทคนิค เราจะหยุดการประมวลผลนอกเหนือจากการจัดเก็บและใช้มาตรการรักษาความปลอดภัยที่จำเป็น

4\. การเพิกถอนความยินยอม

ฟังก์ชันธุรกิจแต่ละอย่างต้องการข้อมูลส่วนตัวพื้นฐานบางอย่างเพื่อให้สมบูรณ์ สำหรับการรวบรวมและการใช้ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่รวบรวมเพิ่มเติม คุณสามารถให้หรือถอนการอนุญาตและความยินยอมของคุณได้ตลอดเวลา

คุณสามารถปิดการอนุญาตของระบบได้โดยตรง เช่น รายชื่อผู้ติดต่อ อัลบั้ม และกล้อง ฯลฯ ในระบบอุปกรณ์ เปลี่ยนขอบเขตของการยินยอม หรือเพิกถอนการอนุญาตของคุณ

หลังจากที่คุณเพิกถอนความยินยอม เราจะไม่สามารถให้บริการที่เกี่ยวข้องกับการเพิกถอนความยินยอมของคุณได้อีกต่อไป และเราจะไม่ใช้ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เกี่ยวข้องของคุณอีกต่อไป อย่างไรก็ตาม การตัดสินใจเพิกถอนความยินยอมของคุณจะไม่ส่งผลกระทบต่อการประมวลผลข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลตามความยินยอมของคุณก่อนหน้านี้

5\. สิทธิ์ในการลบ

คุณสามารถลบบัญชีที่ลงทะเบียนไว้ก่อนหน้านี้ได้ คุณยังสามารถลบบัญชีของคุณบน TeraBox ผ่านเส้นทางต่อไปนี้:

\[รูปประจำตัวบัญชี\] - \[เมนู\] - \[การตั้งค่า\] - \[ศูนย์ความปลอดภัย\] - \[การลบบัญชี\]

เมื่อคุณลบบัญชีของคุณ คุณจะไม่สามารถใช้บริการของผลิตภัณฑ์ TeraBox ได้ ดังนั้นโปรดดำเนินการด้วยความระมัดระวัง เพื่อปกป้องสิทธิ์โดยชอบด้วยกฎหมายและผลประโยชน์ของคุณหรือผู้อื่น เราจะตัดสินว่าจะสนับสนุนคำขอลบของคุณตามการใช้งานของคุณหรือไม่ ตัวอย่างเช่น หากคุณยังไม่ได้ใช้สิทธิประโยชน์ของ Premium หรือยังมีข้อมูลอยู่ในบัญชีของคุณ เราจะไม่สนับสนุนคำขอของคุณในทันที เว้นแต่กฎหมายและข้อบังคับกำหนดไว้เป็นอย่างอื่น เราจะหยุดให้ผลิตภัณฑ์และบริการแก่คุณหลังจากลบบัญชีของคุณ และลบข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณตามความต้องการของคุณ

6\. สิทธิ์ในการคัดลอกและพกพา

คุณมีสิทธิ์ที่จะคัดลอกข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณที่รวบรวมโดยเรา ภายใต้เงื่อนไขที่กำหนดโดยกฎหมายและข้อบังคับ และปฏิบัติตามคำแนะนำและเงื่อนไขที่กำหนดโดยหน่วยงานที่มีอำนาจที่เกี่ยวข้อง และหากเป็นไปได้ในทางเทคนิค คุณสามารถขอให้เราถ่ายโอนข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณไปยังบุคคลอื่น ๆ ที่คุณกำหนดได้

เมื่อคุณใช้สิทธิ์ที่เกี่ยวข้องของหัวข้อข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่กล่าวถึงข้างต้น เราจะซิงค์กับบุคคลที่สามที่เกี่ยวข้องโดยเร็วที่สุดเพื่อให้แน่ใจว่าสิทธิ์ที่กล่าวถึงข้างต้นของคุณเป็นไปตามกฎหมายและข้อบังคับ ข้อกำหนดด้านกฎระเบียบ และความเป็นไปได้ทางเทคนิค

เมื่อคำขอของคุณเห็นได้ชัดว่าไม่สมเหตุสมผลหรือเกินขีดจำกัดที่จำเป็น โดยเฉพาะอย่างยิ่งเมื่อคำขอซ้ำซ้อน เราอาจ:

(a) คิดค่าธรรมเนียมที่สมเหตุสมผลร่วมกับค่าใช้จ่ายในการจัดการในการให้ข้อมูล การสื่อสาร หรือการดำเนินการที่เกี่ยวข้อง หรือ

(b) ปฏิเสธ เพื่อดำเนินการตามคำขอ

คุณสามารถควบคุมข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่คุณเก็บรักษาไว้และวิธีการรวบรวม ใช้ และแบ่งปันตาม พระราชบัญญัติคุ้มครองข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของญี่ปุ่น ("ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เก็บรักษาไว้") ตัวอย่างเช่น คุณสามารถ:

a. ขอให้เปิดเผยข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เก็บรักษาไว้ซึ่งสามารถระบุตัวคุณได้

b. เมื่อเนื้อหาของข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เก็บรักษาไว้ซึ่งสามารถระบุตัวบุคคลนั้นไม่ใช่ข้อเท็จจริง จำเป็นต้องแก้ไข เพิ่มหรือลบเนื้อหาของข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เก็บไว้

c. หากเราได้รับข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เก็บไว้ของคุณอย่างผิดกฎหมาย หรือหากเรากำลังใช้ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เก็บไว้ของคุณ โปรดลบหรือหยุดใช้ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เก็บรักษาไว้ของคุณทันที

d. หากเราให้ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เก็บรักษาไว้ของคุณแก่บุคคลที่สามอย่างผิดกฎหมาย โปรดหยุดให้ข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลที่เก็บรักษาไว้ของคุณทันที

การเปลี่ยน

ในกรณีของการปรับโครงสร้างองค์กร การควบรวมกิจการ หรือการเข้าซื้อกิจการของ Flextech หรือการขายทรัพย์สินของเรา ข้อมูลของคุณอาจถูกโอนไปยังนิติบุคคลที่รอดชีวิต ผู้ซื้อหรือผู้สืบทอดของธุรกรรมนี้ เราจะแจ้งให้คุณทราบถึงธุรกรรมดังกล่าว (เช่น โดยการส่งข้อความไปยังที่อยู่อีเมลที่เชื่อมโยงกับบัญชีของคุณ) และร่างตัวเลือกของคุณในเหตุการณ์นั้น

นโยบายความเป็นส่วนตัวนี้อาจมีการแก้ไขเป็นครั้งคราว เราจะโพสต์เวอร์ชันล่าสุดบนเว็บไซต์ของ TeraBox เราจะแจ้งให้คุณทราบหากการแก้ไขดังกล่าวส่งผลกระทบอย่างมีนัยสำคัญต่อสิทธิ์ของคุณ

ติดต่อเรา:

หากคุณมีคำถามหรือข้อกังวลใด ๆ เกี่ยวกับ TeraBox การบริการของเราและความเป็นส่วนตัว โปรดติดต่อเราที่ [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com)

TeraBox 프라이버시 정책

TeraBox 프라이버시 정책

정보 수집 내용 및 목적

제3자에 대한 개인정보 제공

기타 유저와 공유

저희는 제3자에게 유저님의 개인 정보를 공유할 수 있습니다

개인정보 저장 및 보호 방안

개인정보 저장 및 처리 장소

유저 측의 개인정보 통제 및 접근 방법

{{ $t('termsOfServicePrivacyPolicy.age.title') }}

변경

연락처：

TeraBox 프라이버시 정책

정책 배포 시간：2023년 4월 18일

효력 발생 시간：2023년 4월 18일

TeraBox를 이용해 주셔서 감사합니다! TeraBox는 Flextech Inc. (이하 "Flextech" 혹은 "저희")가 유저님께 제공해 드리는 서비스입니다. 저희는 유저님의 프라이버시를 보호하기 위해 최선을 다할 것입니다. 해당 프라이버시 정책은 유저님께서 저희의 웹사이트, 소프트웨어, 그리고 서비스 (이하 "서비스") 등을 사용하실 때 저희가 어떤 방식으로 유저님의 정보를 수집, 저장, 처리, 공유, 그리고 사용하는지에 대한 규정을 다루고 있습니다.

저희는 반드시 필요한 유저님의 개인 정보만 합법적이고 정당한 방식으로 수집 및 사용한다는 원칙을 준수합니다. 구체적으로 저희는 유저님께 상응하는 업무 기능을 제공해 드리기 위해 유저님의 개인 정보를 수집 및 처리하고 있습니다. 해당 업무 기능을 사용하시면서 유저님이 제공해 주신 개인 정보가 타인의 것일 경우에는 반드시 해당 인원으로부터의 인가를 받은 상태이도록 확인해 주십시오. 저희는 개인정보의 출처를 수시로 조사할 수 있는 합법적인 권리를 지니고 있습니다.

저희는 법률과 법규 상의 요구 사항들을 엄격하게 준수할 것이며, 특정 상황에서 유저님의 단독적인 동의를 구할 수 있습니다. 저희는 해당 프라이버시 정책을 제외하고도 제품 페이지 상의 고지, 팝업 창 알림, 푸시 메시지 발송 등의 방식을 통해 저희의 개인정보 처리 규칙을 설명할 수 있습니다. 구체적인 업무 기능에 상응하는 개인 정보의 처리 현황은 구체적인 규칙들을 기준으로 하며, 해당 구체적인 규칙들은 본 프라이버시 정책과 동등한 효력을 지니고 있습니다.

주의: 아래의 상황에서 유저님의 개인 정보를 수집, 사용, 공유, 이전, 공개하는 것에 대해서는 유저님의 사전 동의를 구할 필요가 없습니다.

국가 안보와 국방 안전에 직접적으로 관련되어 있는 사안일 경우;

계약 당사자로서 계약 내용을 정립 및 이행하는데 반드시 필요할 경우;

법정 직책과 법정 의무를 이행하기 위해 반드시 필요할 경우;

돌발적인 공공보건 사태에 대응하거나 긴급 상황 하에서 인원들의 생명과 재산의 안전을 보호하기 위해 반드시 필요한 경우;

범죄 수사, 기소, 재판, 판결 집행 등과 직접적으로 연결되어 있는 경우;

유저님과 기타 인원의 생명과 자산을 보호하고 중대한 합법적인 권리를 보호하기 위해 반드시 필요하나 본인의 동의를 구하기가 어려운 상황일 경우;

법률 상의 규정에 따라 합리적인 범위 내에서 유저님께서 이미 자발적으로 사회에 공개했거나 이미 합법적으로 공개된 기타 개인 정보(합법적인 뉴스 보도, 정부 공개 출처 등)들을 수집하는 것일 경우;

공공의 이익을 위해 실시하는 뉴스 보도, 여론 감독 등 행위를 위해 합리적인 범위 내에서 개인 정보를 처리하는 경우;

학술 연구기관이 공공의 이익을 위해 통계 및 학술 연구를 진행하는데 필요할 경우;

학술 연구 결과 및 이에 대한 설명을 제공할 시 해당 결과에 포함되어 있는 개인 정보에 대한 태그 처리를 진행하는 경우;

법률 상 규정된 기타 상황의 경우.

정보 수집 내용 및 목적

이하의 목록에는 유저님께서 해당 서비스를 이용하시면서 저희에게 제공해 주신 정보의 유형들을 나열하고 있으며, 저희가 이러한 정보들을 사용하는 목적을 함께 설명하고 있습니다. 저희는 저희의 서비스를 제공, 최적화, 보호, 그리고 홍보하기 위해 이하의 정보들을 수집 및 사용할 것입니다.

| 정보 유형 | 수집 목적 |
| --- | --- |
| 계정 정보. 저희는 유저님이 일부 작업(계정 등록 등)을 진행하실 때 저희에게 제공해 주시는 이메일 주소, 전화번호 등 정보(SNS 계정을 이용하여 로그인을 진행하시는 경우에는 유저님의 닉네임과 SNS 프로필 사진 등 데이터들을 수집하게 됩니다)들을 수집하게 되며, 이러한 정보들을 유저님의 계정과 동기화하게 됩니다. | 저희는 해당 정보를 이용하여 유저님이 계정의 소유자임을 확인할 수 있으며, 이를 통해 유저님의 계정을 안전하게 보호할 수 있습니다. 저희는 유저님이 계정에 로그인하실 때 아래와 같은 정보들을 수집할 수 있습니다. |
| 유저 자료. 유저님이 TeraBox에 저장하시는 문서, 파일, 이미지, 영상, 음성 등의 ("유저 자료") | 저희는 서비스의 원활한 제공을 보장하고 유저님이 타인과의 협력을 진행하도록 지원함과 동시에 다수의 기기를 통해 서비스를 제공받을 수 있도록 유저 자료들과 이와 관련된 정보들을 저장, 처리, 전송할 수 있습니다. 해당 관련 정보라 함은 유저님이 저장하신 파일의 정보, 파일의 용량, 업로드 일자 및 시간, 그리고 기타 사용 기록 등을 의미합니다. |
| 사용 상황 정보. 서비스 사용에 대한 정보라 함은 유저님께서 계정 내에서 진행하신 편집, 조회, 그리고 파일/폴더 생성 및 이동 작업 등에 대한 정보들을 의미합니다. | 저희는 해당 정보들을 서비스 제공, 개선, 홍보, 그리고 TeraBox 유저들에 대한 보호를 위해 사용할 수 있습니다. |
| 기기 정보. 서비스 이용에 사용되는 기기 정보는 IP 주소, 브라우저, 기기 정보 등의 기기 관련 정보, 그리고 TeraBox를 이용하기 전 방문한 웹페이지, 기기와 연관되어 있는 식별명, 그리고 기기 설정에 따른 위치 정보 등의 정보들을 지칭합니다. | 저희는 해당 정보들을 저희의 서비스를 개선 및 보호하기 위해 사용할 수 있습니다. |
| Cookies. 유저님께서 TeraBox를 이용하실 때 웹페이지에서 유저님의 브라우저에 발송하게 되는 작은 파일을 지칭합니다. 유저님은 브라우저에서 Cookies를 허용하지 않도록 설정하실 수 있지만, 이는 서비스의 기능에 영향을 미칠 수 있습니다. | 저희는 Cookies와 유사한 기술적 수단들을 통해 저희의 서비스를 제공, 개선, 보호 및 홍보할 수 있습니다. Cookies는 저희가 유저님의 ID를 기억하고 유저님의 서비스 이용 패턴을 파악하여 이를 기반으로 서비스를 개선할 수 있도록 합니다. 저희와 협력하는 제3자 서비스 제공 업체 또한 Cookies와 유사 기술적 수단을 활용할 수 있습니다. |
| 연락처. 유저님은 TeraBox의 공유 기능을 통해 휴대폰에 저장되어 있는 연락처, 전화번호, 이메일 주소 (Facebook, Twitter 등)을 활용하여 유저님의 데이터와 정보를 공유하실 수 있습니다. 휴대폰 상의 연락처는 민감 개인 정보에 속합니다. 해당 정보에 대한 제공을 거부하실 경우에는 앞서 언급된 기능을 사용하실 수 없게 되나, TeraBox가 제공하는 기타 기능이나 관련 서비스의 정상적인 사용에 영향을 미치지는 않습니다. | 유저님께서는 TeraBox가 유저님의 연락처 정보에 접근할 수 있도록 허용하여 공유 및 협력 기능을 통해 타인이 유저님의 데이터를 처리할 수 있도록 하는 기능이나, 메시지 발송 및 이메일 주소를 통해 타인이 TeraBox 서비스를 이용하도록 초청하는 작업들을 더욱 편리하게 수행하실 수 있습니다. 해당 작업을 위해서는 유저님으로부터 연락처 접근 권한을 부여받아야 합니다. 저희는 해당 정보들을 저희의 서버 상에 저장하여 유저님이 사용하실 수 있도록 지원해 드립니다. 공유 작업을 진행하기 전에는 메시지 수신자의 신뢰성을 충분히 고려해 주십시오. 또한, 저희는 유저님께서 SNS나 기타 제3자 서비스 제공 업체가 배포한 프라이버시 방침을 검토하여 그들이 유저님의 개인 정보를 어떻게 처리하는지를 파악하신 후 신중한 결정을 내리시는 것을 권장해 드립니다. |
| 클립 보드. 다른 사용자의 초대 코드를 사용하여 Terabox 계정을 등록하거나 다른 사용자가 공유한 파일 링크에 액세스하거나 비밀번호로 친구를 추가하거나 교환 코드를 통해 회원 서비스를 받을 때, 우리는 클립 보드 정보를 읽을 것입니다. | 우리는 클립보드 정보에 액세스하여 링크에 해당하는 파일을 열도록 도와드리고, 비밀번호 및 초대 코드에 해당하는 사용자를 식별하며, 회원 서비스를 교환해 드립니다. 절대로 다른 목적으로 클립보드를 읽지 않습니다. |

유저님께서는 휴대폰 번호로 Terabox 계정을 개설할 수 있으며, 유저님의 계정 정보를 추가적으로 보완하실 수 있습니다.

법률 규정 상의 강제성 의무에 대한 준수 절차의 일환으로 저희의 제품이나 서비스를 제공하기 위해서는 유저님께서 계정에 대한 보안 등급 관련 요구 사항을 준수해 주셔야 합니다. 유저님이 TeraBox의 일부 서비스를 이용하실 때, 혹은 추가적인 요청 사항을 받으시게 되면 유저님께서는 유저님의 법적 성명과 신분증 번호, 그리고 얼굴 보안 정보 등을 제공하여 계정 인증을 마쳐주셔야 합니다. 저희는 유저님이 제공해 주신 정보들의 정확도와 완전성을 확인하거나 유저님의 사용하시는 계정의 안전을 보장해 드리기 위해 유저님께서 TeraBox에 제공해 주신 실명 정보를 법률 상 허용된 기관 혹은 정부 기관의 인가를 받은 기관에 보관하고 이에 대한 검증을 요청할 수 있습니다.

앞서 언급된 정보들을 수집하는 것은 저희의 서비스를 상업적 목적에 따라 더욱 신뢰할 수 있고 안전하게 제공하기 위해서입니다. 저희와 저희의 협력 파트너들은 유저님의 정보들을 기타 목적을 위해 사용해야 할 때 반드시 유저님의 사전 동의를 구하게 됩니다.

유저님께서 저희가 본사의 자체적인 기술, 혹은 위탁 업체 측의 기술을 통해 유저님께서 서비스 이용 중 자의 및 타의적으로 제공해 주신 개인 정보들을 수집 및 종합하여 분석을 진행하고 데이터 프로필을 생성하거나 추가적인 가공 절차를 거쳐 유저님의 행동 패턴, 취향, 혹은 신용 상태 등을 나타내는 다양하고 세분화된 특수 태그 정보(이하 “태그 정보”)들을 생성하는데 동의하실 경우, 저희는 해당 태그 정보들을 특정 상황과 목적에 따라 활용하여 자동화된 전략 수립을 진행함으로써 유저님께 개인화된 정보나 상업 마케팅 정보들을 발송해 드릴 것입니다.

유저님은 저희가 실시하는 전략 수립 자동화 서비스를 거부하실 권리가 있으며, 해당 약관에 배포된 연락처를 통해 저희에게 연락해 주시거나 제품 서비스 상의 관련 스위치를 통해 저희에게 중지를 요청하실 수 있습니다. 또한, 특정 국가 및 지역에 자동화 전략 수립을 금지하는 법규와 감독 관리 규정이 존재할 경우, 저희는 해당 요구 사항을 준수할 것입니다.

당사는 고객님의 계정 데이터를 마케팅 목적으로 사용하며, TeraBox의 새로운 제품, 업그레이드 및 기타 마케팅 자료에 관한 정보를 때때로 보내드릴 수 있습니다. 고객님은 언제든지 당사로부터 받은 이메일에서 "구독 취소" 링크를 클릭하여 마케팅 자료 수신을 거부할 수 있습니다.

제3자에 대한 개인정보 제공

저희는 이하의 필수적인 상황을 제외하고는 유저님의 사전 동의를 거치지 않고 제3자에게 유저님의 개인 정보를 제공할 수 없습니다.

(a) 저희는 국가 및 지방 정부 혹은 기타 대리인들과 협력하여 관련 법률과 법규에 따라 직책과 의무를 이행할 의무가 있습니다. 만약 반드시 유저님의 동의를 구해야 할 경우에는 이러한 이행을 배제할 수 있습니다.

(b) 특정 인물의 생명이나 재산에 중대한 위해를 가하는 경우.

(c) 공공 보건 개선 및 청소년들의 건전한 성장을 위해 특별한 필요가 있는 경우.

유저님의 개인 정보가 앞서 언급된 상황 하에서 공유, 제공, 혹은 공개될 경우, 저희는 관련 정보의 처리 근거, 처리 정보의 범위, 수신자 관련 정보 등을 기록해 둘 것입니다. 구체적인 기록 내역은 이하와 같으며, 데이터 제공을 최소화하고 반드시 필요한 데이터만 제공한다는 원칙에 따라 유저님의 합법적인 권리를 보호할 것입니다.

(1) 데이터 관리자, 데이터 보호 담당자의 성명과 상세한 연락처 정보;

(2) 데이터 처리 목적;

(3) 데이터 주체의 유형과 개인 데이터 유형에 대한 묘사;

(4) 개인 정보가 이미 제공되거나 제공될 예정인 수취자 (제3국이나 국제기구의 수취자를 포함);

(5) 개인 정보를 제3국이나 국제기구로 이전하는 기록 및 이에 대한 적절한 보호 조치에 대한 기록;

(6) 다양한 유형의 데이터에 대한 예상 삭제 기한;

(7) 기술적/조직적인 안전 조치에 대한 일반적인 묘사.

기타 유저와 공유

유저님께서 TeraBox가 제공하는 팀 협력 및 파일 공유 기능을 이용하시게 되면, 저희 서비스는 유저님의 닉네임, 기기, 이메일 주소 등 사용 정보들을 유저님이 함께 협력 중인 기타 유저들에게 표시하고 유저님의 권한 설정에 따라 유저님에게 공유해 드립니다. 이는 유저님과 유저님이 가입하시고자 하는 팀과 동기화를 진행하고 기타 유저들이 유저님과 파일과 폴더들을 공유하는 데 도움을 줍니다.

저희는 제3자에게 유저님의 개인 정보를 공유할 수 있습니다

저희는 저희의 서비스를 더 나은 방식으로 제공, 최적화, 보호, 홍보할 수 있도록 일부 신뢰성 있는 제3자 업체(고객 지원 및 IT 서비스 제공 업체 등)가 제공하는 서비스를 이용할 수 있습니다. 해당 제3자 업체들은 유저님의 정보에 접근할 수 있으며, 저희를 대리하여 업무를 진행할 수 있습니다. 단, 저희는 여전히 제3자 업체가 저희의 지시에 따라 유저님의 개인 정보를 처리하는 전체 과정에 대한 책임을 지게 됩니다.

또한, 저희는 저희의 서비스를 제공, 개선, 보호, 그리고 홍보하기 위해 Flextech 측의 계열사들과 기초 인프라, 시스템, 그리고 기술들을 공유할 수 있습니다. 해당 계열사들은 저희와 함께 유저님의 개인 정보들을 사용하게 되며, “수집 정보의 내용 및 목적” 상의 리스트에 명시되어 있는 유저님의 개인 정보들을 해당 정책 상에 기술되어 있는 목적에 따라 사용하게 됩니다. 저희는 해당 업체들이 유저님의 개인 정보를 사용하는 과정에 책임을 지게 됩니다.

유저님께서는 제3자 서비스를 통해 TeraBox 계정에 연결하는 방식을 선택하실 수 있습니다. 유저님께서는 이러한 서비스 연결을 진행함으로써 해당 제3자 서비스 제공자들과 저희가 해당 프라이버시 정책 내의 “수집 정보의 내용 및 목적” 파트에 나열되어 있는 정보들을 교환하는 것에 동의하시게 됩니다. 이는 해당 제3자 업체들과 저희가 그들이 제공하는 서비스를 제공, 개선, 보호, 및 촉진할 수 있도록 하기 위함입니다. 이러한 상황 하에서 유저님의 개인 정보에 대한 사용은 유저님이 서비스 연결을 위해 선택하신 제3자 서비스 제공자가 제정한 프라이버시 정책과 서비스 약관의 관할 하에 놓이게 됩니다.

저희는 GDPR 측의 요구 사항을 참고하여 국경 간 데이터 전송의 반출 체계를 수립할 것이며, GDPR의 요구 사항에 따라 필요할 시 적정한 시점에 해당 반출 체계를 갱신할 것입니다. 개인 데이터에 대해 진행하는 모든 처리 절차는 GDPR의 기본적인 원칙과 규정을 만족하는 선에서 이루어지며, 유효한 데이터 주체의 동의를 얻거나 기타 합법적인 사유를 만족하는 선에서 진행됩니다. 이를 제외하고, 저희는 데이터 보호를 위해 별도의 체계를 마련하여 데이터 처리에 대한 GDPR 측의 실질적인 요구 사항들을 만족시킬 것입니다.

개인정보 저장 및 보호 방안

저희는 유저님의 정보를 보호하고 보안 테스팅을 진행하는 데 주력하는 1개의 업무팀을 운영하고 있습니다. 저희는 2중 신분 인증, 파일 암호화 금지, 신규 기기 및 앱을 통한 계정 접근 시 알림 발송 등 조치들 외에도 지속적인 노력을 통해 유저님의 개인 정보를 안전하게 보호할 것입니다. 저희는 저희의 서비스를 손상 시킬 수 있는 행위 및 컨텐츠, 그리고 유저님이나 기타 유저들의 잠재적인 남용 행위를 포착하기 위해 자동화 기술을 도입했습니다.

유저님이 TeraBox 계정을 신규 개설하시게 되면 저희는 유저님의 계정이 존재하는 동안, 혹은 저희가 유저님에게 서비스를 제공해 드려야 하는 이상 유저님이 저희 서버 상에 저장하신 정보들을 지속적으로 보관할 것입니다. 계정 삭제를 원하실 경우에는 [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com)로 이메일을 발송하여 유저님의 정보를 삭제해 주십시오. 저희는 유저님의 요청 사항을 수신한 후 30일 내에 해당 업무를 완료할 것입니다. 단, (1) 유저님의 신분이 검증되기 전까지는 유저님의 계정 정보를 삭제하지 않을 것입니다. (2) 저희의 서버나 백업 스토리지 상에서 데이터를 삭제하는 데는 시간이 추가적으로 소요될 수 있습니다. (3) 저희는 법적 의무를 준수하고 분쟁을 해결하거나 약관 상의 권리를 이행하기 위해 필요할 시 해당 정보들을 그대로 보관할 수 있습니다.

저희는 서비스를 제공하기 위해 필요한 기간 내에 유저님의 개인 정보를 보관할 예정입니다. 단, 데이터 보존 기간에 대한 별도의 법적 근거가 존재하고 유저님이 데이터 보관 기한 연장에 동의하시며, 서비스의 안정성과 품질을 보장하고 분쟁 해결의 목적을 달성하거나 해당 조치가 기술적으로 어려울 경우에는 앞서 기술된 데이터 보관 기간이 만료되어도 법적 근거와 약관, 혹은 합리적인 범위 내에서 보관 기간을 연장할 수 있습니다.

보관 기한을 초과하게 될 경우, 저희는 법률 상의 규정에 따라 유저님의 개인 정보를 삭제하거나 익명화 작업을 진행하여

‘최소화’의 원칙을 준수하며 유저님의 개인 정보를 수집, 사용, 저장, 및 전송하게 됩니다. 또한, 이 경우 저희는 유저 약관과 프라이버시 정책, 기타 관련 규정, 혹은 팝업창이나 통지 등 방식을 통해 유저님의 관련 정보가 사용되는 목적이나 범위를 고지할 것입니다.

저희는 유저님이 제공해 주신 데이터의 안전을 매우 중요하게 생각하고 있습니다. 저희는 데이터 보안 기술과 프로그램에 대한 개발과 응용 업무를 담당하는 전담 부서를 설립했으며, 보안 관리 책임자와 주요 직책 상의 인원들에 대해 보안 배경 심사를 진행하게 됩니다. 아울러, 저희는 뛰어난 데이터 보안 관리 제도와 내부 보안 사건 처리 시스템 등을 구축해 두었습니다. 저희는 유저님의 데이터가 유실되거나, 인가받지 않은 주체에 의해 접근되거나, 외부에 의해 공개되고 사용, 훼손, 유실, 유출되는 사고를 방지하기 위해 업계 표준에 해당하는 보안 조치와 기술적 수단을 적절히 활용하여 유저님의 개인 정보를 보관 및 보호하게 됩니다. 저희는 합리적이고 실행 가능한 모든 조치들을 취하여 유저님의 개인 정보를 보호할 것입니다. 저희는 암호화 기술을 통해 데이터의 보안성을 보장할 것입니다; 저희는 신뢰받는 보호 시스템을 기반으로 유저님의 데이터를 악의적인 공격으로부터 보호할 것입니다.

저희는 내부 직원들에 대해 데이터 보안 의식 함양을 위한 교육을 진행하고 보안 인력에 대한 연수와 심사를 진행하여 개인 정보 보호의 중요성에 대한 임직원들의 인식을 강화할 것입니다. 저희는 개인 정보 처리를 담당하는 임직원들에 대해 신원 인증과 권한 통제를 진행하고 유저님의 개인 정보에 접근할 수 있는 임직원이나 협력 업체들에 대해 보안 서약을 요구할 것입니다. 또한, 저희는 각 직책의 관할 업무와 행동 수칙을 명확히 규정할 것이며, 이를 통해 인가를 받은 인원만이 유저님의 개인 정보에 접근할 수 있도록 통제할 것입니다. 보안 서약 관련 내용에 대한 위반 행위가 발생할 경우에는 당사와의 협력 관계가 그 즉시 중단되고 관련 법률적 책임을 묻게 되며, 개인 정보를 다루던 임직원들이 퇴사할 시에도 보안을 유지하도록 조치하고 있습니다.

유저님에게 주의의 말씀을 드립니다. 인터넷이 절대적으로 안전한 환경이라고는 할 수 없습니다. 유저님이 TeraBox에 기입하신 제3자 SNS 소프트웨어, 이메일, 문자 등을 통해 기타 유저와 지리적 위치와 사용 기록 등 정보들을 교환하게 될 경우에는 제3자 소프트웨어가 정보 전달에 있어 완벽한 암호화 작업을 진행하고 있는지 알기 어려우니 유저님의 개인 정보 보안에 만전을 기해주시기 바랍니다.

또한, 인터넷 업계에서는 기술적 한계와 기술의 빠른 발전, 그리고 충분히 존재할 수 있는 악의적인 공격 수단으로 인해 최선을 다해 보안 조치를 강화하더라도 언제나 유저님의 정보에 대한 100%의 안전성을 보장 드릴 수는 없습니다. 이 부분 양해 부탁드리겠습니다. 또한, 유저님이 저희의 제품이나 서비스를 이용하시면서 사용하시는 시스템이나 통신 네트워크 또한 저희의 통제 밖에 있는 요소로서 저희가 관여할 수 없는 부분에서 보안 문제가 발생할 가능성도 있습니다. 이 부분 역시 양해 부탁드립니다.

개인 정보 유출, 훼손, 혹은 유실 사태는 저희의 보안 관리 제도에 따라 초대형 안전사고로 규정되어 있으며, 이러한 사태가 발발할 경우 본사에서 최고 등급의 긴급 사태가 발령되며, 다수의 부서들이 연합 긴급 대응팀을 구성하여 이를 처리하게 됩니다.

저희는 인터넷 보안 사태 긴급 대응안을 제정하여 시스템 상의 허점, 컴퓨터 바이러스, 네트워크 공격, 네트워크 침입 등 보안 문제들에 대한 즉각적인 조치를 취할 것입니다. 네트워크 보안을 위협하는 사태가 발생할 시, 저희는 긴급 대응안을 활성화하여 상응하는 대응 조치를 취하고 규정에 따라 각 주관 부서에 보고를 진행하게 됩니다.

개인 정보 유출, 훼손, 유출 등 문제들은 본사가 규정하는 초대형 보안 사고이므로, 저희는 업무 팀의 구성원들에 대한 정기적인 보안 예비 훈련을 진행하여 이러한 사태의 발생을 방지하기 위해 책임을 다하겠습니다. 만일 그럼에도 이러한 사태가 발생했을 경우, 저희는 최우선적인 처리를 요하는 대응 태세를 발령하고 긴급 예비안을 발효하여 긴급 대응팀을 구성할 것이며, 최단 시간 내에 원인을 파악하고 손실을 최소화할 것입니다.

개인 정보에 대한 보안 사고가 발생하게 되면 저희는 법률 상 규정된 요구 사항에 따라 즉시 유저님께 보안 사고에 대한 기본적인 상황 설명을 진행하고 이에 따른 잠재적 영향, 저희 측의 대응 조치, 유저님께서 리스크 절감을 위해 취하실 수 있는 자체적인 조치, 유저님에 대한 지원 조치 등을 고지할 것입니다. 저희는 유저님이 기재해 주신 연락처를 기반으로 해당 사태에 대한 관련 상황을 웹페이지 상 고지, 문자 알림, 전화, 우편 등 방식을 통해 즉각적으로 고지해 드릴 것이며, 전체 인원에 대한 고지가 어려울 시에는 합리적이고 효과적인 방식으로 공고를 게시할 예정입니다. 또한, 저희는 감독 기관의 요구 사항에 따라 개인 정보 보안 사태에 대한 조치 현황을 자발적으로 보고할 것입니다. 법률 상 규정에 따르면, 저희가 취하는 조치들이 정보 유출, 왜곡, 유실 등에 따른 피해를 효과적으로 회피할 수 있을 경우에는 감독 기관이 별도로 유저님께 통지하지 않는 이상 저희는 유저님께 해당 개인 정보 보안 사태에 대한 통지를 하지 않도록 선택할 수 있습니다.

저희는 GDPR 측의 요구 사항을 참고하여 데이터 처리의 속성, 범위, 배경, 목적, 그리고 개인에 대해 일으킬 수 있는 위협 등을 고려하여 적절한 기술적 보안 조치를 취할 것이며, 이에 대한 정기적인 테스팅과 평가를 진행하여 저희가 취할 수 있는 조치들의 유효성을 유지할 것입니다.

데이터 유출 사건이 발생하게 되면 데이터 유출의 영향을 받게 되는 관련 인원들에게 최대한 빠르게 이를 고지할 것이며, 72시간 이내에 주관 부서에 해당 내용을 보고하게 됩니다. 72시간 내에 보고를 진행할 수 없을 경우에는 보고 연기 사유를 소명하게 됩니다.

저희는 적절한 기술적/조직적 조치들을 취해 데이터에 대한 보안 목표를 달성할 것이며, 데이터 최소화 및 필수적인 보장 조치 등을 데이터 처리 과정과 융합하여 데이터 주체의 각종 권리들을 보호하기 위해 기본적인 상황 하에서 특정 목적으로 진행되는 데이터 처리 절차가 반드시 필요한지의 여부를 확인할 것입니다.

개인정보 저장 및 처리 장소

서비스를 제공할 때, 저희는 유저님의 제공 동의하에 일본에서 유저님의 데이터를 저장, 처리, 전송할 수 있습니다. 유저님의 개인정보는 서비스 접근에 이용되는 로컬 스토리지에 저장될 수 있습니다.

유저 측의 개인정보 통제 및 접근 방법

저희는 관련 국가/지역의 법률, 법규, 표준, 그리고 통상적인 관행에 따라 유저님이 자신의 개인 정보에 대한 아래의 권리들을 행사할 수 있도록 보장할 것입니다. 권리 행사에 대한 문의 사항이나 건의 사항이 있으실 경우 [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com)를 통해 저희와 연락을 취하실 수 있습니다. 유저님께서는 TeraBox 계정에서 유저님의 개인 정보를 조회, 수정, 다운로드, 삭제, 혹은 공유하실 수 있습니다.

1\. 조회의 권리

TeraBox가 획득, 보관, 공유하는 개인 정보의 범위 혹은 개인 정보의 처리 목적에 대한 설명을 원하시는 경우에는 언제나 저희에게 연락을 취해 관련 내용을 제공받으실 수 있습니다.

2\. 수정 및 보충의 권리

유저님께서 저희가 처리하는 유저님의 개인 정보에 오류가 있다는 사실을 발견하실 경우에는 착오가 있거나 불완전한 정보에 대한 정정을 진행하실 수 있습니다. 유저님에 대한 신원 인증 절차가 완료된 후, 유저님께서는 피드백 및 오류 제기 등을 통해 앞서 명시된 당사의 연락처 등을 통해 수정 및 보충 신청서를 전달해 주실 수 있습니다. 유저님의 신청서를 접수한 후 최대한 빠르게 피드백을 드리도록 하겠습니다.

3\. 삭제의 권리

이하 상황에서 유저님께서는 저희에게 개인 정보 삭제를 요청하실 수 있습니다.

저희가 법률 상의 규정이나 유저님과의 약관을 위반하는 방식으로 개인정보를 처리할 경우;

저희가 명시한 데이터 처리 목적이 이미 달성되었거나, 실현이 불가능하거나, 목표 달성에 더 이상 해당 데이터가 필요하지 않을 경우;

저희가 제품 및 서비스의 제공을 중단하거나 데이터 보관 기간이 만료되었을 경우; 유저님이 동의를 철회하실 경우;

법률 및 행정 법규 상의 규정에 따른 기타 상황이 적용될 경우.

유저님이 저희의 서비스에서 개인 정보를 삭제하실지라도 백업 시스템에 저장되어 있는 관련 정보들은 즉각적으로 삭제되지 않을 수 있습니다. 단, 백업이 갱신되면 해당 정보들이 삭제됩니다. 단, 법률 혹은 행정 법규 상의 규정이나 해당 프라이버시 정책 상에 설명된 보존 기간이 만료되지 않았거나 개인 정보 삭제가 기술적으로 실현되기 어려울 경우에는 저장 및 반드시 필요한 보안 조치를 제외한 기타 처리 작업을 중단하게 됩니다.

4\. 동의를 철회

각 업무 기능에 대한 동의를 철회하는 작업을 완성하기 위해서는 일부 기본적인 개인 정보들이 필요합니다. 별도로 수집된 개인 정보들에 대한 수집 및 사용 동의는 언제나 부여 혹은 철회하실 수 있습니다.

유저님은 통신 로그, 사진 앨범, 렌즈 등에 대한 시스템 권한들을 기기 시스템 상에서 직접적으로 비활성화하시거나, 동의 범위를 수정하거나 철회하실 수 있습니다.

동의를 철회하신 후에는 동의를 철회하신 부분에 상응하는 서비스의 지속적인 제공이 어려워지며, 이에 상응하는 개인 정보 또한 더 이상 사용하지 않게 됩니다. 단, 유저님의 동의 철회는 과거 제공된 유저님의 동의에 따라 이미 전개된 개인정보 처리 절차에는 영향을 미치지 않습니다.

5\. 계정 삭제의 권리

유저님은 과거 개설하신 계정을 삭제하실 수 있습니다. 유저님께서는 이하의 디렉터리를 따라 TeraBox에서 유저님의 계정을 삭제하실 수 있습니다.

\[프로필 아이콘\] – \[메뉴\] – \[설정\] – \[보안센터\] – \[계정 삭제\].

유저님의 계정이 삭제되면 TeraBox의 제품과 서비스를 이용하실 수 없게 되니 신중히 진행해 주시기 바랍니다. 저희는 유저님과 타인들의 합법적인 권리와 이익을 보호하기 위해 유저님의 사용 현황을 기반으로 유저님의 계정 삭제 요청에 대한 수락 여부를 판단하게 됩니다. 유저님께서 아직 소비하지 않으신 Premium이 존재하는 경우, 혹은 유저님의 계정 상에 아직 저장되어 있는 자료가 존재할 경우에는 유저님의 삭제 요청에 대한 즉각적인 삭제 조치는 진행하지 않게 됩니다. 법률 상 별도의 규정이 존재하지 않는 한, 계정이 삭제되면 저희는 유저님에 대한 제품 및 서비스 제공을 중단하게 되며, 유저님의 요청 사항에 다라 개인 정보를 삭제하게 도비니다.

6\. 복제 및 휴대 가능의 권리

유저님은 저희가 수집한 유저님의 개인 정보를 복제하실 권리가 있습니다. 법률 및 법규의 규정, 그리고 관련 주관 부서의 규정 및 조건을 동시에 만족하게 되는 경우, 유저님은 유저님의 개인 정보를 기술적으로 실행할 수 있는 수준에서 유저님이 지정하신 기타 주체로 이전할 것을 요청하실 수 있습니다.

유저님께서 앞서 언급된 개인 정보 주체 관련 권리를 행사하실 때, 저희는 이를 즉각적으로 관련 제3자에게 전달할 것이며, 법률과 감독 관리 상의 요구 사항에 따라 기술적으로 가능한 범위 안에서 유저님의 권리들을 보장할 수 있도록 조치할 것입니다.

유저님의 요구 사항에 확실하고 정당한 이유가 없거나 필요한 수준을 넘어서는 경우, 특히 해당 요청 사항이 중복적일 경우, 저희는 해당 조치들을 취할 수 있습니다.

(a) 제공 정보, 커뮤니케이션, 그리고 관련 조치에 소요되는 행정 비용들을 종합하여 합리적인 수준에서 일정 비용을 수취하는 것; 혹은

(b) 요청 사항에 대한 처리를 거부하는 것.

유저님께서는 <일본 개인정보 보호법> (“보류된 개인정보”)에 의거하여 유저님이 보류하고자 선택하신 개인정보나 그에 대한 수집, 사용, 공유 방식을 통제하실 수 있습니다. 예시는 아래와 같습니다.

a. 현재 저장되어 있는 유저님의 신분을 식별해낼 수 있는 개인정보에 대한 공개를 요구하는 것.

b. 특정 개인을 식별해낼 수 있는 보류된 개인 정보의 내용이 사실이 아닐 경우 해당 개인정보 내용에 대한 수정, 추가, 삭제를 요청하는 것.

c. 유저님이 보류하신 개인 정보가 저희에 의해 불법적으로 획득된 정보이거나, 해당 보류된 개인 정보가 저희에 의해 사용 중일 경우, 보류된 개인정보에 대한 즉각적인 삭제나 사용 중지를 요청하는 것.

d. 저희가 유저님이 보류하신 개인정보를 불법적으로 제3자에게 제공할 경우 보류된 개인정보의 제공을 즉각적으로 중지하도록 요청하는 것.

변경

Flextech에 대한 구조조정, 합병, 인수가 이루어지거나 저희의 자산이 판매되는 경우에는 유저님의 정보가 해당 거래의 생존 측, 구매자, 혹은 계승자에게 이전될 수 있습니다. 이러한 유형의 거래가 있을 경우에는 유저님께 관련 정보를 통지해 드리고(예: 유저님의 계정과 관련되어 있는 이메일 주소로 안내 발송), 해당 상황에서 유저님께서 선택하실 수 있는 선택지에 대한 설명을 진행해 드릴 예정입니다.

해당 프라이버시 정책은 수시로 수정될 수 있습니다. 저희는 TeraBox의 웹페이지 상에 최신 버전을 공개할 예정입니다. 해당 내용에 유저님의 권리에 중대한 영향을 미칠 수 있는 수정 사항이 발생하는 경우에는 유저님께 해당 내용이 통지됩니다.

연락처：

TeraBox나 저희의 서비스 및 프라이버시 관련 권리에 대해 문의 혹은 우려 사항이 있으실 경우에는 [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com)를 통해 저희에게 연락해 주시기 바랍니다.

TeraBox गोपनीयता नीति

TeraBox गोपनीयता नीति

\>कंटेंट और जानकारी संग्रह करने का उद्देश्य

तीसरी पार्टी के लिए निजी जानकारी का प्रावधान

अन्य उपयोगकर्ताओं के साथ साझा

हम आपकी जानकारी तीसरी पार्टी से भी शेयर कर सकते है

हम कैसे रक्षा करते हैं और आपकी जानकारी स्टोर करते है

हम कहाँ आपकी जानकारी स्टोर और प्रोसेस करते हैं

कैसे आप नियंत्रण और अपनी जानकारी को पा सकते हैं

{{ $t('termsOfServicePrivacyPolicy.age.title') }}

बदलाव

हमें संपर्क करें:

TeraBox गोपनीयता नीति

प्रकाशित तिथि: 18 अप्रैल, 2023

प्रभावी तिथि: 18 अप्रैल, 2023

TeraBox का उपयोग करने के लिए धन्यवाद! TeraBox आपको Flextech Inc. ("Flextech" या "हमलोग") द्वारा प्रदान किया जाता है। आपकी गोपनीयता की रक्षा करने के लिए हम वचनबद्ध हैं। यह गोपनीयता नीति निर्धारित करती है कि जब आप हमारी वेबसाइट, सॉफ़्टवेयर और सेवाओं ("सेवाएं") का उपयोग करते हैं तो हम आपकी जानकारी को कैसे एकत्रित, संग्रहीत, संसाधित, साझा और उपयोग करते हैं।

हम आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को वैधता, न्याय और आवश्यकता के सिद्धांतों के अनुसार एकत्रित और उपयोग करेंगे। विशेष रूप से, हम आपको संबंधित व्यावसायिक कार्य प्रदान करने के लिए आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी एकत्र और संसाधित करते हैं। संबंधित कार्य में, यदि आप दूसरों की व्यक्तिगत जानकारी प्रदान करते हैं, तो कृपया सुनिश्चित करें कि आपने संबंधित विषय का प्राधिकरण प्राप्त कर लिया है, और हम किसी भी समय ऐसी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी के कानूनी स्रोत की जाँच करने का अधिकार रखते हैं।

हम कानूनों और विनियमों की आवश्यकताओं का सख्ती से पालन करेंगे, और विशिष्ट परिस्थितियों में आपकी अलग सहमति मांगेंगे। इस गोपनीयता नीति के अलावा, हम आपको उत्पाद पृष्ठों, पॉप-अप विंडो, सूचना पुश आदि पर सूचनाओं के माध्यम से आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को संसाधित करने के लिए हमारे नियम भी समझा सकते हैं। विशिष्ट नियमों के अनुरूप व्यक्तिगत जानकारी के प्रसंस्करण के लिए विशिष्ट नियम प्रबल होंगे। व्यावसायिक कार्य, विशिष्ट नियमों का वही प्रभाव होता है जो इस गोपनीयता नीति का होता है।

कृपया ध्यान दें: निम्नलिखित स्थितियों में, व्यक्तिगत जानकारी के संग्रह, उपयोग, साझाकरण, हस्तांतरण और सार्वजनिक प्रकटीकरण के लिए आपके पूर्व प्राधिकरण और सहमति की आवश्यकता नहीं है:

राष्ट्रीय सुरक्षा और राष्ट्रीय रक्षा सुरक्षा से सीधे संबंधित;

किसी अनुबंध के समापन और प्रदर्शन के लिए जो व्यक्ति एक पार्टी है आवश्यक;

वैधानिक कर्तव्यों या दायित्वों को पूरा करने के लिए आवश्यक;

सार्वजनिक स्वास्थ्य आपात स्थितियों का जवाब देने के लिए आवश्यक, या आपातकालीन स्थितियों में प्राकृतिक व्यक्तियों के जीवन, स्वास्थ्य और संपत्ति की सुरक्षा की रक्षा करने के लिए;

आपराधिक जांच, अभियोजन, परीक्षण से सीधे संबंधित और निर्णयों का निष्पादन;

आपके या अन्य व्यक्तिगत जीवन, संपत्ति और अन्य प्रमुख वैध अधिकारों और हितों की रक्षा के लिए लेकिन व्यक्ति की सहमति प्राप्त करना मुश्किल है;

कानूनों और विनियमों के प्रावधानों के अनुसार, व्यक्तिगत जानकारी एकत्र करें जिसे आप सार्वजनिक रूप से खुलासा करें या एक उचित सीमा के भीतर कानूनी रूप से खुलासा किया गया है;

कानून और विनियमों के प्रावधानों के अनुसार कानूनी रूप से प्रकट जानकारी से एक उचित सीमा के भीतर अपनी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी एकत्र करें, जैसे कानूनी समाचार रिपोर्ट, सरकारी सूचना प्रकटीकरण और अन्य चैनल;

जनता के हित के लिए समाचार रिपोर्ट और सार्वजनिक राय पर्यवेक्षण को एक उचित सीमा के भीतर लागू करें;

शैक्षणिक अनुसंधान संस्थानों के लिए सार्वजनिक हितों के आधार पर सांख्यिकीय या शैक्षणिक अनुसंधान करना आवश्यक है, और जब बाहरी दुनिया को अकादमिक शोध या विवरण परिणाम प्रदान करते हैं, तो पहचान को हटा दें परिणामों में निहित व्यक्तिगत जानकारी;

प्रासंगिक कानून और नियम निर्दिष्ट अन्य परिस्थितियां।

कंटेंट और जानकारी संग्रह करने का उद्देश्य

नीचे दी गई तालिका इन सेवाओं का उपयोग करते समय आपके द्वारा हमें सबमिट की जाने वाली जानकारी के प्रकार और उन उद्देश्यों को सूचीबद्ध करती है जिनके लिए हम इसका उपयोग कर सकते हैं। हम अपनी सेवाएं प्रदान करने, अनुकूलन, सुरक्षा और प्रचार करने के लिए निम्नलिखित जानकारी एकत्र करते हैं और उसका उपयोग करते हैं।

| सूचना का प्रकार | संग्रह करने का उद्देश्य |
| --- | --- |
| खाता संबंधी जानकारी। हम ई-मेल , फोन नंबर और अन्य जानकारी एकत्र करेंगे (जैसे खाता पंजीकृत करना) जो आप हमें प्रदान करते हैं जब आप कुछ संचालन करते हैं (यदि आप लॉग इन या लॉग इन करने के लिए एसएनएस खाते का उपयोग करते हैं, तो हम आपका उपनाम प्राप्त करेंगे और SNS प्रोफ़ाइल चित्र डेटा ) और इस जानकारी को अपने खाते से संबद्ध करें। | हम इस जानकारी का उपयोग आपको खाता धारक के रूप में पहचानने और आपके खाते की सुरक्षा के लिए करते हैं। जब आप अपने खाते में लॉग इन होते हैं तो हम यह जानकारी एकत्र कर सकते हैं। |
| उपयोगकर्ता के लिए जानकारी। सामग्री जिसे आप TeraBox पर संग्रहीत करते हैं, जैसे फ़ाइलें, दस्तावेज़, फ़ोटो, वीडियो और ऑडियो ("उपयोगकर्ता सामग्री")। | सेवाओं के उचित संचालन को सुनिश्चित करने और आपको दूसरों के साथ सहयोग करने और कई उपकरणों और सेवाओं पर काम करने की अनुमति देने के लिए हम उपयोगकर्ता सामग्री और उससे संबंधित जानकारी को संग्रहीत, संसाधित और प्रसारित कर सकते हैं। इस संबंधित जानकारी में आपकी प्रोफ़ाइल जानकारी, फ़ाइल आकार, अपलोड दिनांक और समय और उपयोग गतिविधि शामिल है। |
| उपयोग की जानकारी। सेवाओं का उपयोग करने के तरीके के बारे में जानकारी, जिसमें खाते के भीतर की जाने वाली कार्रवाइयाँ शामिल हैं, जैसे फ़ाइलों या फ़ोल्डरों को संपादित करना, देखना, बनाना और स्थानांतरित करना। | हम इस जानकारी का उपयोग सेवाओं को प्रदान करने, बेहतर बनाने और विस्तार करने और इसके अलावा TeraBox के उपयोगकर्ताओं की सुरक्षा के लिए कर सकते हैं। |
| डिवाइस जानकारी। सेवाओं तक पहुँचने के लिए उपयोग की जाने वाली डिवाइस के बारे में जानकारी, जैसे IP पता, ब्राउज़र और डिवाइस की जानकारी, TeraBox से पहले विज़िट किए गए वेब पेज, डिवाइस से जुड़े पहचानकर्ता, और डिवाइस की सेटिंग के आधार पर स्थान की जानकारी। | हम इस जानकारी का उपयोग अपने सर्विस को बेहतर बनाने और उसकी रक्षा करने के लिए कर सकते हैं। |
| Cookies। जब आप TeraBox पर जाते हैं तो एक वेबसाइट द्वारा आपके ब्राउज़र पर भेजा गया पाठ का एक छोटा सा टुकड़ा। आप अपने ब्राउज़र को Cookies स्वीकार न करने के लिए सेट कर सकते हैं, लेकिन यह सेवाओं की कार्यक्षमता को प्रभावित कर सकता है। | हम सेवाओं को प्रदान करने, सुधारने, सुरक्षित करने और बढ़ावा देने के लिए Cookies और समान तकनीकों का उपयोग कर सकते हैं। Cookies हमें आपका निकनाम याद रखने, आपके सर्विस के उपयोग को समझने और जानकारी के अनुसार सर्विस को सुधारने में मदद करता हैं। तीसरे पक्ष के सेवा प्रदाता जिनके साथ हम काम करते हैं, वे भी Cookies और इसी तरह की तकनीकों का उपयोग कर सकते हैं। |
| संपर्क की सुविधा। आप TeraBox के साझाकरण फ़ंक्शन का उपयोग कर के फोन एड्रेस बुक, मोबाइल नंबरों, ईमेल पतों (जैसे Facebook, Twitter) में संपर्कों के साथ अपना डेटा और जानकारी साझा करने के लिए साझाकरण फ़ंक्शन का उपयोग कर सकते हैं। पता पुस्तिका की जानकारी व्यक्तिगत और संवेदनशील जानकारी है। यह जानकारी प्रदान करने से इनकार करने से आप केवल उपरोक्त कार्यों का उपयोग करने में असमर्थ हो जाएंगे, लेकिन अन्य TeraBox कार्यों और संबंधित सेवाओं के आपके सामान्य उपयोग को प्रभावित नहीं करेंगे। | आप कुछ कार्यों को सुगम बनाने के लिए TeraBox को अपनी संपर्क जानकारी तक पहुंचने की अनुमति देना चुन सकते हैं, जैसे आपके डेटा पर दूसरों के साथ साझा करना और सहयोग करना, संदेश भेजना और दूसरों को ईमेल भेजकर टेराबॉक्स सेवाओं का उपयोग करने के लिए आमंत्रित करना। इस क्रिया के लिए आपको पता पुस्तिका अनुमतियों को सक्षम करने की आवश्यकता है। हम आपके उपयोग के लिए इस जानकारी को अपने सर्वर पर स्टोर करेंगे। कृपया साझा करने से पहले संदेश प्राप्तकर्ता की विश्वसनीयता पर विचार करें। उसी समय, हम अनुशंसा करते हैं कि आप विवेकपूर्ण निर्णय लेने के लिए यह समझने के लिए सामाजिक नेटवर्क या तृतीय-पक्ष सेवा प्रदाताओं के गोपनीयता कथनों की जाँच करें कि वे आपकी जानकारी को कैसे संभालते हैं। |
| क्लिपबोर्ड। जब आप किसी के आमंत्रण कोड का उपयोग करके Terabox खाता रजिस्टर करते हैं, तो आपकी क्लिपबोर्ड सूचना पढ़ेंगे जब आप किसी के आमंत्रण कोड का उपयोग करके Terabox खाता रजिस्टर करते हैं, अन्य उपयोगकर्ताओं द्वारा साझा किए गए फ़ाइल लिंक तक पहुँचते हैं, पासवर्ड के माध्यम से दोस्तों को जोड़ते हैं, या रिडेंप कोड के माध्यम से सदस्यता सेवाओं को प्राप्त करते हैं, तो हम आपकी क्लिपबोर्ड जानकारी पढ़ेंगे। | हम क्लिपबोर्ड की जानकारी तक पहुँचेंगे ताकि आपकी मदद कर सकें लिंक के अनुरूप फाइल खोलने में, पासवर्ड और आमंत्रण कोड के अनुरूप उपयोगकर्ता की पहचान करने में, या आपके लिए सदस्यता सेवाएँ भुनाने में। हम कभी भी किसी अन्य उद्देश्य से आपके क्लिपबोर्ड को नहीं पढ़ेंगे। |

आप अपने मोबाइल फोन नंबर के माध्यम से TeraBox खाता बना सकते हैं, और आप अपनी खाता जानकारी पूरी कर सकते हैं।

कानूनों और विनियमों की अनिवार्य आवश्यकताओं को पूरा करने के लिए, उत्पादों या सेवाओं को प्रदान करने के लिए, या बढ़ी हुई खाता सुरक्षा की आपकी मांग के आधार पर, आपको TeraBox की कुछ सेवाओं का उपयोग करते समय या जब आपकी और ज़रूरतें हों, तो आपको अपना वास्तविक नाम प्रदान करने की आवश्यकता होती है , खाता प्रमाणीकरण संख्या और चेहरे की जानकारी। आपके द्वारा प्रदान की गई जानकारी की सटीकता और पूर्णता को सत्यापित करने के लिए, या आपके खाते की सुरक्षा की रक्षा के लिए, हम आपके द्वारा TeraBox को प्रदान की जाने वाली वास्तविक नाम की जानकारी की तुलना सरकारी एजेंसियां कानूनों और विनियमों द्वारा अनुमत या अधिकृत संस्थानों द्वारा संग्रहीत आपकी संबंधित जानकारी से कर सकते हैं। तुलना करें और सत्यापित करें।

उपरोक्त जानकारी सेवाओं के विश्वसनीय और सुरक्षित प्रावधान और वैध व्यावसायिक उद्देश्यों के लिए एकत्र की गई है। हम या हमारे सहयोगी किसी अन्य उद्देश्य के लिए आपकी जानकारी को संसाधित करने से पहले आपकी पूर्व सहमति मांगेंगे।

आप सहमत हैं कि हम आपके द्वारा इस सेवा में सक्रिय रूप से या निष्क्रिय रूप से प्रदान की जाने वाली व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को हमारे अपने या सौंपी गई पार्टी की तकनीक के माध्यम से एकत्रित, पहचान, विश्लेषण, प्रोफाइल या आगे की प्रक्रिया करेंगे, और विभिन्न प्रकार और विभिन्न ग्रैन्युलैरिटी तैयार करेंगे जो आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को दर्शा सकते हैं। व्यवहार की आदतों, शौक, या क्रेडिट स्थिति (इसके बाद "टैग जानकारी" के रूप में संदर्भित) जैसी विशेषताओं के साथ टैग जानकारी, हम स्वचालित निर्णय लेने के लिए विशिष्ट परिदृश्यों और उद्देश्यों के लिए टैग जानकारी का उपयोग करेंगे, और वैयक्तिकृत प्रदर्शन जानकारी और/या व्यवसाय को आगे बढ़ाएंगे विपणन जानकारी।

आपके पास हमारी स्वचालित निर्णय लेने वाली तकनीकी सेवाओं को अस्वीकार करने का अधिकार है। आप इस समझौते में प्रकाशित संपर्क जानकारी के माध्यम से हमसे संपर्क कर सकते हैं या उत्पाद सेवा में प्रासंगिक स्विच के माध्यम से हमें बंद करने के लिए कह सकते हैं। साथ ही, स्वचालित निर्णय लेने के निषेध पर प्रासंगिक देशों या क्षेत्रों के कानूनों और विनियमों या नियामक आवश्यकताओं के अनुसार, हम उन्हें आवश्यकतानुसार लागू भी करेंगे।

हम आपके खाता डेटा का उपयोग विपणन उद्देश्यों के लिए कर सकते हैं, और समय-समय पर आपको TeraBox के नए उत्पादों, उन्नयनों और अन्य विपणन सामग्री के बारे में जानकारी भेज सकते हैं। आप कभी भी विपणन सामग्री प्राप्त करने का विकल्प त्याग सकते हैं, इसका तरीका है कि आपको प्राप्त हुए किसी भी ई-मेल में "सदस्यता रद्द करें" लिंक पर क्लिक करें।

तीसरी पार्टी के लिए निजी जानकारी का प्रावधान

हम आपकी सहमति के बिना किसी तीसरे पक्ष को व्यक्तिगत जानकारी प्रदान नहीं करेंगे, जब तक कि निम्नलिखित में से किसी भी परिस्थिति के लिए आवश्यक न हो:

(a) हमें लागू कानूनों और विनियमों के तहत अपने कर्तव्यों या दायित्वों को पूरा करने के लिए राष्ट्रीय या क्षेत्रीय सरकारी संगठनों या उनके एजेंटों के साथ सहयोग करना चाहिए, जो आपकी सहमति की आवश्यकता होने पर ऐसे प्रदर्शन को रोक सकते हैं।

(b) किसी व्यक्ति के जीवन या संपत्ति के लिए गंभीर खतरा प्रस्तुत करता है;

(c) सार्वजनिक स्वास्थ्य में सुधार या स्वस्थ युवा विकास को बढ़ावा देने की विशेष आवश्यकता है

उपरोक्त अपवादों के तहत आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को साझा करने, स्थानांतरित करने या प्रकट करने के लिए, हम प्रासंगिक जानकारी को संसाधित करने के लिए आधार, प्रसंस्करण जानकारी का दायरा और प्राप्तकर्ता की जानकारी रिकॉर्ड जारी रखे विशेष रूप से निम्नलिखित सामग्री शामिल करें, और अपने कानूनी अधिकारों की रक्षा के लिए न्यूनतम और आवश्यक सिद्धांतों का पालन करें।

(1) डेटा नियंत्रक और डेटा सुरक्षा अधिकारी का नाम और संपर्क विवरण;

(2) डेटा प्रोसेसिंग का उद्देश्य;

(3) डेटा विषय के प्रकार और व्यक्तिगत डेटा के प्रकार का विवरण;

(4) व्यक्तिगत डेटा में खुलासा किया गया है या प्राप्तकर्ताओं के प्रकार (तीसरे देशों या अंतरराष्ट्रीय संगठनों में स्थित प्राप्तकर्ताओं सहित) जिनके लिए इसका खुलासा किया जाएगा;

(5) तीसरे देशों या अंतरराष्ट्रीय संगठनों को व्यक्तिगत डेटा के हस्तांतरण के रिकॉर्ड और उचित सुरक्षा उपायों के रिकॉर्ड;

(6) अलग अलग प्रकार के डेटा को हटाने के लिए अनुमानित समय सीमा;

(7) तकनीकी और संगठनात्मक सुरक्षा उपायों का एक सामान्य विवरण।

अन्य उपयोगकर्ताओं के साथ साझा

जब आप TeraBox द्वारा प्रदान किए गए टीम सहयोग या फ़ाइल साझाकरण कार्यों का उपयोग करते हैं, तो हमारी सेवा अन्य उपयोगकर्ताओं को आपका उपनाम, उपकरण, ईमेल पता और उपयोग जानकारी प्रदर्शित करेगी जो आपके साथ सहयोग करते हैं या आपकी अनुमति के अनुसार आपके साथ साझा करना चुनते हैं। यह आपको उन टीमों के साथ सिंक करने में मदद करेगा, जिनसे आप लगातार जुड़ा रहना चाहते हैं और अन्य उपयोगकर्ताओं को आपके साथ फ़ाइलें और फ़ोल्डर साझा करने में मदद मिलेगी।

हम आपकी जानकारी तीसरी पार्टी से भी शेयर कर सकते है

हम कुछ विश्वसनीय तृतीय पक्षों का उपयोग कर सकते हैं (जैसे ग्राहक सहायता और आईटी सेवा) , आपकी सेवाओं को बेहतर ढंग से प्रदान करने, अनुकूलन करने, सुरक्षा और प्रचार करने में मदद करने के लिए। इन तृतीय पक्षों के पास हमारी ओर से कार्य करने के लिए आपकी जानकारी तक पहुंच सकते हैं और हम अपने निर्देशों के अनुसार तृतीय पक्ष द्वारा आपकी जानकारी के प्रसंस्करण के लिए जिम्मेदार हैं।

हम इन सेवाओं को प्रदान करने, सुधारने, सुरक्षित करने और बढ़ावा देने के लिए Flextech सहयोगियों के साथ बुनियादी ढांचा, सिस्टम और तकनीक साझा कर सकते हैं। ये सहयोगी आपकी जानकारी हमारे साथ साझा करेंगे और उसमें वर्णित उद्देश्यों के लिए आपके द्वारा "कंटेंट और जानकारी संग्रह करने का उद्देश्य" अनुभाग में सूचीबद्ध जानकारी का उपयोग करेंगे। इन कंपनियों द्वारा आपकी जानकारी के उपयोग के लिए हम जिम्मेदार होंगे।

आप तृतीय-पक्ष सेवा के माध्यम से अपने TeraBox खाते से जुड़ना चुन सकते हैं। ऐसी सेवाओं से जुड़कर, आप इन तृतीय पक्षों और हमें इस गोपनीयता नीति के "कंटेंट और जानकारी संग्रह करने का उद्देश्य" अनुभाग में सूचीबद्ध जानकारी का आदान-प्रदान करने की अनुमति देते हैं ताकि ये तृतीय पक्ष और हम अपनी सेवाएं प्रदान, सुधार, सुरक्षा और सुविधा प्रदान कर सकें। इन मामलों में, आपकी जानकारी का उपयोग गोपनीयता नीति और तृतीय-पक्ष सेवा की शर्तों द्वारा नियंत्रित किया जाएगा जिसके माध्यम से आप कनेक्ट करना चुनते हैं।

हम GDPR की आवश्यकताओं के संदर्भ में सीमा-पार डेटा स्थानांतरण के लिए एक निर्यात तंत्र स्थापित करेंगे, और GDPR की आवश्यकताओं के आधार पर इसके सीमा-पार तंत्र को समयबद्ध तरीके से अपडेट करेंगे। व्यक्तिगत डेटा का कोई भी प्रसंस्करण GDPR के मूलभूत सिद्धांतों के प्रावधानों को पूरा करेगा, मान्य डेटा विषय की सहमति प्राप्त करेगा या अन्य वैध आधारों को पूरा करेगा। इसके अलावा, डेटा प्रोसेसिंग के लिए GDPR की मूल आवश्यकताओं को पूरा करने के लिए डेटा की सुरक्षा के लिए अतिरिक्त तंत्र स्थापित किए जाएंगे।

हम कैसे रक्षा करते हैं और आपकी जानकारी स्टोर करते है

हमारी एक टीम है जो आपकी जानकारी को सुरक्षित रखने और कमजोरियों के परीक्षण के लिए समर्पित है। टू-फैक्टर ऑथेंटिकेशन, फाइल एनक्रिप्शन को डिसेबल करने और नए डिवाइस और ऐप के आपके अकाउंट को लिंक करने पर आपको अलर्ट करने के अलावा, हम आपकी जानकारी को सुरक्षित रखने के लिए कड़ी मेहनत कर रहे हैं। हम ऐसे अपमानजनक व्यवहार और सामग्री का पता लगाने के लिए स्वचालित तकनीकों को तैनात करते हैं जो हमारी सेवाओं, आपको या अन्य उपयोगकर्ताओं को नुकसान पहुंचा सकती हैं।

जब आप TeraBox खाते के लिए साइन अप करते हैं, तो हम आपके द्वारा हमारी सेवाओं पर संग्रहीत जानकारी को तब तक बनाए रखेंगे जब तक आपका खाता मौजूद है या हमें आपको सेवाएं प्रदान करने की आवश्यकता है। यदि आप अपना खाता हटाना चाहते हैं, तो कृपया अपनी जानकारी हटाने के लिए [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) पर ईमेल करें और हम आपका अनुरोध प्राप्त होने के 30 दिनों के भीतर पूर्ण करेंगे; हालाँकि, यदि: (1) जब तक हम आपकी उपयोगकर्ता पहचान सत्यापित नहीं कर लेते, तब तक हम आपकी खाता जानकारी को नही हटाएंगे और ना ही मिटाएंगे; (2) हमारे सर्वर और बैकअप स्टोरेज से हटाने में देरी हो सकती है, और (3) हम इस जानकारी को अपने कानूनी दायित्वों का पालन करने, विवादों को सुलझाने या अनुबंध के तहत अपने अधिकारों को लागू करने के लिए आवश्यकतानुसार रख सकते हैं।

हम आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को सेवाएं प्रदान करने के लिए आवश्यक अवधि के भीतर रखेंगे, लेकिन कानूनों और विनियमों में भंडारण अवधि पर अन्य प्रावधान हैं, आप इसे लंबी अवधि के लिए रखने के लिए सहमत हैं, सेवाओं की सुरक्षा और गुणवत्ता सुनिश्चित करने के उद्देश्य को प्राप्त करने के लिए विवाद समाधान, और प्राप्त करने के लिए तकनीकी रूप से कठिन ऐसी परिस्थितियों में, उपरोक्त भंडारण अवधि समाप्त होने के बाद, हम कानून के अनुसार, समझौते के अनुसार या उचित सीमा के भीतर भंडारण अवधि का विस्तार करेंगे।

भंडारण अवधि समाप्त हो जाने के बाद, हम आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को हटा देंगे या कानून के अनुसार इसे गुमनाम कर देंगे।

हम "न्यूनीकरण" के सिद्धांत के आधार पर और उपयोगकर्ता समझौते और गोपनीयता नीति के आधार पर उपयोगकर्ता जानकारी एकत्र, उपयोग, संग्रहीत और प्रसारित करेंगे। संबंधित नियम, पॉप-अप विंडो, सूचनाएं आदि आपको प्रासंगिक जानकारी के उपयोग के उद्देश्य और दायरे के बारे में सूचित करते हैं।

हम सूचना सुरक्षा को बहुत गंभीरता से लेते हैं। हमने विभिन्न सुरक्षा तकनीकों और प्रक्रियाओं आदि के विकास और अनुप्रयोग के लिए जिम्मेदार एक समर्पित टीम की स्थापना की है। हम सुरक्षा प्रबंधन के प्रभारी व्यक्ति और प्रमुख सुरक्षा पदों पर कर्मियों की सुरक्षा पृष्ठभूमि की जांच करेंगे, और हमने पूरी जानकारी स्थापित की है। हमने एक ठोस सूचना सुरक्षा प्रबंधन प्रणाली और एक आंतरिक सुरक्षा घटना प्रबंधन तंत्र स्थापित किया है। हम आपकी जानकारी को खो जाने, अनधिकृत पहुंच, सार्वजनिक प्रकटीकरण, उपयोग, क्षति, हानि या रिसाव से बचाने के लिए आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को संग्रहीत और सुरक्षित करने के लिए उपयुक्त उद्योग-मानक सुरक्षा उपाय और तकनीकी साधन अपनाएंगे। हम आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी की सुरक्षा के लिए सभी उचित और व्यवहार्य उपाय करेंगे। हम डेटा की गोपनीयता सुनिश्चित करने के लिए एन्क्रिप्शन तकनीक का उपयोग करेंगे; हम दुर्भावनापूर्ण हमलों से डेटा को रोकने के लिए विश्वसनीय सुरक्षा तंत्र का उपयोग करेंगे।

हम व्यक्तिगत जानकारी की सुरक्षा के महत्व के बारे में कर्मचारियों की जागरूकता को मजबूत करने के लिए कर्मचारियों के लिए डेटा सुरक्षा जागरूकता प्रशिक्षण और सुरक्षा क्षमता प्रशिक्षण और मूल्यांकन आयोजित करेंगे। हम व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को संभालने वाले कर्मचारियों के लिए पहचान प्रमाणीकरण और अधिकार नियंत्रण का संचालन करेंगे, और यह सुनिश्चित करने के लिए कि केवल अधिकृत कर्मचारी ही व्यक्तिगत जानकारी तक पहुंच सकते हैं, नौकरी की जिम्मेदारियों और आचार संहिता को स्पष्ट करने के लिए कर्मचारियों और भागीदारों के साथ गोपनीयता समझौते पर हस्ताक्षर करेंगे, जिनके पास आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी है। यदि गोपनीयता समझौते का कोई उल्लंघन होता है, तो कंपनी के साथ सहकारी संबंध तुरंत समाप्त कर दिए जाएंगे, और प्रासंगिक कानूनी जिम्मेदारियों की जांच की जाएगी। जिन कर्मियों की व्यक्तिगत जानकारी तक पहुंच है, उन्हें पद छोड़ने पर गोपनीय रखने की भी आवश्यकता है।

हम आपको याद दिला दे कि इंटरनेट पूरी तरह से सुरक्षित वातावरण नहीं है, जब आप अपने भौगोलिक स्थान या जानकारी को ट्रैक करने के लिए TeraBox में एम्बेड किए गए तृतीय-पक्ष सामाजिक सॉफ़्टवेयर, ई-मेल, एसएमएस आदि के माध्यम से अन्य उपयोगकर्ताओं के साथ बातचीत करते हैं, तो यह सुनिश्चित नहीं होता है कि तृतीय-पक्ष सॉफ़्टवेयर जानकारी के प्रसारण को पूरी तरह से एन्क्रिप्ट करता है या नही इसलिए अपनी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी की सुरक्षा सुनिश्चित करने पर ध्यान दें।

हम आपको यह समझने के लिए भी कहते हैं कि इंटरनेट उद्योग में प्रौद्योगिकी की सीमाओं और तेजी से विकास के साथ-साथ विभिन्न दुर्भावनापूर्ण हमले के तरीके जो मौजूद हो सकते हैं, भले ही हम सुरक्षा उपायों को मजबूत करने के लिए अपना सर्वश्रेष्ठ प्रयास करें लिकिन हमेशा 100% गारंटी देना असंभव है। कृपया समझें कि हमारे उत्पादों और/या सेवाओं का उपयोग करते समय आप जिन प्रणालियों और संचार नेटवर्क का उपयोग करते हैं, उनमें हमारे नियंत्रण से बाहर के लिंक में सुरक्षा संबंधी समस्याएं हो सकती हैं।

हमारी सुरक्षा प्रबंधन प्रणाली के अनुसार, व्यक्तिगत जानकारी का रिसाव, क्षति या हानि सबसे गंभीर सुरक्षा घटना के रूप में सूचीबद्ध है , एक बार ऐसा होने पर, कंपनी की उच्चतम-स्तरीय आपातकालीन योजना सक्रिय हो जाएगी, और एक संयुक्त आपातकालीन प्रतिक्रिया टीम गठित की जाएगी इससे निपटने के लिए कई विभाग होते है।

हम नेटवर्क सुरक्षा घटनाओं के लिए आपातकालीन योजनाएँ बनाएंगे, कंप्यूटर वायरस, नेटवर्क हमलों और नेटवर्क घुसपैठ जैसे सुरक्षा जोखिमों से निपटने के लिए और नेटवर्क सुरक्षा घटनाओं से बचने के लिए संबंधित अधिकारियों को रिपोर्ट करना आवश्यक है।

व्यक्तिगत जानकारी का रिसाव, क्षति, और नुकसान कंपनी स्तर पर प्रमुख सुरक्षा घटनाएं हैं , हम ऐसी सुरक्षा घटनाओं को होने से रोकने के लिए सुरक्षा अभ्यास करेंगे कार्यकारी समूह के सदस्यों को नियमित रूप से संगठित करने के लिए जिम्मेदार होंगे। एक दुर्भाग्यपूर्ण घटना की स्थिति में, हम सर्वोच्च प्राथमिकता के अनुसार आपातकालीन योजना को सक्रिय करेंगे, एक आपातकालीन प्रतिक्रिया टीम का गठन करेंगे, कारण का पता लगाएंगे और कम से कम समय में नुकसान को कम करेंगे।

दुर्भाग्यपूर्ण व्यक्तिगत सूचना सुरक्षा घटना होने के बाद, कानूनों और विनियमों की आवश्यकताओं के अनुसार, हम आपको तुरंत बुनियादी स्थिति और सुरक्षा घटनाओं के संभावित प्रभाव के बारे में सूचित करेंगे, जिन्हें आप स्वतंत्र रूप से रोक सकते हैं या कम कर सकते हैं , आपके लिए उपचारात्मक उपाय आदि। आपके द्वारा आरक्षित की गई संपर्क विधियों, जैसे ऑन-साइट सूचनाएं, पाठ संदेश सूचनाएं, फोन कॉल और ईमेल के माध्यम से हम आपको तुरंत घटना-संबंधी स्थिति के बारे में सूचित करेंगे , जब एक-एक करके सूचित करना मुश्किल हो, तो हम घोषणा जारी करने के लिए एक उचित और प्रभावी तरीका अपनाएंगे। साथ ही, हम नियामक प्राधिकरणों की आवश्यकताओं के अनुसार व्यक्तिगत सूचना सुरक्षा घटनाओं से निपटने के लिए भी सक्रिय रूप से रिपोर्ट करेंगे। कृपया समझें कि, कानूनी नियम के अनुसार, यदि हम जो उपाय करते हैं, वे प्रभावी ढंग से सूचनाओं के रिसाव, छेड़छाड़ और नुकसान से होने वाले नुकसान से बच सकते हैं, तो हम आपको व्यक्तिगत सूचना सुरक्षा घटना के बारे में सूचित नहीं करने का विकल्प चुन सकते हैं जब तक कि पर्यवेक्षी विभाग को अधिसूचना की आवश्यकता न हो आपसे।

हम GDPR की आवश्यकताओं का उल्लेख करेंगे, प्रकृति, कार्यक्षेत्र, पृष्ठभूमि और डेटा के प्रसंस्करण के उद्देश्य और व्यक्तियों के लिए जोखिमों के आधार पर उपयुक्त तकनीकी सुरक्षा उपायों का चयन करेंगे, और किए गए उपायों की प्रभावशीलता को बनाए रखने के लिए नियमित परीक्षण और मूल्यांकन करें।

जब कोई डेटा लीक होता है, तो हम जल्द से जल्द सूचना लीक से प्रभावित संबंधित लोगों को सूचित करेंगे और 72 घंटों के भीतर हम संबंधित सक्षम प्राधिकारी को रिपोर्ट करेंगे। जब 72 घंटे के भीतर रिपोर्ट नहीं की जाती तो , रिपोर्ट में देरी का कारण बताया जाएगा।

हम डेटा सुरक्षा उद्देश्यों को प्राप्त करने के लिए उपयुक्त तकनीकी और संगठनात्मक उपायों को लागू करते हैं, जैसे डेटा न्यूनीकरण और डेटा प्रोसेसिंग में आवश्यक सुरक्षा उपायों का एकीकरण ताकि डेटा विषयों के अधिकारों की रक्षा की जा सके और डिफ़ॉल्ट रूप से यह सुनिश्चित किया जा सके कि किसी विशिष्ट उद्देश्य के लिए संसाधित डेटा ज़रूरी है।

हम कहाँ आपकी जानकारी स्टोर और प्रोसेस करते हैं

सेवाएँ प्रदान करने में, हम आपकी जानकारी को जापान में संग्रहीत, संसाधित और स्थानांतरित कर सकते हैं और आप अपनी जानकारी प्रदान करने के लिए सहमत हो l आपकी जानकारी उस डिवाइस पर भी स्थानीय रूप से संग्रहीत की जा सकती है जिसका उपयोग आप सेवाओं तक पहुँचने के लिए करते हैं।

कैसे आप नियंत्रण और अपनी जानकारी को पा सकते हैं

प्रासंगिक देशों और क्षेत्रों के कानूनों, विनियमों, मानकों और सामान्य प्रथाओं के अनुसार, हम आपको आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी के संबंध में निम्नलिखित अधिकारों का प्रयोग करने की गारंटी देते हैं , यदि अधिकारों के प्रयोग के बारे में आपके कोई प्रश्न या दावे हैं, तो आप भी [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) के माध्यम से हमसे संपर्क करें । आप अपने TeraBox खाते से अपनी जानकारी देख सकते हैं, बदल सकते हैं, डाउनलोड कर सकते हैं, हटा सकते हैं या साझा कर सकते हैं।

1\. एक्सेस का अधिकार

जब आप अपनी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी के TeraBox के अधिग्रहण, भंडारण, साझाकरण आदि के दायरे या अपनी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को संसाधित करने के उद्देश्य के बारे में जानना चाहते हैं, तो आप प्रासंगिक सामग्री प्राप्त करने के लिए हमसे संपर्क कर सकते हैं।

2\. सुधार और पूरक का अधिकार

जब आप पाते हैं कि हम आपके बारे में जो व्यक्तिगत जानकारी गलत है, तो आपके पास गलत या अधूरी जानकारी को ठीक करने का अधिकार है। अपनी पहचान सत्यापित करने के बाद, आप प्रतिक्रिया और त्रुटि रिपोर्टिंग का उपयोग कर सकते हैं या अपना सुधार सबमिट कर सकते हैं या ऊपर उल्लिखित संपर्क जानकारी प्रकाशित करके हमारे लिए पूरक आवेदन दे सकते हैं। आपका आवेदन प्राप्त होने के बाद, हम आपको जल्द से जल्द प्रतिक्रिया देंगे।

3\. हटाने का अधिकार

निम्नलिखित स्थितियों में है, आप हमसे अपनी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को हटाने का अनुरोध कर सकते हैं:

यदि हम आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को कानूनों और विनियमों या आपके साथ हमारे समझौते के उल्लंघन में संसाधित करते हैं;

यदि हमारे प्रसंस्करण उद्देश्यों को प्राप्त किया गया है, प्राप्त नहीं किया जा सकता है या प्रसंस्करण उद्देश्यों को प्राप्त करने के लिए अब आवश्यक नहीं है;

यदि हम उत्पाद प्रदान करना बंद कर देते हैं या सेवाएं, या भंडारण अवधि समाप्त हो गई है;

यदि आप अपनी सहमति वापस लेते हैं;

कानूनों और प्रशासनिक नियमों द्वारा निर्धारित अन्य परिस्थितियाँ।

आपके द्वारा हमारी सेवा से जानकारी हटाने के बाद, हम बैकअप सिस्टम में संबंधित जानकारी को तुरंत नहीं हटा सकते हैं, लेकिन बैकअप अपडेट होने पर जानकारी को हटा देंगे। कृपया जान लें और समझें कि यदि कानून, प्रशासनिक नियमों द्वारा निर्धारित या इस गोपनीयता नीति में वर्णित प्रतिधारण अवधि समाप्त नहीं हुई है, या यदि व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को हटाना तकनीकी रूप से कठिन है, तो हम आवश्यक सुरक्षा उपायों को संग्रहीत करना और लेना बंद कर देंगे।

4\. सहमति वापस लेना

प्रत्येक व्यावसायिक कार्य को पूरा करने के लिए कुछ बुनियादी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी की आवश्यकता होती है। अतिरिक्त रूप से एकत्र की गई व्यक्तिगत जानकारी के संग्रह और उपयोग के लिए, आप किसी भी समय अपना प्राधिकरण और सहमति दे या वापस ले सकते हैं।

आप डिवाइस सिस्टम में सिस्टम अनुमतियों जैसे एड्रेस बुक, फोटो एल्बम और कैमरा को सीधे बंद कर सकते हैं, सहमति का दायरा बदल सकते हैं या अपना प्राधिकरण वापस ले सकते हैं।

आपके द्वारा अपनी सहमति वापस लेने के बाद, हम आपको आपकी सहमति वापस लेने के अनुरूप सेवाएं प्रदान करने में सक्षम नहीं होंगे, और हम आपकी संबंधित व्यक्तिगत जानकारी का उपयोग नहीं करेंगे। हालाँकि, आपकी सहमति वापस लेने का आपका निर्णय आपकी सहमति के आधार पर व्यक्तिगत जानकारी के पिछले प्रसंस्करण को प्रभावित नहीं करेगा।

5\. रद्द करने का अधिकार

आप पहले पंजीकृत खाते को रद्द कर सकते हैं। आप निम्न पथ से TeraBox पर अपने खाते से लॉग आउट भी कर सकते हैं:

\[खाता प्रोफ़ाइल चित्र\] - \[मेनू\] - \[सेटिंग्स\] - \[सुरक्षा केंद्र\] - \[खाता निरस्तीकरण\]।

एक बार जब आप अपना खाता रद्द कर देते हैं, तो आप TeraBox उत्पादों की सेवाओं का उपयोग नहीं कर पाएंगे, इसलिए कृपया सावधानी से आगे बढ़ें। आपके या अन्य लोगों के वैध अधिकारों और हितों की रक्षा के लिए, हम निर्णय लेंगे कि आपके उपयोग के आधार पर आपके रद्दीकरण अनुरोध का समर्थन करना है या नहीं। उदाहरण के लिए, यदि आपने Premium लाभ का उपभोग नहीं किया है, या आपके खाते में अभी भी डेटा है, तो हम आपके अनुरोध का तुरंत समर्थन नहीं करेंगे। जब तक कानूनों और विनियमों द्वारा अन्यथा निर्धारित नहीं किया जाता है, हम आपका खाता रद्द करने के बाद आपको उत्पाद और सेवाएं प्रदान करना बंद कर देंगे, और आपकी आवश्यकताओं के अनुसार आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को हटा देंगे।

6\. कॉपी और पोर्टेबिलिटी का अधिकार

आपके पास हमारे द्वारा एकत्र की गई आपकी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को कॉपी करने का अधिकार है। कानून और नियम द्वारा निर्धारित शर्तों के तहत, संबंधित सक्षम अधिकारियों द्वारा निर्धारित निर्देशों और शर्तों के अनुपालन में , यदि तकनीकी रूप से संभव हो तो आप हमसे अपनी व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को आपके द्वारा निर्दिष्ट अन्य विषयों में स्थानांतरित करने का अनुरोध भी कर सकते हैं।

जब आप उपर्युक्त व्यक्तिगत सूचना विषय के प्रासंगिक अधिकारों का प्रयोग करते हो और हम यह सुनिश्चित करने के लिए यथाशीघ्र संबंधित तृतीय पक्षों के साथ समन्वय स्थापित करेंगे कि आपके उपरोक्त अधिकार विनियमों, विनियामक आवश्यकताओं और तकनीकी व्यवहार्यता के अनुपालन में प्राप्त किए गए हैं।

जब आपका अनुरोध स्पष्ट रूप से उचित नहीं है या आवश्यक सीमा से अधिक है, विशेष रूप से जब अनुरोध दोहराया जाता है, तो हम:

(a) सूचना, संचार या संबंधित कार्यों को प्रदान करने की प्रशासनिक लागत के संयोजन में उचित शुल्क ले सकते हैं; या

(b) अनुरोध पर कार्रवाई करने के लिए मना कर सकते हैं।

आप अपने द्वारा रखी गई व्यक्तिगत जानकारी को नियंत्रित कर सकते हैं जापानी व्यक्तिगत सूचना संरक्षण अधिनियम ("प्रतिबंधित व्यक्तिगत जानकारी") के अनुसार इसे कैसे एकत्र करे , उपयोग और साझा करे। उदाहरण के लिए, आप कर सकते हैं:

a. आपकी पहचान रखने वाली व्यक्तिगत जानकारी के प्रकटीकरण का अनुरोध करें।

b. जब प्रतिधारित व्यक्तिगत जानकारी की सामग्री जो किसी व्यक्ति की पहचान करती है और सत्य नहीं है, तो प्रतिधारित व्यक्तिगत जानकारी की सामग्री में सुधार और जोड़ने या हटाने का अनुरोध करें।

c. यदि आपकी रखी गई व्यक्तिगत जानकारी हमारे द्वारा अवैध रूप से प्राप्त की जाती है, या हम आपकी रखी गई व्यक्तिगत जानकारी का उपयोग कर रहे हैं, तो कृपया अपनी रखी गई व्यक्तिगत जानकारी का उपयोग तुरंत हटा दें या बंद कर दें।

d. यदि हम अवैध रूप से आपके द्वारा रखी गई व्यक्तिगत जानकारी किसी तीसरे पक्ष को प्रदान करते हैं, तो कृपया तुरंत आपके द्वारा रखी गई व्यक्तिगत जानकारी प्रदान करना बंद कर दें।

बदलाव

Flextech के पुनर्गठन, विलय या अधिग्रहण या हमारी संपत्तियों की बिक्री की स्थिति में, आपकी जानकारी उस लेन-देन के जीवित इकाई, अधिग्रहणकर्ता या उत्तराधिकारी को स्थानांतरित की जा सकती है। हम आपको ऐसे किसी भी लेन-देन के बारे में सूचित करेंगे (उदाहरण के लिए, आपके खाते से जुड़े ईमेल पते पर संदेश द्वारा) और उस घटना में आपके विकल्पों की रूपरेखा तैयार करेंगे।

इस गोपनीयता नीति में समय-समय पर संशोधन किया जा सकता है। हम TeraBox की वेबसाइट पर नवीनतम संस्करण पोस्ट करेंगे। यदि ऐसा कोई संशोधन आपके अधिकारों को वास्तविक रूप से प्रभावित करता है तो हम आपको सूचित करेंगे।

हमें संपर्क करें:

यदि TeraBox और हमारी सेवाओं और गोपनीयता के बारे में आपके कोई प्रश्न या चिंताएं हैं, तो कृपया [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) पर हमसे संपर्क करें।

Kebijakan Privasi

Kebijakan Privasi

Konten informasi yang dikumpulkan dan tujuannya

Pemberian informasi pribadi kepada pihak ketiga

Berbagi dengan pengguna lain

Kami mungkin akan membagikan informasi Anda dengan pihak ketiga

Bagaimana cara kami melindungi dan menyimpan informasi Anda

Di mana kami akan menyimpan dan memproses informasi Anda

Bagaimana cara Anda mengendalikan dan mengakses informasi Anda

{{ $t('termsOfServicePrivacyPolicy.age.title') }}

Perubahan

Hubungi kami:

Kebijakan Privasi

Tanggal rilis: 18 April 2023

Tanggal berlaku: 18 April 2023

Terima kasih telah menggunakan TeraBox! TeraBox disediakan oleh Flextech Inc. ("Flextech" atau "Kami") untuk Anda. Kami berusaha untuk menjaga privasi Anda. Kebijakan Privasi ini menetapkan cara kami mengumpulkan, menyimpan, memproses, membagikan, dan menggunakan informasi Anda saat Anda menggunakan situs web, perangkat lunak, dan layanan ("Layanan") kami.

Kami akan mengumpulkan dan menggunakan informasi pribadi Anda sesuai dengan prinsip legalitas, keadilan, dan kebutuhan. Secara khusus, kami mengumpulkan dan memproses informasi pribadi Anda dengan tujuan menyediakan fitur bisnis yang sesuai untuk Anda. Dalam fitur terkait, jika Anda memberikan informasi pribadi orang lain, harap pastikan bahwa Anda telah memperoleh otorisasi dari subjek yang bersangkutan, dan kami berhak untuk memeriksa sumber sah informasi pribadi tersebut kapan saja.

Kami akan secara ketat mengikuti persyaratan hukum dan peraturan untuk meminta persetujuan Anda secara khusus dalam keadaan tertentu. Selain kebijakan privasi ini, kami juga dapat menjelaskan aturan kami dalam memproses informasi pribadi Anda kepada Anda melalui pemberitahuan di halaman produk, peringatan pop-up, informasi push dan lainnya. Pemrosesan informasi pribadi yang berkaitan dengan fitur bisnis spesifik akan tunduk pada aturan spesifik, dan aturan spesifik memiliki efek yang sama dengan kebijakan privasi ini.

Harap dicatat：Dalam situasi berikut, pengumpulan, penggunaan, pembagian, transfer, dan pengungkapan informasi pribadi kepada publik tidak memerlukan otorisasi dan persetujuan Anda sebelumnya:

Berkaitan langsung dengan keamanan nasional dan keamanan pertahanan negara;

Diperlukan untuk menyimpulkan dan melaksanakan kontrak di mana individu adalah salah satu pihak yang terlibat;

Diperlukan untuk melakukan tugas hukum atau kewajiban hukum;

Diperlukan untuk menanggapi insiden darurat kesehatan masyarakat atau melindungi jiwa, kesehatan, dan keamanan harta benda orang perseorangan dalam keadaan darurat;

Berkaitan langsung dengan investigasi kriminal, penuntutan, persidangan, dan pelaksanaan putusan;

Dengan tujuan untuk melindungi jiwa Anda atau orang lain, harta benda serta hak dan kepentingan hukum yang signifikan lainnya, tetapi sulit untuk mendapatkan persetujuan dari orang tersebut;

Mengumpulkan informasi pribadi yang diungkapkan kepada publik oleh Anda sendiri atau yang telah diungkapkan secara sah dalam lingkup yang wajar sesuai dengan ketentuan hukum dan peraturan;

Mengumpulkan informasi pribadi Anda dari informasi yang diungkapkan secara sah dalam lingkup yang wajar sesuai dengan ketentuan hukum dan peraturan, seperti laporan berita yang sah, pengungkapan informasi pemerintah, dan saluran lainnya;

Memproses informasi pribadi dalam lingkup yang wajar untuk melakukan pelaporan berita, pengawasan opini publik, dan perilaku lain demi kepentingan publik;

Diperlukan oleh lembaga penelitian akademik untuk melakukan statistik atau penelitian akademik berdasarkan kepentingan publik, dan menghilangkan informasi pribadi yang terkandung dalam hasil saat menyediakan hasil penelitian atau deskripsi akademik kepada dunia luar;

Situasi lain yang diatur dalam ketentuan hukum dan peraturan terkait.

Konten informasi yang dikumpulkan dan tujuannya

Tabel berikut mencantumkan jenis informasi yang Anda berikan kepada kami saat menggunakan layanan ini, dan tujuan kami menggunakan informasi tersebut. Kami mengumpulkan dan menggunakan informasi berikut untuk menyediakan, mengoptimalkan, melindungi, dan mempromosikan layanan kami.

| Jenis informasi | Tujuan pengumpulan |
| --- | --- |
| Informasi akun. Kami akan mengumpulkan email, nomor telepon, dan informasi lain yang Anda berikan kepada kami saat Anda melakukan beberapa operasi (seperti mendaftarkan akun) (jika Anda login dengan akun SNS, maka kami akan menerima nama panggilan Anda dan data gambar profil SNS), dan menghubungkan informasi tersebut dengan akun Anda. | Kami dapat menggunakan informasi tersebut untuk mengenali Anda sebagai pemilik akun, dan menjaga akun Anda tetap aman. Kami mungkin akan mengumpulkan informasi tersebut saat Anda login ke akun Anda. |
| Data pengguna. Materi yang Anda simpan di TeraBox, seperti file, dokumen, foto, video, dan audio ("Materi Pengguna"). | Kami mungkin akan menyimpan, memproses, dan mentransmisikan Materi Pengguna dan informasi yang berkaitan dengannya untuk memastikan layanan beroperasi dengan benar, dan memungkinkan Anda untuk berkolaborasi dengan orang lain, dan melakukan pekerjaan di beberapa perangkat dan layanan. Informasi yang berkaitan tersebut mencakup informasi file konfigurasi Anda, ukuran file, tanggal dan waktu unggah serta aktivitas penggunaan. |
| Informasi penggunaan. Informasi tentang cara menggunakan layanan, termasuk operasi yang dilakukan dalam akun, seperti mengedit, melihat, membuat dan memindahkan file atau folder. | Kami dapat menggunakan informasi ini untuk menyediakan, meningkatkan, dan mempromosikan layanan, serta melindungi pengguna TeraBox. |
| Informasi perangkat. Informasi perangkat yang digunakan untuk mengakses layanan, seperti alamat IP, browser, dan informasi perangkat, halaman web yang diakses sebelum mengakses TeraBox, tanda pengenal yang terhubung dengan perangkat dan informasi lokasi yang sesuai dengan pengaturan perangkat. | Kami dapat menggunakan informasi tersebut untuk memperbaiki dan melindungi layanan kami. |
| Cookie. Sepotong teks singkat yang dikirimkan oleh situs web ke browser Anda saat Anda mengaksesTeraBox. Anda dapat menolak cookie dengan mengubah pengaturan browser Anda, tetapi hal ini dapat mempengaruhi fungsi layanan. | Kami mungkin akan menggunakan cookie dan teknologi serupa untuk menyediakan, memperbaiki, melindungi, dan mempromosikan layanan. Cookie memungkinkan kami untuk mengingat nama pengguna Anda, mengetahui penggunaan Anda atas layanan, dan memperbaiki layanan berdasarkan informasi tersebut. Penyedia layanan pihak ketiga yang bekerjasama dengan kami juga dapat menggunakan cookie dan teknologi serupa. |
| Informasi kontak. Anda dapat menggunakan fitur berbagi TeraBox untuk berbagi data dan informasi Anda dengan kontak di buku telepon, nomor ponsel, email (seperti Facebook, Twitter). Informasi dalam buku telepon adalah informasi pribadi yang sensitif. Menolak untuk memberikan informasi tersebut hanya akan membuat Anda tidak dapat menggunakan fitur-fitur yang disebutkan di atas, tetapi tidak akan mempengaruhi Anda untuk menggunakan fitur yang lain dan layanan terkait TeraBox dengan normal. | Anda dapat memilih untuk mengizinkan TeraBox mengakses informasi kontak Anda, untuk memudahkan operasi tertentu, seperti berbagi dan berkolaborasi dengan orang lain untuk memproses data Anda, mengirim pesan dan mengundang orang lain untuk menggunakan layanan TeraBox dengan mengirimkan email. Operasi tersebut mengharuskan Anda untuk mengaktifkan izin akses buku telepon. Kami akan menyimpan informasi tersebut di server kami, agar dapat digunakan oleh Anda. Sebelum berbagi, harap sepenuhnya mempertimbangkan kredibilitas penerima pesan. Sementara itu, kami menyarankan Anda untuk memeriksa pernyataan privasi dari jejaring sosial atau penyedia layanan pihak ketiga, agar dapat memahami cara mereka memproses informasi Anda, untuk memudahkan Anda membuat keputusan yang bijaksana. |
| Papan klip. Ketika Anda mendaftar akun Terabox menggunakan kode undangan seseorang, mengakses tautan file yang dibagikan oleh pengguna lain, menambahkan teman melalui kata sandi, atau memperoleh layanan keanggotaan melalui kode penukaran, kami akan membaca informasi papan klip Anda. | Kami akan mengakses informasi clipboard untuk membantu Anda membuka file yang sesuai dengan tautan, mengidentifikasi pengguna yang sesuai dengan kata sandi dan kode undangan, atau menukarkan layanan keanggotaan untuk Anda. Kami tidak akan pernah membaca clipboard Anda untuk tujuan lain. |

Anda dapat membuat akun TeraBox melalui nomor ponsel, dan Anda dapat melengkapi informasi akun Anda.

Agar dapat memenuhi persyaratan hukum dan peraturan yang diwajibkan, dan yang diperlukan untuk menyediakan produk atau layanan, atau berdasarkan kebutuhan Anda untuk meningkatkan tingkat perlindungan akun, Anda harus memberikan nama asli Anda, nomor dokumen identitas, dan informasi wajah untuk menyelesaikan otentikasi akun saat Anda menggunakan layanan TeraBox tertentu atau saat Anda memiliki kebutuhan selanjutnya. Agar dapat memverifikasi keakuratan dan kelengkapan informasi yang Anda berikan, atau memastikan keamanan akun Anda, kami mungkin akan membandingkan dan memverifikasi informasi nama asli yang Anda berikan kepada TeraBox dengan informasi yang berkaitan dengan Anda yang disimpan oleh lembaga yang diizinkan oleh hukum dan peraturan atau lembaga yang diberi wewenang oleh badan pemerintah.

Informasi tersebut dikumpulkan untuk menyediakan layanan yang andal dan aman serta untuk tujuan komersial yang sah. Kami atau mitra kami akan meminta persetujuan Anda terlebih dahulu sebelum memproses informasi Anda untuk segala tujuan lain.

Anda setuju bahwa kami akan menggunakan teknologi kami sendiri atau pihak yang dipercayakan untuk mengumpulkan dan menggabungkan, mengidentifikasi dan menganalisis, memotret data atau memprosesnya lebih lanjut, dan membentuk berbagai jenis informasi tag dengan perincian yang berbeda (selanjutnya disebut sebagai "Informasi Tag") yang dapat mencerminkan kebiasaan perilaku, hobi, atau status kredit Anda dan karakteristik lainnya, kami akan menggunakan informasi tag untuk melakukan pengambilan keputusan otomatis dalam skenario dan untuk tujuan tertentu, dan mendorong informasi tampilan yang dipersonalisasi dan/atau informasi pemasaran komersial kepada Anda.

Anda berhak untuk menolak layanan teknik pengambilan keputusan otomatis yang diterapkan oleh kami, Anda dapat meminta kami untuk menghentikannya dengan menghubungi kami melalui informasi kontak yang dipublikasikan dalam perjanjian ini atau melalui tombol yang berkaitan di layanan produk. Sementara itu, berdasarkan persyaratan hukum atau peraturan dari negara atau wilayah terkait tentang larangan pengambilan keputusan otomatis, kami juga akan menerapkannya sesuai dengan persyaratan tersebut.

Kami mungkin akan menggunakan Data Akun Anda untuk tujuan pemasaran, dan sesekali mengirimkan informasi tentang produk baru, peningkatan, dan materi pemasaran lainnya dari TeraBox. Anda dapat memilih untuk tidak menerima materi pemasaran kapan saja, caranya adalah dengan mengklik tautan "berhenti berlangganan" dalam email apa pun yang Anda terima.

Pemberian informasi pribadi kepada pihak ketiga

Tanpa mendapat persetujuan Anda terlebih dahulu, kami tidak boleh memberikan informasi pribadi kepada pihak ketiga mana pun, kecuali jika diperlukan dalam kondisi berikut:

(a) Kami harus bekerjasama dengan organisasi pemerintah nasional atau daerah atau agennya untuk melaksanakan tugas atau kewajibannya sesuai dengan hukum dan peraturan yang berlaku. Jika kami harus mendapatkan persetujuan Anda, maka pelaksanaan tersebut mungkin akan dikecualikan;

(b) Ada bahaya yang signifikan terhadap nyawa atau harta benda seseorang;

(c) Sangat diperlukan untuk meningkatkan kesehatan masyarakat atau mendorong perkembangan yang sehat bagi kaum muda;

Untuk pembagian, transfer, atau pengungkapan informasi pribadi Anda dalam situasi yang dikecualikan di atas, kami akan mencatat bukti pemrosesan informasi yang berkaitan, ruang lingkup pemrosesan informasi, informasi penerima dan lainnya, yang secara khusus mencakup konten berikut, dan mematuhi prinsip minimum dan kebutuhan untuk melindungi hak dan kepentingan hukum Anda.

(1) Nama dan informasi kontak terperinci dari pengontrol data dan petugas perlindungan data;

(2) Tujuan pemrosesan data;

(3) Deskripsi jenis subjek data dan jenis data pribadi;

(4) Jenis penerima (termasuk yang berlokasi di negara ketiga atau organisasi internasional) kepada siapa data pribadi telah atau akan diungkapkan;

(5) Catatan transfer data pribadi ke negara ketiga atau organisasi internasional dan catatan tindakan pengamanan yang tepat;

(6) Batas waktu perkiraan untuk menghapus data dengan jenis yang berbeda;

(7) Gambaran umum tentang tindakan keamanan teknis dan organisasi.

Berbagi dengan pengguna lain

Saat Anda menggunakan fitur kolaborasi tim atau berbagi file yang disediakan oleh TeraBox, layanan kami akan menampilkan nama panggilan, perangkat, email, dan informasi penggunaan Anda kepada pengguna lain yang bekerjasama dengan Anda atau memilih untuk berbaginya dengan Anda berdasarkan izin akses Anda. Hal ini akan membantu Anda untuk bersinkronisasi dengan tim yang ingin Anda ikuti, dan membantu pengguna lain untuk berbagi file dan folder dengan Anda.

Kami mungkin akan membagikan informasi Anda dengan pihak ketiga

Kami mungkin akan menggunakan beberapa pihak ketiga terpercaya (seperti dukungan pelanggan dan penyedia layanan TI) untuk membantu kami menyediakan, mengoptimalkan, melindungi, dan mempromosikan layanan kami dengan lebih baik. Pihak ketiga tersebut dapat mengakses informasi Anda dan mewakili kami untuk melakukan tugas, dan kami tetap akan bertanggung jawab atas pemrosesan informasi Anda yang dilakukan oleh pihak ketiga sesuai dengan instruksi kami.

Kami dapat berbagi infrastruktur, sistem, dan teknologi dengan perusahaan afiliasi Flextech untuk menyediakan, memperbaiki, melindungi, dan mempromosikan layanan tersebut. Perusahaan afiliasi tersebut akan menggunakan informasi Anda bersama-sama dengan kami, dan akan menggunakan informasi Anda yang tercantum di bagian "Konten informasi yang dikumpulkan dan tujuannya" untuk tujuan yang dijelaskan di dalamnya. Kami akan bertanggung jawab untuk mengizinkan perusahaan tersebut menggunakan informasi Anda.

Anda dapat memilih untuk terhubung ke akun TeraBox melalui layanan pihak ketiga. Dengan terhubung ke layanan tersebut, Anda mengizinkan pihak ketiga tersebut untuk bertukar informasi yang tercantum di bagian "Konten informasi yang dikumpulkan dan tujuannya" dari Kebijakan Privasi ini dengan kami, sehingga pihak ketiga tersebut dan kami dapat menyediakan, memperbaiki, melindungi, dan memajukan layanan mereka. Dalam kondisi-kondisi ini, penggunaan informasi Anda akan dikuasai oleh kebijakan privasi dan ketentuan layanan yang ditentukan oleh layanan pihak ketiga yang Anda pilih untuk terhubung melaluinya.

Kami akan menetapkan mekanisme output untuk transmisi data lintas batas dengan mengacu pada persyaratan GDPR, dan memperbarui mekanisme lintas batasnya secara tepat waktu berdasarkan persyaratan GDPR. Setiap pemrosesan data pribadi akan memenuhi ketentuan prinsip dasar GDPR, mendapatkan persetujuan dari subjek data yang valid atau memenuhi alasan sah lainnya. Selain itu, mekanisme tambahan akan ditetapkan untuk melindungi data, agar dapat memenuhi persyaratan substantif GDPR terhadap pemrosesan data.

Bagaimana cara kami melindungi dan menyimpan informasi Anda

Kami memiliki tim yang berdedikasi untuk memastikan informasi Anda tetap aman dan menguji kerentanan. Selain autentikasi dua faktor, dilarang enkripsi file dan peringatan yang dikeluarkan saat perangkat dan aplikasi baru terhubung ke akun Anda, kami juga akan terus bekerja keras untuk menjaga keamanan informasi Anda. Kami menerapkan teknologi otomatisasi untuk mendeteksi apa yang mungkin akan merusak layanan kami, penyalahgunaan dan konten Anda atau pengguna lain.

Saat Anda mendaftarkan akun TeraBox, kami akan menyimpan informasi yang Anda simpan di layanan kami selama akun Anda masih aktif atau kami perlu menyediakan layanan untuk Anda. Jika ingin menghapus akun Anda, harap kirim email ke [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) untuk menghapus informasi Anda, kami akan menyelesaikannya dalam waktu 30 hari setelah permintaan Anda diterima; namun, jika: (1) kami belum memverifikasi identitas Anda sebagai pengguna, kami tidak akan menghapus informasi akun Anda; (2) mungkin ada penundaan jika menghapus server dan penyimpanan cadangan kami, (3) jika perlu, kami dapat menyimpan informasi tersebut untuk mematuhi kewajiban hukum kami, menyelesaikan perselisihan, atau menegakkan hak kami berdasarkan kontrak.

Kami akan menyimpan informasi pribadi Anda dalam jangka waktu yang diperlukan untuk menyediakan layanan. Namun, jika hukum dan peraturan menetapkan sebaliknya tentang batas waktu penyimpanan, Anda setuju untuk menyimpannya dalam jangka waktu yang lebih lama, memastikan keamanan dan kualitas layanan, mencapai tujuan menyelesaikan perselisihan, hal yang sulit tercapai secara teknis dan lainnya, kami akan memperpanjang batas waktu penyimpanan sesuai dengan hukum, kesepakatan, atau dalam rentang yang wajar setelah berakhirnya batas waktu penyimpanan tersebut.

Setelah berakhirnya batas waktu penyimpanan, kami akan menghapus informasi pribadi Anda atau menganonimkannya sesuai dengan ketentuan hukum.

Kami akan mengumpulkan, menggunakan, menyimpan, dan mengirim informasi pengguna berdasarkan prinsip "minimisasi", dan memberitahukan tujuan dan ruang lingkup penggunaan informasi terkait kepada Anda melalui perjanjian pengguna dan kebijakan privasi, serta aturan terkait, jendela pop-up, pemberitahuan dan lainnya.

Kami sangat mementingkan keamanan informasi. Kami telah membentuk tim khusus untuk bertanggung jawab atas penelitian, pengembangan, dan penerapan berbagai teknologi, prosedur keamanan dan lainnya. Kami akan melakukan pemeriksaan latar belakang keamanan terhadap penanggung jawab manajemen keamanan dan personel yang menjabat di posisi keamanan penting, kami telah menetapkan sistem manajemen keamanan informasi, mekanisme penanganan insiden keamanan internal yang baik, dan lainnya. Kami akan mengambil tindakan keamanan dan sarana teknis yang sesuai dengan standar industri untuk menyimpan dan melindungi informasi pribadi Anda, agar dapat mencegah informasi Anda dari kehilangan, akses yang tidak sah, pengungkapan publik, penggunaan, perusakan, kehilangan atau kebocoran. Kami akan mengambil semua tindakan yang wajar dan layak untuk melindungi informasi pribadi Anda. Kami akan menggunakan teknologi enkripsi untuk memastikan kerahasiaan data; Kami akan menggunakan mekanisme perlindungan terpercaya untuk mencegah data dari serangan jahat.

Kami akan memberikan pelatihan kesadaran keamanan data serta pelatihan dan penilaian kapabilitas keamanan untuk karyawan, agar dapat meningkatkan kesadaran karyawan akan pentingnya melindungi informasi pribadi. Kami akan melakukan autentikasi identitas dan kontrol akses untuk karyawan yang menangani informasi pribadi, dan akan menandatangani perjanjian kerahasiaan dengan karyawan dan mitra yang memiliki akses ke informasi pribadi Anda, untuk memperjelas tanggung jawab pekerjaan dan kode etik, serta memastikan bahwa hanya personel yang berwenang dapat mengakses informasi pribadi. Jika terdapat perilaku yang melanggar perjanjian kerahasiaan, hubungan kerja sama dengan perusahaan akan segera dihentikan, dan akan dituntut untuk tanggung jawab hukum yang berkaitan, dan persyaratan kerahasiaan juga berlaku untuk personel yang memiliki akses ke informasi pribadi saat berhenti kerja.

Kami mengingatkan Anda bahwa Internet bukanlah lingkungan yang benar-benar aman. Saat Anda berinteraksi dengan pengguna lain tentang lokasi geografis atau informasi pelacakan Anda melalui perangkat lunak media sosial pihak ketiga, email, SMS dan lainnya yang disematkan di TeraBox, tidak pasti apakah perangkat lunak pihak ketiga sepenuhnya mengenkripsi informasi yang ditransmisikan, berhati-hatilah untuk memastikan keamanan informasi pribadi Anda.

Kami juga meminta Anda untuk memahami bahwa dalam industri Internet, karena keterbatasan dan pesatnya perkembangan teknologi, serta berbagai kemungkinan serangan jahat, meskipun kami berusaha sebaik mungkin untuk meningkatkan tindakan keamanan, kami juga tidak dapat selalu menjamin 100% keamanan informasi. Harap dipahami sistem dan jaringan komunikasi yang Anda gunakan untuk menggunakan produk dan/atau layanan kami mungkin akan menyebabkan masalah keamanan di sesi lain yang berada di luar kendali kami.

Menurut sistem manajemen keamanan kami, insiden kebocoran, kerusakan, atau kehilangan informasi pribadi termasuk insiden keamanan paling serius. Jika insiden tersebut terjadi, maka rencana darurat tingkat tertinggi perusahaan akan diaktifkan, dan akan ditangani oleh tim tanggap darurat gabungan yang terbentuk dari berbagai departemen.

Kami akan merumuskan rencana darurat untuk insiden keamanan jaringan, agar dapat menangani kerentanan sistem, virus komputer, serangan jaringan, intrusi jaringan dan risiko keamanan lainnya secara tepat waktu. Jika terjadi insiden yang membahayakan keamanan jaringan, kami akan segera mengaktifkan rencana darurat, mengambil tindakan perbaikan yang sesuai, dan melaporkan kepada departemen kompeten yang berkaitan sesuai dengan ketentuan.

Kebocoran, kerusakan, dan kehilangan informasi pribadi merupakan insiden keamanan serius di tingkat perusahaan. Kami akan bertanggung jawab untuk mengorganisir anggota tim kerja untuk melakukan latihan rencana keamanan secara rutin, agar dapat mencegah insiden keamanan tersebut terjadi. Jika terjadi kejadian yang merugikan, kami akan mengaktifkan rencana darurat sesuai dengan prioritas tertinggi, dan membentuk tim tanggap darurat untuk melacak penyebabnya dan mengurangi kerugian dalam waktu sesingkat mungkin.

Setelah terjadinya insiden keamanan informasi pribadi yang merugikan, kami akan segera memberitahu Anda tentang situasi dasar dan kemungkinan dampak insiden keamanan, tindakan penanganan yang telah diambil atau yang akan kami ambil, saranan untuk risiko yang dapat Anda cegah dan kurangi secara mandiri, dan tindakan perbaikan untuk Anda sesuai dengan persyaratan hukum dan peraturan. Kami akan segera memberitahu Anda tentang situasi kejadian yang berkaitan melalui pemberitahuan situs web, pemberitahuan SMS, telepon, email, dan metode kontak lain yang telah Anda berikan. Jika sulit untuk memberitahukannya satu per satu, kami akan mengambil metode yang wajar dan efektif untuk mempublikasikan pengumuman. Sementara itu, kami juga akan berinisiatif untuk melaporkan situasi penanganan insiden keamanan informasi pribadi sesuai dengan persyaratan departemen pengawasan. Harap dipahami bahwa, sesuai dengan ketentuan hukum dan peraturan, jika tindakan yang kami ambil dapat secara efektif menghindari kerugian yang timbul dari kebocoran, perusakan dan kehilangan informasi, kami dapat memilih untuk tidak memberitahukan insiden keamanan informasi pribadi tersebut kepada Anda, kecuali departemen pengawasan meminta kami untuk memberitahu Anda.

Kami akan memilih tindakan perlindungan keamanan teknis yang sesuai berdasarkan sifat, ruang lingkup, latar belakang, serta tujuan pemrosesan data dan risiko terhadap individu dengan mengacu pada persyaratan GDPR, dan melakukan pengujian dan evaluasi rutin terhadap tindakan tersebut untuk menjaga efektivitas tindakan yang diambil.

Saat terjadi kebocoran data, kami akan memberitahu grup pengguna yang terkena dampak kebocoran informasi tersebut sesegera mungkin, dan kami akan melaporkannya kepada departemen kompeten yang terkait dalam waktu 72 jam. Jika tidak dapat melaporkannya dalam waktu 72 jam, maka kami akan menjelaskan penyebab keterlambatan penyampaian laporan.

Kami mengambil tindakan teknis dan organisasi yang sesuai untuk mencapai tujuan perlindungan data, seperti minimisasi data dan menggabungkan tindakan pengamanan yang diperlukan ke dalam proses pemrosesan data untuk melindungi setiap hak subjek data. Secara default, perlu memastikan data yang diproses untuk tujuan tertentu.

Di mana kami akan menyimpan dan memproses informasi Anda

Saat menyediakan layanan, informasi Anda mungkin akan disimpan, diproses, dan ditransfer di Jepang, dan Anda setuju untuk memberikan informasi Anda. Informasi Anda juga dapat disimpan di perangkat penyimpanan lokal yang digunakan untuk mengakses layanan.

Bagaimana cara Anda mengendalikan dan mengakses informasi Anda

Sesuai dengan hukum, peraturan, standar, dan praktik yang berlaku di negara dan wilayah terkait, kami menjamin Anda dapat menggunakan hak-hak berikut sehubungan dengan informasi pribadi Anda. Jika Anda memiliki pertanyaan atau klaim tentang penggunaan hak, Anda juga dapat menghubungi kami melalui [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com). Anda dapat melihat, mengubah, mengunduh, menghapus, atau berbagi informasi Anda dari akun TeraBox.

1.Hak pemeriksaan

Jika Anda ingin mengetahui ruang lingkup informasi pribadi Anda yang diperoleh, disimpan, dibagi oleh TeraBox atau tujuan memproses informasi pribadi Anda, Anda dapat menghubungi kami untuk memperoleh informasi terkait.

2.Hak koreksi dan penambahan

Jika Anda menemukan bahwa terdapat kesalahan dalam informasi pribadi Anda yang diproses oleh kami, Anda berhak untuk mengoreksi informasi yang salah atau tidak lengkap. Setelah identitas Anda diverifikasi, Anda dapat mengirim permohonan koreksi atau penambahan Anda kepada kami melalui umpan balik dan pelaporan kesalahan atau informasi kontak yang dipublikasikan sebelumnya. Kami akan memberikan umpan balik kepada Anda sesegera mungkin setelah kami menerima permohonan Anda.

3\. Hak penghapusan

Dalam situasi berikut, Anda dapat mengajukan permintaan kepada kami untuk menghapus informasi pribadi:

Jika kami melanggar hukum dan peraturan atau perjanjian kami dengan Anda untuk memproses informasi pribadi Anda;

Jika tujuan pemrosesan kami telah tercapai, tidak dapat dicapai, atau tidak diperlukan lagi untuk mencapai tujuan pemrosesan tersebut;

Jika kami berhenti menyediakan produk atau layanan, atau batas waktu penyimpanan telah berakhir; Jika Anda mencabut persetujuan Anda;

Situasi lain yang ditetapkan oleh hukum dan peraturan administrasi.

Saat Anda menghapus informasi dari layanan kami, kami mungkin tidak akan segera menghapus informasi terkait dalam sistem pencadangan, tetapi kami akan menghapus informasi tersebut saat pencadangan diperbarui. Harap ketahui dan pahami bahwa jika batas waktu penyimpanan yang ditentukan oleh hukum dan peraturan administrasi atau dijelaskan dalam kebijakan privasi ini belum berakhir, atau jika sulit untuk menghapus informasi pribadi di bidang teknis, kami akan menghentikan tindakan pemrosesan selain penyimpanan dan tindakan perlindungan keamanan yang diperlukan.

4\. Penabutan persetujuan

Setiap fitur bisnis memerlukan beberapa informasi pribadi dasar untuk menyelesaikannya. Untuk pengumpulan dan penggunaan informasi pribadi tambahan yang dikumpulkan, Anda dapat memberikan atau mencabut otorisasi dan persetujuan Anda kapan saja.

Anda dapat langsung menonaktifkan izin sistem seperti buku telepon, album, dan kamera di sistem perangkat, mengubah ruang lingkup persetujuan atau mencabut otorisasi Anda.

Setelah Anda mencabut persetujuan Anda, kami tidak dapat menyediakan layanan yang terkait dengan persetujuan yang dicabut Anda, dan juga tidak akan menggunakan informasi pribadi terkait Anda. Namun, keputusan Anda untuk mencabut persetujuan Anda tidak akan mempengaruhi informasi pribadi yang diproses sebelumnya berdasarkan persetujuan Anda.

5.Hak penghapusan akun

Anda dapat menghapus akun yang telah didaftarkan sebelumnya. Anda juga dapat menghapus akun Anda di TeraBox dengan cara berikut:

\[Avatar Akun\] - \[Menu\] - \[Pengaturan\] - \[Pusat Keamanan\] - \[Penghapusan Akun\].

Setelah Anda menghapus akun, Anda tidak akan dapat menggunakan layanan produk TeraBox, jadi lanjutkan operasi ini dengan cermat. Untuk melindungi hak dan kepentingan sah Anda atau orang lain, kami akan menilai apakah permintaan penghapusan Anda dapat disetujui berdasarkan kondisi penggunaan Anda. Misalnya, jika Anda memiliki manfaat Premium yang belum digunakan atau Anda masih memiliki data di akun Anda, maka kami tidak akan segera menyetujui permintaan Anda. Kecuali ditentukan lain oleh hukum dan peraturan, kami akan berhenti menyediakan produk dan layanan kepada Anda setelah akun Anda terhapus, dan menghapus informasi pribadi Anda berdasarkan permintaan Anda.

6\. Hak penyalinan dan portabilitas

Anda berhak untuk menyalin informasi pribadi Anda yang kami kumpulkan. Berdasarkan syarat-syarat yang ditentukan oleh hukum dan peraturan, dan sesuai dengan arahan dan syarat-syarat yang ditetapkan oleh departemen kompeten yang terkait, jika memungkinkan secara teknis, Anda juga dapat meminta kami untuk mentransfer informasi pribadi Anda ke subjek lain yang Anda tentukan.

Saat Anda menggunakan hak yang berkaitan dengan subjek informasi pribadi di atas, kami juga akan menyinkronkan dengan pihak ketiga yang berkaitan sesegera mungkin untuk memastikan bahwa hak Anda di atas dapat diwujudkan sesuai dengan peraturan hukum, persyaratan pengawasan, dan kelayakan teknis.

Ketika permintaan Anda secara jelas tidak masuk akal atau melebihi batas yang diperlukan, terutama saat permintaan tersebut berulang-ulang, kami dapat:

(a) membebankan biaya yang wajar sehubungan dengan biaya administrasi untuk menyediakan informasi, komunikasi, atau tindakan terkait; atau

(b) menolak untuk melakukan tindakan terhadap permintaan tersebut.

Anda dapat mengendalikan informasi pribadi yang Anda simpan dan cara pengumpulan, penggunaan, dan pembagian informasi tersebut sesuai dengan Undang-Undang Perlindungan Informasi Pribadi Jepang ("Informasi Pribadi yang Disimpan"). Misalnya, Anda dapat:

a. Meminta untuk mengungkapkan informasi pribadi yang telah disimpan dan dapat mengidentifikasi Anda.

b. Meminta untuk memperbaiki, menambah atau menghapus konten informasi pribadi yang telah disimpan, apabila konten informasi pribadi yang telah disimpan dan dapat mengidentifikasi status tidak benar.

c. Segera menghapus atau berhenti menggunakan informasi pribadi yang Anda simpan, jika kami memperoleh informasi pribadi yang Anda simpan secara ilegal, atau kami sedang menggunakan informasi pribadi yang Anda simpan.

d. Segera berhenti memberikan informasi pribadi yang Anda simpan, jika kami memberikan informasi pribadi yang Anda simpan kepada pihak ketiga secara ilegal.

Perubahan

Jika terjadi reorganisasi, merger, atau akuisisi Flextech atau aset kami dijual, maka informasi Anda mungkin akan ditransfer ke entitas yang masih bertahan, pihak pengakuisisi, atau penerus yang melakukan transaksi tersebut. Kami akan memberitahukan transaksi semacam itu (misalnya, mengirim pesan ke alamat email yang berhubungan dengan akun Anda), dan menguraikan pilihan Anda dalam peristiwa tersebut.

Kebijakan Privasi ini mungkin akan direvisi dari waktu ke waktu. Kami akan mempublikasikan versi terbaru di situs web TeraBox. Jika revisi tersebut secara signifikan mempengaruhi hak Anda, maka kami akan memberitahukan Anda.

Hubungi kami:

Jika Anda memiliki pertanyaan atau kekhawatiran tentang TeraBox, layanan kami dan hak privasi, harap hubungi kami melalui [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com).

Политика конфиденциальности TeraBox

Политика конфиденциальности TeraBox

Содержание и цели сбора данных

Предоставление личных данных третьим сторонам

Обмен информацией с другими пользователями

Мы можем передавать для общего доступа Ваши данные третьим сторонам

Каким образом мы защищаем и храним Ваши данные

Где мы храним и обрабатываем Ваши данные

Каким образом Вы управляете Вашими данными и получаете к ним доступ

{{ $t('termsOfServicePrivacyPolicy.age.title') }}

Внесение изменений

Связаться с нами:

Политика конфиденциальности TeraBox

Дата опубликования: 18 апреля 2023 года

Дата вступления в действие: 18 апреля 2023 года

Благодарим Вас за использование TeraBox! TeraBox предоставляется Вам компанией Flextech Inc. (далее "Flextech" или "мы"). Мы стремимся защищать вашу конфиденциальность. Данная политика конфиденциальности определяет, как мы собираем, храним, обрабатываем, передаем и используем вашу информацию, когда вы пользуетесь нашим веб-сайтом, программным обеспечением и услугами (далее "услуги").

Мы будем руководствоваться принципами законности, правомерности и необходимости при сборе и использовании вашей личной информации. В частности, мы собираем и обрабатываем вашу личную информацию для предоставления вам соответствующих операционных функций. В соответствующей функции, если вы предоставляете личную информацию других лиц, пожалуйста, убедитесь, что вы получили разрешение соответствующего субъекта, при этом мы оставляем за собой право проверить законный источник такой личной информации в любое время.

Мы будем запрашивать ваше отдельное согласие при определенных обстоятельствах в строгом соответствии с требованиями законов и нормативных актов. В дополнение к настоящей политике конфиденциальности мы также можем разъяснить наши правила обработки вашей личной информации с помощью уведомлений на странице продукта, всплывающих подсказок, информационных сообщений и другими способами. Особые правила обработки личной информации, соответствующие конкретным операционным функциям, будут иметь преимущественную силу, при этом конкретные правила имеют одинаковую силу, что и настоящая политика конфиденциальности.

Пожалуйста, обратите внимание, что в следующих случаях сбор, использование, совместное использование, передача и публичное раскрытие личной информации не требуют вашего предварительного разрешения:

непосредственная связь с государственной безопасностью и безопасностью национальной обороны;

необходимость для заключения и исполнения контракта, стороной которого является физическое лицо;

необходимость для выполнения юридических обязанностей или поручительств;

необходимость для реагирования на чрезвычайные ситуации в области общественного здравоохранения или защиты жизни, здоровья и имущественной безопасности физических лиц в чрезвычайных ситуациях;

непосредственная связь с уголовным расследованием, судебным преследованием, судебным разбирательством и исполнением судебных решений;

необходимо в целях защиты вашей или сторонней личной жизни, собственности и других основных законных прав и интересов, но имеется трудность получения вашего согласия;

сбор вашей личной информации, раскрытой общественности, или другой раскрытой по закону личной информации в разумных пределах в соответствии с законами и нормативными актами;

сбор вашей личной информации из юридически раскрытой информации в разумных пределах в соответствии с положениями законов и нормативных актов, таких как юридические новостные репортажи, раскрытие правительственной информации и другие каналы;

осуществление новостных репортажей, наблюдение за общественным мнением и другие формы поведения в общественных интересах, а также обработка личной информации в рациональных пределах;

академическим исследовательским учреждениям необходима информация для проведения статистики или академических исследований, основанных на общественных интересах, и проведения деидентификации личной информации, содержащейся в результатах, при предоставлении академических исследований или описанных результатов;

другие обстоятельства, предусмотренные соответствующими законами и нормативными актами.

Содержание и цели сбора данных

В таблице ниже перечислены типы информации, которую вы предоставляете нам при использовании этих сервисов, а также цели, для которых мы можем использовать такую информацию. Мы собираем и используем следующую информацию для предоставления, оптимизации, защиты и продвижения наших услуг.

| Тип информации | Цели сбора |
| --- | --- |
| Сведения об учетной записи. Мы можем собирать данные, предоставляемые Вами при выполнении некоторых операций (например, при регистрации учетной записи), такие как Ваш адрес электронной почты, номер телефона и т.д. (если Вы входите в систему с помощью учетной записи SNS, в таком случае мы получаем Ваш ник и данные изображения учетной записи SNS), также мы привязываем эти данные к Вашей учетной записи. | Мы можем использовать данную информацию, чтобы идентифицировать вас как владельца вашего аккаунта и защитить ваш аккаунт. Мы можем собирать данную информацию, когда вы входите в свой аккаунт. |
| Пользовательские данные. Материалы, которые вы храните в TeraBox, такие как файлы, документы, фотографии, видео и аудио ("Пользовательские материалы"). | Мы можем хранить, обрабатывать и передавать пользовательские материалы и связанную с ними информацию для обеспечения надлежащей работы сервиса, а также для того, чтобы позволить вам сотрудничать с другими пользователями и работать на нескольких устройствах и сервисах. Данная информация включает информацию о вашем профиле, размер файлов, дату и время загрузки, а также действия по использованию. |
| Информация об использовании. Информация об использовании услуг, включая действия, выполняемые в аккаунте, такие как редактирование, просмотр, создание и перемещение файлов или папок. | Мы можем использовать эту информацию для предоставления, улучшения и продвижения услуг и защиты пользователей TeraBox. |
| Сведения об устройстве. Сведения об устройстве, используемом для доступа к услугам, например, IP адрес, сведения о браузерах и устройстве, о посещенных до посещения приложения TeraBox веб-страницах, об идентификаторе устройства, а также данные о местоположении в зависимости от настроек устройства. | Мы можем использовать эти данные для улучшения и защиты наших услуг. |
| Cookies. Короткий фрагмент текста, отправляемый веб-сайтом в ваш браузер, когда вы посещаете TeraBox. Вы можете настроить свой браузер так, чтобы он не принимал файлы cookies, однако это может повлиять на функциональность сервиса. | Мы можем использовать файлы cookies и аналогичные технологии для предоставления, улучшения, защиты и продвижения услуг. Файлы cookies позволяют нам запоминать ваше имя пользователя, понимать, как вы пользуетесь сервисом, а также улучшать сервис на основе этой информации. Сторонние поставщики услуг, работающие с нами, также могут использовать файлы cookies и аналогичные технологии. |
| Контактная информация. Вы можете использовать функцию общего доступа TeraBox, чтобы поделиться своими данными и информацией с контактами, номерами мобильных телефонов, адресами эл. почты (такими как Facebook, Twitter) в телефонной адресной книге. Информация из адресной книги представляет собой личную конфиденциальную информацию. Отказ предоставить эту информацию только лишит вас возможности использовать вышеуказанные функции, но не повлияет на ваше нормальное использование других функций TeraBox и связанных с ними сервисов. | Вы можете разрешить TeraBox доступ к вашей контактной информации для облегчения определенных операций, таких как обмен вашими данными и сотрудничество с другими для обработки ваших данных, отправка сообщений и приглашение других пользователей воспользоваться услугами TeraBox путем отправки электронной почты. Данная операция требует, чтобы вы включили разрешения адресной книги. Мы будем хранить эту информацию на нашем сервере для вашего использования. Прежде чем обмениваться информацией, пожалуйста, полностью оцените надежность получателя сообщения. В то же время мы рекомендуем вам ознакомиться с заявлением о конфиденциальности социальных сетей или сторонних поставщиков услуг, чтобы понять, как они обрабатывают вашу информацию, и принять разумное решение. |
| Буфер обмена. Когда вы регистрируетесь в аккаунте Terabox, используя пригласительный код другого человека, получаете доступ к ссылкам на файлы, совместно используемым другими пользователями, добавляете друзей по паролю или получаете членство через коды обмена, мы будем читать информацию из вашего буфера обмена. | Мы будем получать доступ к информации буфера обмена, чтобы помочь вам открыть файл, соответствующий ссылке, идентифицировать пользователя по паролю и пригласительному коду, или обменять для вас услуги по членству. Мы никогда не будем читать ваш буфер обмена в других целях. |

Вы можете создать аккаунт TeraBox с помощью своего номера мобильного телефона, вы также можете улучшить информацию о своем аккаунте.

В целях удовлетворения обязательных требований законов и нормативных актов, необходимых для предоставления продуктов или услуг, или исходя из вашей потребности повысить уровень защиты аккаунта, когда вы пользуетесь определенными услугами TeraBox или когда у вас есть дополнительные потребности, вам необходимо предоставить свои настоящие ФИО, номер удостоверения личности и информацию о лице для полной аутентификации аккаунта. В целях проверки точности и полноты предоставленной вами информации или обеспечения безопасности вашего аккаунта, мы можем сравнить информацию о реальных ФИО, которую вы предоставили TeraBox, с вашей соответствующей информацией, сохраненной учреждениями, разрешенными законами и нормативными актами или уполномоченными государственными учреждениями.

Вышеуказанная информация собирается для надежного и безопасного предоставления услуг и законных коммерческих целей. Мы или наши партнеры будем запрашивать ваше предварительное согласие, прежде чем использовать вашу информацию для каких-либо иных целей.

Вы соглашаетесь с тем, что мы будем использовать нашу собственную технологию или технологию доверенной стороны для сбора и интеграции, идентификации и анализа, изображения или дальнейшей обработки личной информации, которую вы активно или пассивно предоставляете в сервисе, и формирования информации о ярлыке (далее именуемой "информация о тегах"), которая отражает ваши привычки поведения, хобби или статус доверия и другие характеристики различных типов и различной степени детализации, мы будем использовать информацию о тегах в определенных сценариях и целях для принятия автоматических решений и предоставления вам персонализированной информации о показе и/ или маркетинговой информации для операций.

Вы имеете право отказаться от наших автоматизированных технических услуг по принятию решений, вы можете связаться с нами или через соответствующие переключатели в обслуживании продукции, чтобы попросить нас прекратить работу. В то же время, в соответствии с государственными или региональными нормативными актами или нормативными требованиями по запрещению принятия автоматизированных решений, мы будем осуществлять деятельность согласно предъявленным требованиям.

Мы можем использовать данные вашего аккаунта в маркетинговых целях и периодически отправлять вам информацию о новых продуктах, обновлениях и других маркетинговых материалах TeraBox. Вы всегда можете отказаться от получения маркетинговых материалов, щелкнув ссылку "Отписаться" в любом полученном вами электронном письме.

Предоставление личных данных третьим сторонам

Без получения вашего предварительного согласия мы не будем предоставлять информацию личного характера какой-либо третьей стороне, кроме как по причине:

(а) Мы обязуемся сотрудничать с национальными или региональными правительственными организациями или их представителями, согласно применимому праву и законодательным и нормативным актам выполнять свои функции и обязательства. Выполнение такого рода может быть исключено, если требуется получение Вашего согласия;

(b) В случае наличия серьезного риска, угрожающего чьей-либо жизни или имуществу;

(c) Имеется особая необходимость в усовершенствовании общественного здравоохранения или стимулировании здорового развития молодежи;

Для обмена, передачи или раскрытия вашей личной информации при вышеуказанных исключительных обстоятельствах мы запишем основание для обработки соответствующей информации, объем обработки информации, информацию о получателе и т. д., включая нижеследующее содержание, и будем следовать минимальному и необходимому принципу для защиты ваших законных прав и интересов.

(1) ФИО и контактные данные контролера данных и сотрудника по защите данных;

(2) Цель обработки данных;

(3) Описание типа субъекта данных и типа персональных данных;

(4) Тип получателей (включая тех, кто находится в третьей стране или международной организации), которым были или будут раскрыты персональные данные;

(5) Записи о передачи персональных данных третьим странам или международным организациям и записей о соответствующих мерах предосторожности;

(6) Удаление расчетных периодов для различных типов данных;

(7) Общее описание технических и организационных мер безопасности.

Обмен информацией с другими пользователями

При использовании функции совместной работы в команде или обмена файлами, предоставляемую TeraBox, наш сервис будет отображать ваш никнейм, устройство, адрес эл. почты и информацию об использовании другим пользователям, которые работают с вами или решают поделиться с вами в соответствии с вашим разрешением. Это поможет вам синхронизироваться с командой, к которой вы хотите присоединиться, а также поможет другим пользователям обмениваться с вами файлами и папками.

Мы можем передавать для общего доступа Ваши данные третьим сторонам

Мы можем использовать некоторых доверенных третьих лиц (таких как служба поддержки клиентов и поставщики ИТ-услуг) для помощи в лучшем предоставлении, оптимизации, защите и продвижении наших услуг. Эти третьи лица могут получать доступ к вашей информации и выполнять задачи от нашего имени. При этом, мы по-прежнему будем нести ответственность за процесс обработки вашей информации в соответствии с нашими инструкциями.

Мы можем делиться инфраструктурой, системами и технологиями с аффилированными компаниями Flextech для предоставления, улучшения, защиты и продвижения вышеупомянутых услуг. Данные аффилированные компании будут использовать вашу информацию вместе с нами, а также будут использовать информацию, указанную вами в разделе "Содержание и цель сбора информации", для целей, описанных в нем. Мы будем нести ответственность за предоставление вашей информации этим компаниям.

Вы можете подключиться к своему аккаунту TeraBox через сторонний сервис. При подключении к таким сервисам, вы позволяете этим третьим лицам и нам обмениваться информацией, указанной в разделе "Содержание и цель сбора информации" настоящей политики конфиденциальности, чтобы эти третьи стороны и мы могли предоставлять, улучшать, защищать и продвигать свои услуги. В таких случаях использование вашей информации будет регулироваться политикой конфиденциальности и условиями предоставления услуг, разработанными сторонним сервисом, через который вы решите подключиться.

Мы будем ссылаться на требования GDPR для создания экспортного механизма для трансграничной передачи данных и своевременно обновлять его трансграничный механизм на основе требований GDPR. Любая обработка персональных данных будет соответствовать положениям основных принципов GDPR с получением согласия действующего субъекта данных или соответствием другим законным причинам. Помимо этого, будут созданы дополнительные механизмы для защиты данных в соответствии с основными требованиями GDPR касательно обработки данных.

Каким образом мы защищаем и храним Ваши данные

У нас есть команда, занимающаяся сохранением вашей информации в безопасности и ее тестированием на наличие уязвимостей. В дополнение к двойной аутентификации, отключению шифрования файлов и оповещениям, когда новые устройства и приложения подключаются к вашему аккаунту, мы продолжим работать над обеспечением безопасности вашей информации. Мы внедряем автоматизированные технологии для обнаружения злоупотреблений и контента, которые могут нанести вред нашим сервисам, вам или другим пользователям.

При регистрации аккаунта TeraBox, до тех пор, пока ваш аккаунт существует или нам необходимо предоставлять вам услуги, мы будем хранить информацию, которую вы сохранили на наших сервисах. Если вы хотите удалить свой аккаунт, пожалуйста, отправьте электронное письмо с просьбой удалить вашу информацию на адрес [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com), при этом мы выполним ваш запрос в течение 30 дней после получения вашего эл. письма; однако: (1) мы не будем удалять информацию вашего аккаунта до подтверждения вашей личности пользователя; (2) удаление наших серверов и резервное хранилище может быть отложено, (3) при необходимости мы можем сохранить эту информацию для выполнения наших юридических обязательств, разрешения споров или обеспечения соблюдения наших прав по контракту.

Мы будем сохранять ваши личные данные в течение срока, необходимого для оказания услуг, но если законами и нормативными актами установлен иной срок хранения, вы согласны сохранить на более длительный срок, обеспечить безопасность и качество услуг, достичь цели разрешения споров, технически трудно выполнить и т.д., мы будем продлевать срок хранения по закону, по соглашению или в разумных пределах после истечения вышеуказанного срока хранения информации.

По истечении срока хранения мы удалим ваши личные данные или проведем анонимную обработку в соответствии с законодательством, мы будем собирать, использовать, хранить и передавать информацию пользователей в соответствии с принципом «минимального вмешательства» и будем информировать вас о цели и объеме использования соответствующей информации с помощью пользовательского соглашения и политики конфиденциальности, а также соответствующих правил, всплывающих окон, уведомлений и т.д.

Мы придаем большое значение информационной безопасности. Мы учредили специальную команду, которая будет отвечать за исследования, разработку и применение различных технологий и процедур безопасности. Мы будем тщательно рассматривать биографию руководителей служб безопасности и ключевых сотрудников службы безопасности. Мы создали надежную систему управления информационной безопасностью и механизм обработки инцидентов внутренней безопасности. Наряду с этим, мы примем соответствующие меры безопасности и технические средства, соответствующие отраслевым стандартам, для хранения и защиты вашей личной информации, чтобы предотвратить ее потерю, несанкционированный доступ, публичное раскрытие, использование, повреждение, утрату или разглашение. Мы примем все рациональные и осуществимые меры для защиты вашей личной информации. Мы будем использовать технологию шифрования для обеспечения конфиденциальности данных; а также, использовать надежные механизмы защиты для предотвращения вредоносных атак в отношении данных.

Мы будем обучать и оценивать осведомленность сотрудников о безопасности данных и возможностях обеспечения безопасности, чтобы повысить их осведомленность о важности защиты личной информации. Мы проведем аутентификацию личности и контроль полномочий для сотрудников, которые обрабатывают личную информацию, и при этом подпишем соглашения о конфиденциальности с сотрудниками и партнерами, которые обращаются к вашей личной информации, чтобы уточнить должностные обязанности и кодексы поведения для гарантии того, чтобы только уполномоченный персонал мог получить доступ к личной информации. В случае любого нарушения соглашения о конфиденциальности отношения сотрудничества с компанией будут немедленно прекращены, при этом будут расследованы соответствующие юридические обязательства. Персонал, который контактирует с личной информацией, также будет обязан сохранять конфиденциальность при уходе со своих постов.

Мы напоминаем вам, что Интернет не является абсолютно безопасной средой. При взаимодействии с другими пользователями через стороннее социальное программное обеспечение, эл. почту, СМС и т. д., встроенные в TeraBox, когда вы не уверены, полностью ли стороннее программное обеспечение шифрует передачу информации, обращайте внимание на обеспечение безопасности вашей личной информации.

Мы также просим вас понять, что в Интернет-индустрии из-за ограничений и быстрого развития технологий и различных возможных вредоносных атак, даже если мы изо всех сил стараемся усилить меры безопасности, мы не всегда можем гарантировать 100%-ную безопасность информации. Пожалуйста, поймите, что система и коммуникационная сеть, которые вы используете при использовании наших продуктов и/ или услуг, могут вызвать проблемы безопасности в других каналах, находящихся вне нашего контроля.

Согласно нашей системе управления безопасностью, случаи разглашения, уничтожения или потери персональных данных относятся к наиболее серьезным инцидентам в области безопасности. В случае возникновения таких инцидентов, будет запущен план аварийного реагирования на самом высоком уровне компании, который будет рассматриваться совместной группой аварийного реагирования, состоящей из нескольких департаментов.

Мы разрабатываем план аварийного реагирования на инциденты сетевой безопасности, своевременно устраняем пробелы в системе, компьютерные вирусы, кибератаки, сетевые вторжения и другие риски безопасности. При возникновении инцидентов, угрожающих кибербезопасности, мы немедленно запустим план аварийного реагирования, примем соответствующие меры по исправлению и сообщим соответствующим компетентным органам согласно требованиям.

Разглашение, уничтожение и потеря персональных данных относятся к исключительно серьезным инцидентам в области безопасности на уровне компании, мы отвечаем за организацию регулярных тренировок по безопасности для членов рабочей группы в целях предотвращения таких инцидентов. В случае возникновения какого-либо инцидента мы запустим план действий в чрезвычайных ситуациях в соответствии с наивысшим приоритетом и сформируем группу реагирования на чрезвычайные ситуации, чтобы отследить причины и сократить потери в кратчайшие сроки.

В случае неприятного инцидента с безопасностью личной информации мы, в соответствии с требованиями законов и нормативных актов, незамедлительно проинформируем вас об основной ситуации и возможных последствиях инцидента с безопасностью, мерах по обработке, которые мы приняли или будем принимать, предложениях о рисках, которые вы можете предотвратить и уменьшить, и мерах по исправлению положения. Мы своевременно проинформируем вас о соответствующей информации о мероприятии в форме уведомления на месте, СМС-уведомления, связи по телефону, по эл. почте и по другой контактной информации, которую вы зарезервировали. При наличии трудности извещения, мы выберем рациональный и эффективный способ публикации объявления. Наряду с этим, мы будем активно сообщать об устранении инцидентов личной информационной безопасности в соответствии с требованиями регулирующих органов. Пожалуйста, поймите, что в соответствии с положениями законов и нормативных актов, если принимаемые нами меры могут эффективно избежать вреда, причиненного раскрытием информации, подделкой и потерей, если только регулирующий орган не потребует, чтобы вы были уведомлены, мы можем принять решение не уведомлять вас об инциденте с безопасностью личной информации.

Мы будем ссылаться на требования GDPR, выбирать соответствующие технические меры защиты безопасности, исходя из характера, объема, предыстории и цели обработки данных, а также рисков для отдельных лиц, и проводить регулярное тестирование и оценку их для поддержания эффективности принятых мер.

При возникновении разглашения данных, мы как можно скорее уведомим соответствующие группы пользователей, пострадавших от утечки информации, и сообщим в соответствующий компетентный отдел в течение 72 часов. В случае невозможности составления отчета в течение 72 часов, будет объяснена причина задержки.

Мы принимаем соответствующие технические и организационные меры для достижения целей защиты данных, таких как сведение к минимуму объема данных и включение необходимых мер предосторожности в процесс обработки данных для защиты прав субъектов данных. По умолчанию мы гарантируем, что данные, обрабатываемые для определенных целей, необходимы.

Где мы храним и обрабатываем Ваши данные

При оказании услуг мы можем хранить, обрабатывать и передавать вашу информацию в Японии, при этом необходимо получение согласия на предоставление вашей информации. Ваша информация также может храниться на локальном устройстве для доступа к услугам.

Каким образом Вы управляете Вашими данными и получаете к ним доступ

В соответствии с государственными и региональными законами, правилами, стандартами и преобладающей практикой, мы гарантируем вам осуществление следующих прав в отношении своих персональных данных, если выставите под сомнение или утверждаете осуществление прав, вы также можете связаться с нами через [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com). Вы можете просматривать, изменять, скачивать, удалять Ваши данные или предоставлять к ним общий доступ в своей учетной записи TeraBox.

1\. Право доступа

Если вы хотите узнать объем доступа, хранения, совместного использования и другой личной информации TeraBox или цель обработки вашей личной информации, вы можете связаться с нами для получения соответствующего контента.

2\. Право на исправление и дополнение

В случае, если вы обнаружите, что в вашей личной информации, обрабатываемой нами, присутствует ошибка, вы имеете право исправить ошибку или неполную информацию. После подтверждения вашей личности вы можете отправить нам свою заявку на исправление или дополнение через форму обратной связи и сообщения об ошибках или вышеупомянутую опубликованную контактную информацию. Мы дадим вам ответ, как только получим вашу заявку.

3\. Право на удаление

В нижеследующих случаях вы можете попросить нас удалить вашу личную информацию:

если мы обрабатываем вашу личную информацию в нарушение законов и нормативных актов или вашего соглашения;

если цель нашей обработки была достигнута, не может быть достигнута или больше не является необходимой для достижения цели обработки информации;

если мы прекращаем предоставлять продукты или услуги, или срок подошел к истечению;

если вы отзываете свое согласие;

другие обстоятельства, предусмотренные законами и административными актами.

Когда вы удаляете информацию из нашего сервиса, мы не можем удалить соответствующую информацию в системе резервного копирования немедленно, но мы обязуемся удалить информацию, когда резервная копия будет обновлена. Пожалуйста, ознакомьтесь и поймите, что если срок хранения, указанный законами, административными актами или настоящей политикой конфиденциальности, не истек, или удаление личной информации технически затруднено, мы прекратим обработку, кроме хранения и принятия необходимых мер безопасности.

4\. Отзыв согласия

Для выполнения каждой операционной функции требуется некоторая базовая личная информация. Для сбора и использования дополнительной собранной личной информации вы можете дать или отозвать свое согласие на авторизацию в любое время.

Вы можете непосредственно выключить адресную книгу, альбом, видеокамеру и другие права системы в системе оборудования, изменить объем согласия или отозвать ваши разрешения.

После отзыва вашего согласия мы не можем продолжать предоставлять вам услуги, соответствующие отзыву согласия, и при этом не будем использовать ваши соответствующие личные данные. Но ваше решение об отмене согласия не влияет на обработку персональных данных, которая была начата ранее на основании вашего согласия.

5\. Право на удаление

Вы можете удалить свой ранее зарегистрированный аккаунт. Вы также можете выйти из своего аккаунта в TeraBox следующим образом:

\[Фото профиля аккаунта\] - \[Меню\] - \[Настройки\] - \[Центр безопасности\] - \[Удаление аккаунта\].

Как только вы удалите свой аккаунт, вы не сможете пользоваться услугами продукта TeraBox, поэтому, пожалуйста, будьте осторожны в действиях. В целях защиты ваших законных прав и интересов или интересов других лиц, мы решим, следует ли поддерживать ваш запрос на удаление, основываясь на вашем использовании. Например, если у вас есть неиспользованные привилегии Premium или в вашем аккаунте есть данные, то мы не будем немедленно обрабатывать ваш запрос. Если иное не предусмотрено законами и нормативными актами, мы прекратим предоставление вам продуктов и услуг после того, как вы удалите свой аккаунт, и удалим вашу личную информацию в соответствии с вашими требованиями.

6\. Право на копирование и переносимость

Вы имеете право копировать вашу личную информацию, собранную нами. На условиях, предусмотренных законами и нормативными актами, и в соответствии с инструкциями и условиями, предусмотренными соответствующими компетентными органами, если это технически возможно, вы также можете попросить нас передать вашу личную информацию другим указанным вами субъектам.

Когда вы воспользуетесь соответствующими правами вышеуказанного субъекта персональных данных, мы также в первый раз проведем синхронизацию с соответствующей третьей стороной, чтобы убедиться, что ваши вышеуказанные права реализованы в условиях соблюдения нормативных актов, нормативных требований и технической осуществимости.

В тех случаях, когда ваша просьба явно не обоснована или превышает необходимые пределы, особенно когда просьба является повторной, мы можем:

(a) взимать определенный рациональный сбор в сочетании с административными расходами на предоставление информации, обмен или соответствующие действия; или

(b) отказывать в принятии решения по просьбе.

Вы можете управлять сохраненными Вами личными данными, а также способами их сбора, использования и предоставления к ним общего доступа согласно Закону Японии «О защите персональной информации» («Хранимые личные данные»). Например, вы можете:

a. Потребовать раскрытия сохраненных идентифицирующих Вас личных данных.

b. Потребовать внесения изменений, дополнений в сохраненные личные данные или их удаления в случае, если содержание сохраненных идентифицирующих личных данных не соответствует действительности.

c. Если сохраненные Вами личные данные получены нами или используются нами в настоящее время незаконно, пожалуйста, немедленно удалите или прекратите использовать сохраненные Вами личные данные.

d. Если мы незаконно предоставляем сохраненные Вами личные данные третьим сторонам, пожалуйста, немедленно прекратите предоставление сохраненных Вами личных данных.

Внесение изменений

В случае реорганизации, слияния или приобретения компании Flextech, или если наши активы будут проданы, ваша информация может быть передана оставшейся в организации, приобретателю или правопреемнику по сделке. Мы уведомим вас о любых таких транзакциях (например, сообщением на адрес эл. почты, привязанной с вашему аккаунту) и опишем ваш выбор в таком случае.

Настоящая политика конфиденциальности может время от времени пересматриваться. Обновленный вариант будет размещен на веб-сайте TeraBox. Мы уведомим вас, если какие-либо такие поправки окажут существенное влияние на ваши права.

Связаться с нами:

При наличии каких-либо сомнений или опасений, касающихся приложения TeraBox, наших услуг и неприкосновенности частной жизни, пожалуйста, свяжитесь с нами по электронной почте [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com).

Política de Privacidad

Política de Privacidad

Contenido y finalidad de la recopilación de información

Ofrecer los datos personales a los terceros

Compartir con otros usuarios

Podemos compartir sus datos con los terceros

Cómo protegemos y guardamos sus datos

Dónde almacenamos y tratamos sus datos

Su control y acceso a sus datos

{{ $t('termsOfServicePrivacyPolicy.age.title') }}

Cambios

Contacto con nosotros:

Política de Privacidad

Fecha de publicación: 18 de abril de 2023

Fecha de entrada en vigor: 18 de abril de 2023

¡Gracias por usar TeraBox! TeraBox se proporciona a usted por Flextech Inc. (en adelante, “Flextech” o “nosotros”). Nos comprometemos a proteger su privacidad. En esta Política de Privacidad describimos cómo recopilamos, almacenamos, tratamos, compartimos y utilizamos su información cuando utiliza nuestros sitios web, software y servicios (“Servicios”).

Recopilaremos y usaremos su información personal siguiendo los principios de legalidad, licitud y necesidad. Específicamente, recopilamos y procesamos su información personal para proporcionarle las funciones comerciales correspondientes. Para la función correspondiente, si usted proporciona información personal de otras personas, asegúrese de haber obtenido la autorización del sujeto correspondiente. Nos reservamos el derecho de verificar la fuente legal de dicha información personal en cualquier momento.

Solicitaremos su consentimiento personal bajo ciertas circunstancias estrictamente de acuerdo con las leyes y reglamentos. Además de esta política de privacidad, también podemos indicarle a través de la página del producto, el aviso de ventana emergente, el envío de mensaje y otros medios para explicarle las reglas de procesamiento de la información personal. Para el procesamiento de información personal correspondiente a la función comercial concreta se prevalecerán las reglas concretas, y las reglas concretas tienen el mismo efecto con la política de privacidad.

Atención: No necesitamos obtener su autorización y consentimiento para la recogida, uso, intercambio, transferencia y revelación pública de sus datos personales en las siguientes circunstancias:

Directamente relacionadas con la seguridad nacional y la seguridad de la defensa nacional;

Cuando sea necesario para la celebración o ejecución de un contrato en el que la persona sea parte;

Cuando sea necesario para cumplir deberes u obligaciones legales;

Cuando sea necesario para responder a una emergencia de salud pública o para proteger la vida, la salud y los bienes de una persona física en caso de emergencia;

Directamente relacionadas con la investigación, persecución, enjuiciamiento y ejecución de sentencias;

Cuando se haga para preservar la vida, la propiedad o los principales derechos e intereses legítimos suyos o de otra persona, y sea muy difícil obtener su consentimiento;

Cuando se recopila la información personal que haya sido revelada voluntariamente al público por usted u otra información personal divulgada legalmente, dentro de un ámbito razonable de conformidad con las leyes y reglamentos;

Cuando se recopila su información personal a partir de la información divulgada legalmente, como informes de noticias legales, información gubernamental abierta y otros canales similares, dentro de un ámbito razonable de conformidad con las leyes y reglamentos;

Cuando se trata la información personal dentro de un ámbito razonable con el fin de llevar a cabo reportajes de noticias y seguimiento de la opinión pública para interés público;

Cuando sea necesario para llevar a cabo estadísticas o investigaciones académicas de interés público para las instituciones de investigación académica, y cuando se proporcionen resultados de investigaciones académicas o descripciones, se haya realizado la desidentificación de la información personal contenida en el resultado;

Otra circunstancia prevista en cualquier ley o reglamento administrativo.

Contenido y finalidad de la recopilación de información

La tabla siguiente indica los tipos de información que nos presenta al utilizar estos Servicios y los fines para los que podemos utilizarla. Recopilamos y utilizamos la siguiente información para prestar, mejorar, proteger y promocionar nuestros Servicios.

| Tipo de información | Finalidad de recopilación |
| --- | --- |
| Información de la cuenta. Recopilamos y asociamos a su información que nos proporciona (como su dirección de correo electrónico, número de teléfono) cuando hace cosas como registrarse para crear su cuenta (si accede utilizando la cuenta de SNS, recibiremos su apodo y los datos de su foto de perfil de SNS). | Podemos usar esta información para confirmar si usted es el titular de la cuenta, y proteger la seguridad de su cuenta. Podemos recopilar esta información cuando usted accede a su cuenta. |
| Cosas de usuario. Materiales que usted almacena en TeraBox, como sus archivos, documentos, fotos, vídeos y audios (en adelante, “Cosas de usuario”). | Podríamos almacenar, tratar y transmitir Cosas de usuario, así como cualquier información relacionada, para garantizar la operación adecuada de los servicios, y permitir que usted pueda colaborar con otras personas y trabajar con varios dispositivos y servicios. La información relacionada incluye su información de perfil, el tamaño de los archivos, la fecha y hora a la que se han subido, y la actividad de uso. |
| Información de uso. Recopilamos información relacionada con su uso de los Servicios, incluidas las acciones que usted lleva a cabo sobre sus cuentas, como editar, ver, crear y mover archivos o carpetas. | Podemos utilizar esta información para prestar, mejorar, y promocionar nuestros Servicios, y proteger los usuarios de TeraBox. |
| Información del dispositivo. La información de los dispositivos que utiliza para acceder a los Servicios. Esto incluye datos como direcciones IP, navegador y dispositivo que utiliza, la página web que ha visitado antes de acceder a TeraBox, identificadores asociados a su dispositivo e información de ubicación de dispositivos que depende de su configuración. | Podemos utilizar estas informaciones para mejorar y proteger nuestros Servicios. |
| Cookies. Cuando visita TeraBox, un pequeño fragmento de texto se envía por el sitio web a su navegador. Puede configurar su navegador para que no acepte cookies, pero esto podría afectar las funciones de los Servicios. | Podemos utilizar cookies y tecnologías similares para prestar, mejorar, proteger y promocionar los Servicios. Las cookies nos ayudan a recordar su nombre de usuario, entender su uso de nuestros Servicios y mejorarlos a partir de esa información. Los terceros proveedores de servicios que cooperan con nosotros también pueden utilizar cookies y tecnologías similares. |
| Información de contacto. Puede compartir sus datos e información con contactos, números de móvil y direcciones de correo electrónico (por ejemplo, Facebook, Twitter) en la libreta de contactos de su teléfono móvil utilizando la función de intercambio de TeraBox. Son datos personales sensibles los datos en la libreta de contactos. Si se niega a proporcionar tales datos personales, no podrá utilizar dicha función comercial, pero sin afectar su uso normal de otras funciones y servicios relacionados con TeraBox. | Puede optar por darnos acceso a sus contactos para que le resulte más fácil realizar algunas acciones, como compartir sus datos y colaborar en ellas, enviar mensajes e invitar a otras personas a usar los Servicios de TeraBox. Esta operación requiere la habilitación del permiso de la libreta de contactos. En tal caso, almacenaremos dichos contactos en nuestros servidores para que pueda usarlos. Tenga en cuenta la credibilidad del destinatario del mensaje antes de compartir los datos. También le recomendamos que verifique las declaraciones de privacidad publicadas en las redes sociales o por los proveedores de servicios de terceros, para ver cómo traten su información, con el fin de tomar decisiones cautelosas. |
| Portapapeles. Cuando se registra en una cuenta de Terabox utilizando el código de invitación de otra persona, accede a enlaces de archivos compartidos por otros usuarios, agrega amigos mediante contraseñas o obtiene servicios de membresía a través de códigos de canje, leeremos la información de su portapapeles. | Accederemos a la información del portapapeles para ayudarte a abrir el archivo correspondiente al enlace, identificar al usuario correspondiente a la contraseña y al código de invitación, o para canjear servicios de membresía para ti. Nunca leeremos tu portapapeles con ningún otro propósito. |

Puede crear una cuenta de TeraBox con un número de teléfono y puede mejorar la información de su cuenta.

Para cumplir con los requisitos obligatorios de las leyes y reglamentos, a los efectos de proporcionar productos o servicios, o en función de su necesidad de mejorar el nivel de protección de la cuenta, cuando usted utiliza ciertos servicios de TeraBox o si tiene requisitos adicionales, debe proporcionar su nombre real, número de cédula e información de la cara para realizar la autenticación de su cuenta. Para verificar la exactitud e integridad de la información proporcionada por usted, o para garantizar la seguridad de su cuenta, podemos comparar la información del nombre real que proporciona a TeraBox con la información guardada por la institución permitida por la ley o la institución autorizada por la autoridad gubernamental.

Recopilamos los datos descritos anteriormente para prestarle los Servicios de una forma fiable y segura y realizar los fines comerciales legales. En la medida en que tratemos sus datos para otras finalidades, le pediremos su consentimiento por adelantado o solicitaremos que nuestros socios obtengan dicho consentimiento.

Usted acepta que combinaremos, identificaremos y analizaremos, perfilaremos o procesaremos adicionalmente los datos personales que usted proporciona voluntaria o involuntariamente durante el servicio mediante nuestra propia tecnología o la tecnología de la parte confiada, y se formará una variedad de información de etiqueta (en adelante, “información de etiqueta”) con diferente granularidad que puede reflejar su comportamiento, preferencia o estado crediticio y otras características. Utilizaremos la información de etiqueta en escenarios y finalidades específicos para realizar la toma de decisiones automatizada, con el fin de enviarle información de visualización personalizada y/o información de marketing.

Usted tiene el derecho de rechazar la toma de decisiones automatizadas proporcionada por nosotros. Puede contactarnos a través de la información de contacto publicada en este acuerdo, o pedirnos que la paremos a través del interruptor relevante en el servicio del producto. Al mismo tiempo, seguiremos las leyes o los requisitos reglamentarios sobre la prohibición de la automatización de la toma de decisiones en los países o regiones pertinentes para su ejecución.

Podemos usar sus Datos de Cuenta con fines de marketing y le enviemos periódicamente información sobre nuevos productos, actualizaciones y otros materiales promocionales de TeraBox ocasionalmente. Puede optar por no recibir materiales de marketing en cualquier momento haciendo clic en el enlace "cancelar suscripción" en cualquier correo electrónico que reciba.

Ofrecer los datos personales a los terceros

No proporcionaremos información personal a ningún tercero sin su consentimiento previo, a menos que sea necesario para alguno de los siguientes casos:

(a) Debemos colaborar con las organizaciones gubernamentales nacionales o regionales o sus agentes para cumplir sus deberes u obligaciones de conformidad con las leyes y reglamentos aplicables; si se requiere su consentimiento, se excluirá dicho cumplimiento;

(b) Cuando exista un riesgo significativo para la vida o los bienes de una persona;

(c) Cuando exista una necesidad particular de mejorar la salud pública o promover el desarrollo saludable de los jóvenes;

Para intercambio, transferencia o divulgación de su información personal en las excepciones mencionadas anteriormente, registraremos el fundamento de procesamiento de información, el alcance de la información procesada, la información de la parte receptora y otra información, incluyendo específicamente el siguiente contenido, y seguiremos los principios mínimos necesarios para proteger sus derechos e intereses legales.

(1) Nombre y datos de contacto del responsable del tratamiento, responsable de la protección de datos;

(2) Finalidad de tratamiento de datos;

(3) Descripción del tipo del interesado y tipo de los datos personales;

(4) Tipo de los destinatarios a que los datos personales han sido o serán divulgados, incluyendo los destinatarios ubicados en un tercer país o una organización internacional;

(5) Registros de transferencia de datos personales a un tercero país o una organización internacional, y registros de medidas de protección apropiadas;

(6) Fecha límite prevista para eliminar diferentes tipos de datos;

(7) Descripción general de las medidas de seguridad técnica y organizativa.

Compartir con otros usuarios

Nuestros Servicios muestran información como su nombre, la foto de su perfil, el dispositivo, su dirección de correo electrónico y la información de uso a otros usuarios con los que colabora o comparte contenido según su permiso, cuando usted utiliza la función de colaborar en equipo o de compartir los archivos que se suministra por TeraBox. Esto le ayuda a sincronizarse con los equipos a los que puede unirse, y facilita a los demás usuarios la posibilidad de compartir archivos y carpetas con usted.

Podemos compartir sus datos con los terceros

Podemos confiar en determinados terceros (por ejemplo, proveedores de servicios de atención al cliente y IT) con el objetivo de ayudarnos a prestar, mejorar, proteger y promocionar nuestros Servicios. Estos proveedores pueden acceder a su información para realizar tareas en nuestro nombre, y seguiremos siendo los únicos responsables de la gestión de su información por su parte de acuerdo con nuestras instrucciones.

Podemos compartir infraestructura, sistemas y tecnologías con otras empresas afiliadas de Flextech para prestar, mejorar, proteger y promocionar los Servicios. Estas empresas afiliadas compartirán su información con nosotros y utilizarán la información que usted ha indicado en la sección "Contenido y finalidad de la recopilación de información" para los fines descritos en ella. Seremos los responsables de permitir que estas empresas utilicen su información.

Puede elegir conectar su cuenta de TeraBox con servicios de terceros. Al hacerlo, permite que TeraBox y esos terceros intercambien la información listada en la sección “Contenido y finalidad de la recopilación de información” de esta Política de Privacidad, para que TeraBox y esos terceros puedan prestar, mejorar, proteger y promocionar sus servicios. En estos casos, el uso de su información por parte de estos terceros se regirá según sus políticas de privacidad y condiciones del servicio.

Estableceremos un mecanismo de salida para la transmisión de datos entre países en referencia a los requisitos de GDPR, y actualizaremos su mecanismo transfronterizo oportunamente en función de los requisitos de GDPR. Para cualquier tratamiento de datos personales, cumpliremos los principios básicos de las disposiciones de GDPR, obtendremos el consentimiento efectivo del interesado de datos, o cumpliremos con otras razones legales. Además, se establecerán mecanismos adicionales para proteger los datos, con el fin de cumplir los requisitos sustantivos de GDPR para el tratamiento de datos.

Cómo protegemos y guardamos sus datos

Tenemos un equipo dedicado a mantener su información protegida y comprobar la posible existencia de vulnerabilidades. Trabajamos constantemente en funciones que mantendrán su información a salvo, además de elementos como la autenticación en dos pasos, el cifrado de archivos en pausa y las alertas al vincular nuevos dispositivos y aplicaciones a su cuenta. Implementamos tecnologías automatizadas para detectar comportamientos y contenido abusivos que podrían dañar nuestros Servicios, a usted o a otros usuarios.

Cuando se registra para obtener una cuenta de TeraBox, conservamos la información que almacena en nuestros Servicios mientras exista su cuenta o necesitamos prestar los Servicios para usted. Si quiere eliminar su cuenta, envíe el correo electrónico a [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) para eliminar su información, realizaremos el borrado de la información dentro los 30 días contados a partir de la recepción de su solicitud. No obstante: (1) no podríamos borrar la información de su cuenta antes de verificar la identidad de usuario; (2) quizá necesitemos un tiempo para borrar la información de nuestros servidores y el almacenamiento de la copia de seguridad; y (3) podríamos conservar la información si fuera necesaria para cumplir nuestras obligaciones legales, resolver disputas o ejecutar nuestros derechos bajo el contrato.

Conservaremos su información personal dentro del período requerido para prestar el servicio. Sin embargo, ampliaremos el período de conservación después de la expiración del período de conservación mencionado, de conformidad con la ley, por acuerdo o dentro de límites razonables, en las siguientes circunstancias: si el período de conservación esté previsto de otro modo por las leyes y los reglamentos, si usted acepte un período de conservación más largo, en caso de garantizar la seguridad y la calidad del servicio, en caso de lograr fines de resolución de conflictos, o si es técnicamente difícil lograrlo.

Eliminaremos su información personal o realizar la seudonimización según lo estipulado por la ley después de que se exceda el período de conservación.

Recolectaremos, usaremos, almacenaremos y transmitiremos la información del usuario siguiendo el principio de “minimización”, y le informaremos sobre la finalidad y el alcance del uso de la información relevante, mediante el Acuerdo del Usuario, la Política de Privacidad, las reglas pertinentes, la ventana emergente, o los avisos, etc.

La seguridad de su información es importante para nosotros. Hemos establecido un equipo responsable especialmente para desarrollar y aplicar una variedad de tecnologías y procedimientos de seguridad, etc. Llevaremos a cabo una revisión de los antecedentes de seguridad de los responsables de gestión de seguridad y del personal de los puestos clave de seguridad. Hemos establecido un sistema integral de gestión de seguridad de la información y un mecanismo interno de tratamiento de los incidentes de seguridad. Tomamos una serie de medidas de seguridad tecnológicas que cumplen las normas del sector para guardar y proteger sus datos, a fin de que no sean objeto de acceso no autorizado, ni de divulgación pública, ni de uso, ni de modificación, ni de daños ni de pérdida. Tomamos todas las medidas razonables y factibles para proteger sus datos personales. Utilizaremos la tecnología de encriptación para garantizar la confidencialidad de los datos; utilizaremos un mecanismo de protección de confianza para evitar ataques maliciosos a los datos.

Formaremos la conciencia del personal sobre la seguridad de los datos, y realizaremos la capacitación y evaluación de la capacidad de seguridad del personal, para mejorar su conciencia sobre la importancia de proteger la información personal. Autenticaremos la identidad y controlaremos los permisos para el personal que trata la información personal, y firmaremos un acuerdo de confidencialidad con el personal y los socios que acceden a su información personal, para aclarar las responsabilidades laborales y los códigos de conducta, garantizando así que solo las personas autorizadas tengan acceso a la información personal. En caso de una violación del acuerdo de confidencialidad, la asociación con la empresa se dará por terminada inmediatamente, y se investigará la responsabilidad legal pertinente. También habrá requisitos de confidencialidad para el personal que accede a la información personal cuando este abandone este trabajo.

Le recordamos que el entorno de Internet no es 100% seguro. Cuando usted intercambia su ubicación geográfica o información de seguimiento con otros usuarios, a través de software de redes sociales de terceros integrado en TeraBox, correo electrónico, SMS, etc., no se podrá garantizar que el software de terceros encripte completamente para la transmisión de información, por lo que debe tener cuidado para garantizar la seguridad de su información personal.

También le pedimos que comprenda que, en la industria de Internet, debido a las limitaciones tecnológicas y al rápido desarrollo y los posibles ataques maliciosos, es imposible garantizar siempre al 100% la seguridad de la información, incluso si hacemos todo lo posible para mejorar las medidas de seguridad. Por favor, comprenda que los sistemas y las redes de comunicación que utiliza al usar nuestros productos y/o servicios podrían tener problemas de seguridad más allá de nuestro control.

De acuerdo con nuestro sistema de gestión de seguridad, la divulgación, el daño o la pérdida de información personal se clasifica como incidente de seguridad más importante. Una vez ocurrido, se iniciará el plan de emergencia de nivel más alto de la empresa, y se formará un equipo conjunto de respuesta a emergencias por varios departamentos para tratarlo.

Formularemos un plan de contingencia para incidentes de seguridad de las redes, y eliminaremos a tiempo los riesgos de seguridad tales como las vulnerabilidades del sistema, el virus del computador, el ataque a la red, la intrusión a la red, etc. En caso de un incidente que ponga en peligro la seguridad de la red, inmediatamente activaremos el plan de contingencia, y tomaremos las medidas correctivas correspondientes, e informaremos a las autoridades pertinentes según las disposiciones pertinentes.

La divulgación, el daño o la pérdida de información personal se clasifica como incidente de seguridad más importante de la empresa. Seremos responsables de organizar regularmente a los miembros del grupo de trabajo para realizar simulacros de planes de seguridad, para evitar tales incidentes de seguridad. En caso de un incidente, activaremos el plan de contingencia como la más alta prioridad, y formaremos un equipo de contingencia para rastrear la causa y reducir la pérdida en el menor tiempo posible.

Si, desafortunadamente, se produjera un incidente de seguridad de la información personal, según los requisitos de las leyes y los reglamentos, le informaremos sin demora la situación general del incidente de seguridad y su posible impacto, las medidas de eliminación que hemos tomado o tomaremos, las recomendaciones que usted puede hacer para prevenir y reducir el riesgo de forma independiente, y las medidas correctivas para usted. Le comunicaremos inmediatamente el incidente por notificación de la estación, mensaje, teléfono, correo electrónico u otras formas de contacto que usted reserva. Cuando sea difícil informar a los sujetos de la información uno por uno, adoptaremos medios razonables y eficaces para emitir anuncios. También tomaremos la iniciativa de informar sobre el tratamiento de los incidentes de seguridad de la información, tal y como exigen las autoridades reguladoras. Por favor, comprenda que de acuerdo con las leyes y los reglamentos, si las medidas que tomamos puedan evitar efectivamente la divulgación, la alteración o la pérdida de la información, podemos optar por no informarle sobre el incidente de seguridad de la información personal, a menos que las autoridades reguladoras solicite informarle.

Nos referiremos a los requisitos de GDPR, y optaremos por las medidas de protección de la seguridad técnica adecuadas en función de la naturaleza, el alcance, el contexto y la finalidad de los datos tratados, así como del riesgo que supone para la persona, y probaremos y evaluaremos regularmente para mantener la eficacia de las medidas adoptadas.

Tan pronto como se produzca la divulgación de datos, notificaremos al grupo de personas afectadas por la divulgación de información lo antes posible, y dentro de las 72 horas informaremos a las autoridades competentes pertinentes. Cuando no podamos informarle dentro de las 72 horas, indicaremos el motivo de la demora.

Tomamos las medidas técnicas y organizativas apropiadas para lograr objetivos de protección de datos, tales como la minimización de datos y la integración de las salvaguardas necesarias en el tratamiento de datos, para proteger los derechos del interesado de datos. Por defecto, son necesarios los datos tratados para un propósito específico.

Dónde almacenamos y tratamos sus datos

Durante la prestación de los Servicios, podemos almacenar, tratar y transmitir su información en Japón, y usted está de acuerdo con el suministro de su información. Sus datos también pueden almacenarse en los dispositivos locales que utilice para acceder a los Servicios.

Su control y acceso a sus datos

De conformidad con las leyes, los reglamentos y las prácticas vigentes en los países en cuestión, garantizamos que ejerce los siguientes derechos sobre su información personal. Si tiene preguntas u opiniones sobre el ejercicio de sus derechos, también puede ponerse en contacto con nosotros a través de [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com). Puede ver, modificar, descargar, eliminar, o compartir sus datos desde su cuenta de TeraBox.

1\. Derecho de acceso

Cuando desee conocer el alcance de su información personal adquirida, almacenada, compartida, etc. por TeraBox o la finalidad del tratamiento de su información personal, puede ponerse en contacto con nosotros para obtener el contenido pertinente.

2\. Derecho de rectificación y adición

Cuando descubra que la información personal que hemos tratado sobre usted es inexacta o incompleta, tiene derecho a rectificar o completarla; una vez verificada su identidad, puede enviarnos su solicitud de rectificación o adición a través de comentarios y notificación de errores, o los contactos como se han descrito anteriormente. Nos pondremos en contacto con usted lo antes posible después de recibir su solicitud.

3\. Derecho de eliminación

Puede hacernos una solicitud de eliminación de datos personales en las siguientes circunstancias:

en caso de que tratemos los datos personales infringiendo las leyes y los reglamentos, o de forma que incumplamos gravemente nuestro acuerdo con usted;

en caso de que la finalidad de nuestro tratamiento se haya alcanzado, no se pueda alcanzar, o ya no sea necesaria para alcanzarla;

en caso de que dejemos de suministrarle productos o servicios, o de que el período de conservación haya expirado;

en caso de que usted retire su consentimiento;

otras circunstancias estipuladas en las leyes y regulaciones administrativas.

Una vez que usted haya eliminado la información en nuestros servicios, es probable que no podamos eliminar inmediatamente la información correspondiente del sistema de copia de seguridad, pero la eliminaremos cuando se actualice la copia de seguridad. Conozca y comprenda que si no haya expirado el período de conservación estipulado por las leyes y los reglamentos administrativos, o descrito en esta Política de Privacidad, o la eliminación de la información personal sea técnicamente difícil de lograr, dejaremos el tratamiento que excluye el almacenamiento y las medidas de seguridad necesarias.

4\. Retiro del consentimiento

Cada función comercial requiere alguna información personal básica para realizarse. Para la recopilación y el uso de la información personal recopilada adicional, puede otorgar o retirar su consentimiento de autorización en cualquier momento.

Puede cerrar los permisos para la libreta de contactos, el álbum, la cámara y otros sistemas, cambiar el alcance de consentimiento o retirar su autorización directamente en el sistema del dispositivo.

Una vez que haya retirado su consentimiento, no podremos continuar proporcionándole el servicio correspondiente al retiro de su consentimiento, y ya no usará su información personal correspondiente. Sin embargo, su decisión de retirar su consentimiento no afectará a la legitimidad de cualquier tratamiento basado en su consentimiento antes de que lo hubiera retirado.

5\. Derecho de cancelación

Puede cancelar la cuenta previamente registrada. También puede cancelar su cuenta en TeraBox a través de la siguiente ruta:

\[Perfil de la cuenta\] - \[Menú\] - \[Configuración\] - \[Centro de seguridad\] - \[Cancelación de la cuenta\].

Una vez que cancele su cuenta, no podrá usar el servicio del producto TearBox, así que tenga cuidado en esta operación. Con el fin de proteger los derechos e intereses legítimos de usted o de otros, juzgaremos si aceptamos su solicitud de cancelación en función de su uso. Por ejemplo, si tenga beneficios de Premium pendientes de gastar, o si aún tenga datos en su cuenta, no aceptaremos inmediatamente su solicitud. Dejaremos de proporcionarle productos y servicios una vez cancelada la cuenta, y eliminaremos su información personal a petición suya, salvo que se disponga lo contrario en las leyes y los reglamentos.

6\. Derecho de copia y portabilidad

Usted tiene el derecho de copiar su información personal recopilada por nosotros. También puede solicitarnos la transferencia de su información personal a otros sujetos que se especifique por usted, si ella es técnicamente factible, de conformidad con las directivas y condiciones de las autoridades pertinentes, según lo exijan las leyes y los reglamentos.

Cuando ejerza los derechos relacionados con el interesado de la información personal mencionados arriba, también la sincronizaremos en el tercero relevante tan pronto como sea posible, para garantizar que se logren sus derechos anteriores de conformidad con los requisitos reglamentarios y bajo la condición factible técnicamente.

Cuando su solicitud obviamente no esté justificada o exceda los límites necesarios, especialmente cuando la solicitud sea repetitiva, podremos:

(a) cobrar una tarifa razonable en combinación con los costos administrativos de proporcionar información, intercambiar o acción correspondiente; o

(b) negarnos a actuar sobre la solicitud.

Usted puede controlar la información personal conservada y el método de recopilación, utilización y compartimiento de acuerdo con la Ley de Protección de Información Personal de Japón (“información personal conservada”). Por ejemplo, usted puede:

a. pedirnos la divulgación de los datos personales conservados con que puede identificarse.

b. solicitar corrección, adición o eliminación de la información personal conservada cuando descubre que el contenido de la información personal conservada es falso.

c. eliminar o dejar de utilizar la información personal que usted conserva inmediatamente, si su información personal conservada ha sido obtenida por nosotros ilegalmente, o se está utilizando por nosotros.

d. dejar de presentar la información personal que usted conserva inmediatamente, si su información personal conservada se ha presentado ilegalmente a los terceros por nosotros.

Cambios

Si nos vemos implicados en la reorganización, fusión, adquisición de Flextech o venta de nuestros activos, sus datos podrían transferirse a la entidad superviviente, al adquirente o al sucesor en esa transacción. Le notificaremos cualquier transacción de este tipo (por ejemplo, mediante un mensaje a la dirección de correo asociada a su cuenta), y le indicaremos sus posibles opciones en este evento.

Esta Política de Privacidad puede ser revisada cada cierto tiempo. Publicaremos la versión más actualizada en el sitio web de TeraBox. Si alguna revisión afectara negativamente de forma significativa a sus derechos, le notificaríamos al respecto.

Contacto con nosotros:

Si tiene alguna duda o preocupación acerca de TeraBox, nuestros Servicios o el derecho de privacidad, póngase en contacto con nosotros a través de [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com).

سياسة الخصوصية TeraBox

سياسة الخصوصية TeraBox

محتوى المعلومات التي يتم جمعها والغرض من جمعها

تقديم المعلومات الشخصية للطرف الثالث

المشاركة مع مستخدم آخر

مشاركة المعلومات الخاصة بك مع الطرف الثالث

كيفية حماية المعلومات وتخزينها

مكان تخزين ومعالجة المعلومات الخاصة بك

كيفية التحكم في المعلومات الخاصة بك والوصول إليها

{{ $t('termsOfServicePrivacyPolicy.age.title') }}

التغيير

تواصل معنا:

سياسة الخصوصية TeraBox

تاريخ الإصدار: 18 أبريل 2023

تاريخ بدء العمل بها: 18 أبريل 2023

شكراً جزيلاً لك على استخدام TeraBox، الذي يتم تقديمه لك بواسطة شركة Flextech (Flextech أو "نحن"). ولأننا ملزمون بالحرص التام على حماية خصوصيتك، فإن سياسة الخصوصية هذه توضح لك بشكل وافي الطرق التي نستخدمها في جمع بياناتك وتخزينها ومعالجتها ومشاركتها واستخدامها، وذلك خلال قيامك باستخدام موقعنا الإلكتروني وبرنامجنا وخدماتنا ("الخدمات").

ومما لا شك فيه أننا سنتبع المبادئ القانونية والسليمة والضرورية خلال مرحلة جمع معلوماتك الشخصية واستخدامها. وبمزيد من التفصيل، يمكن القول إننا سنقوم بجمع معلوماتك الشخصية ومعالجتها بغرض تزويدك بوظائف العمل ذات الصلة، وفي حالة قيامك بتزويدنا بمعلومات تخص شخص آخر برجاء من الحصول على إذن من صاحب هذه المعلومات، حيث إننا لدينا الحق في أي وقت بالقيام بالتحقق من المصدر القانوني الخاص بهذه المعلومات الشخصية المقدمة.

ووفقًا للقوانين واللوائح الصارمة، سيتم طلب موافقتك الفردية أحياناً في ظل بعض الظروف المعينة. وبالإضافة إلى سياسة الخصوصية هذه، سنقوم أيضًا بتوضيح قواعدنا المتعلقة بالتعامل مع معلوماتك الشخصية من خلال كل من: الإشعارات التي تظهر لك على صفحة المنتج والنوافذ المنبثقة وكذلك تقنية دفع المعلومات وغيرها من الوسائل الأخرى. وستخضع ظروف عملية معالجة المعلومات الشخصية الخاصة بك المرتبطة بشكل وثيق ببعض وظائف العمل المحددة لقواعد محددة، وستمتلك تلك القواعد المحددة تأثير يماثل تأثير سياسة الخصوصية هذه.

برجاء الانتباه إلى أن: عملية جمع المعلومات الشخصية واستخدامها ومشاركتها ونقلها والكشف عنها علنًا لن تتطلب الحصول على إذن مسبق منك في ظل الظروف التالية:

الأمور المتعلقة بشكل مباشرة بالأمن القومي وأمن الدفاع الوطني؛

الأمور الضرورية المتعلقة بعقد أو تنفيذ عقد يكون الفرد طرفًا فيه؛

الأمور الضرورية المتعلقة بأداء الواجبات أو الالتزامات القانونية؛

الأمور الضرورية المتعلقة بالاستجابة إلى حالات الطوارئ الصحية العامة أو المتعلقة بحماية الأرواح وصحة وسلامة ممتلكات الأشخاص الآخرين في حالات الطوارئ؛

الأمور المتعلقة بشكل مباشر بالتحقيقات الجنائية والملاحقة القضائية والمحاكمة وتنفيذ الأحكام المتعلقة بالجرائم؛

الأمور المتعلقة بحماية الأرواح والممتلكات والحقوق والمصالح القانونية الكبرى المتعلقة بك أو بالأفراد الآخرين، ويكون من الصعب الحصول على موافقة الشخص في الوقت المناسب؛

الأمور المتعلقة بجمع معلوماتك الشخصية التي قمت بإعلانها للعامة أو التي تم الإعلان عنها بشكل قانوني ضمن نطاق معقول وفقًا للقوانين واللوائح المتعلقة؛

الأمور المتعلقة بجمع معلوماتك الشخصية التي قمت بالكشف عنها الكشف بشكل قانوني ضمن نطاق معقول وفقًا للقوانين واللوائح المتعلقة، ومثال ذلك: التقارير الإخبارية القانونية والإفصاح عن المعلومات الحكومية وغير ذلك من القنوات الأخرى ذات الصلة؛

الأمور المتعلقة بإجراء التقارير الإخبارية والرقابة على الرأي العام وغير ذلك من الأعمال الأخرى، والتي تتطلب معالجة المعلومات الشخصية الخاصة بك ضمن نطاق معقول؛

الأمور الضرورية المتعلقة بقيام مؤسسات البحث الأكاديمي بإجراء الإحصاءات أو البحث الأكاديمي استناداً إلى المصلحة العامة، مع العلم أنه يتم إجراء ذكر تلك المعلومات الشخصية التي ترد في نتائج البحث الأكاديمي أو النتائج المقدمة للعالم الخارجي دون ذكر هوية صاحبها؛

وما إلى ذلك من الظروف الأخرى المنصوص عليها في القوانين واللوائح المتعلقة.

محتوى المعلومات التي يتم جمعها والغرض من جمعها

يوضح الجدول الموجود أدناه الأنواع المختلفة للمعلومات التي تقدمها إلينا عند استخدام هذه الخدمات، وكذلك الأغراض التي نقوم من أجلها استخدام هذه المعلومات. مع العلم أننا نجمع المعلومات الواردة أدناه ونستخدمها من أجل توفير الخدمات الخاصة بنا وتحسينها والحفاظ عليها والترويج لها.

| نوع المعلومات | الغرض من الجمع |
| --- | --- |
| معلومات الحساب. سنقوم بجمع المعلومات التي ستزودنا بها عند إجراءك بعض العمليات (مثل تسجيل حساب) كعنوان البريد الإلكتروني الخاص بك ورقم الهاتف المحمول وغيرهم من المعلومات الأخرى. (وفي حالة قيامك بتسجيل الدخول الخاص بك من خلال حساب SNS الخاص بك، سنقوم بجمع معلومات الاسم المستعار وبيانات صورة ملف تعريف الموجودين على ذلك الحساب)، ثم القيام بربط هذه المعلومات بحسابك. | يمكننا القيام باستخدام تلك المعلومات من أجل التأكد من هويتك كمالك للحساب وكذلك من أجل حماية الحساب الخاص بك. كما أننا قد نقوم بجمع هذه المعلومات عندما تقوم بتسجيل الدخول إلى الحساب الخاص بك. |
| مواد المستخدم. والتي تشير كافة المواد التي يقوم المستخدم بتخزينها في TeraBox، ومثال ذلك الملفات والمستندات والصور والفيديوهات والمقاطع الصوتية ("مواد المستخدم"). | يمكننا القيام بتخزين كل من مواد المستخدم والمعلومات ذات الصلة بها ومعالجتها ونقلها، وذلك من أجل ضمان التشغيل السليم للخدمة وإتاحة تعاون المستخدم مع الآخرين، والعمل عبر الأجهزة والخدمات المتعددة. ويقصد بالمعلومات ذات الصلة: المعلومات الموجودة بملفك الشخصي وحجم ملفاتك، وتاريخ تحميل الملفات والوقت الذي تم تحميها فيه بالإضافة إلى أنشطة الاستخدام. |
| المعلومات الخاصة بأحوال الاستخدام. والتي تشير إلى المعلومات المتعلقة بكيفية استخدام الخدمة، ويتضمن ذلك العمليات التي يتم تنفيذها في الحساب، مثل تحرير عرض وإنشاء ونقل الملفات أو المجلدات. | يمكننا استخدام هذه المعلومات من أجل غرض تقديم الخدمة والعمل على تحسينها والترويج لها وكذللك من أجل حماية مستخدمي TeraBox. |
| المعلومات الخاصة بالجهاز. والتي تشير إلى المعلومات المتعلقة بالجهاز الذي يتم استخدامه للوصول إلى الخدمة، وذلك مثل: عناوين الـ IP، والمعلومات الخاصة بكل من المتصفح والجهاز، وصفحات الويب التي زارها المستخدم قبل تصفح صفحة TeraBox، والمعرفات المتعلقة بالجهاز، وكذلك المعلومات الخاصة بالموقع التي يتم التي تتحدد طبقاً لإعدادات الجهاز. | يمكننا استخدام هذه المعلومات من أجل تحسين الخدمات الخاصة بنا والحفاظ عليها. |
| ملفات تعريف الارتباط. والتي تشير إلى نص صغير موجز يتم إرساله إلى متصفحك من قِبّل الموقع عند زيارتك لصفحة TeraBox. ويمكنك عدم قبول ملفات تعريف الارتباط من خلال إعدادات متصفحك، ولكن هذا الاختيار من الممكن أن يؤثر على وظائف الخدمة. | يمكننا استخدام ملفات تعريف الارتباط وغيرها من التقنيات المماثلة الأخرى لتقديم الخدمة وتحسينها والحفاظ عليها والترويج لها. والجدير بالذكر أن ملفات تعريف الارتباط تتيح لنا إمكانية تذكر اسم المستخدم الخاص بك، والتعرف على الظروف المتعلقة باستخدامك للخدمة، ومن ثم بناءً على هذه المعلومات يمكننا تحسين الخدمة. ويمكن أيضًا أن يتم استخدام ملفات تعريف الارتباط وغيرها التقنيات المماثلة لمقدمي خدمات الجهات الخارجية الذين نتعاون معهم في الأعمال. |
| طرق التواصل. يوجد بـ TeraBox تقنية المشاركة والتي يمكن أن تستخدمها لتقوم بمشاركة البيانات والمعلومات الخاصة بك مع جهات الاتصال الموجود بدفتر هاتفك بما في ذلك أرقام الهواتف المحمولة وعناوين البريد الإلكتروني ومواقع التواصل الاجتماعي (مثل Facebook وTwitter). ولأن المعلومات الموجودة في دفتر الهاتف غالباً ما تكون شخصية حساسة، لذا ففي حالة رفضك لمشاركة هذه المعلومات لن يؤثر ذلك إلا على إمكانية استخدامك لميزة المشاركة المذكورة أعلاه، ولكن لن يؤثر بأي شكل على استخدامك الطبيعي لميزات TeraBox الأخرى وغيرها من الخدمات ذات الصلة. | بمقدورك أن تختار السماح لـ TeraBox بأن يصل إلى معلومات طرق الاتصال الخاصة بك وذلك من أجل تسهيل بعض العمليات المعينة، مثل: تقنية المشاركة مع أطراف آخرين والتعاون معهم لمعالجة البيانات الخاصة بك وإرسال الرسائل القصيرة، هذا بالإضافة إلى إرسال بريد إلكتروني لتدعو الآخرين لاستخدام الخدمات الخاصة بـ TeraBox. وبالطبع تتطلب هذه العمليات قيامك بالموافقة على إذن السماح الخاص بوصول TeraBox إلى دفتر هاتفك. وسيلي ذلك قيامنا بتخزين تلك المعلومات على الخوادم الخاصة بنا من أجل اتاحتها لاستخدامك فيما بعد. ولكن برجاء التأكد قبل القيام بالمشاركة من درجة موثوقية الشخص مستلم الرسالة. وفي الوقت نفسه، نقترح عليك ان تتحقق من بيان الخصوصية الخاص بالشبكات الاجتماعية أو موفري الخدمات الآخرين لتفهم بشكل واضح كيف يتم التعامل مع معلوماتك، ومن ثم يمكنك لاتخاذ قرار حكيم. |
| الحافظة. عند تسجيل حساب Terabox باستخدام رمز دعوة من شخص آخر، أو الوصول إلى روابط ملفات تم مشاركتها من قبل مستخدمين آخرين، أو إضافة أصدقاء من خلال كلمات المرور، أو الحصول على خدمات العضوية من خلال رموز الاسترداد، سنقوم بقراءة معلومات الحافظة الخاصة بك. | سنقوم بالوصول إلى معلومات الحافظة لمساعدتك على فتح الملف المقابل للرابط، وتحديد المستخدم المقابل لكلمة المرور ورمز الدعوة، أو لاستبدال خدمات العضوية لك. نحن لن نقرأ الحافظة الخاصة بك لأي غرض آخر. |

يمكنك القيام بإنشاء حساب في TeraBox باستخدام رقم هاتفك، وبهذه الخطوة ستكون قد ساعدت بشكل كبير على إكمال المعلومات الخاصة بحسابك.

يتعين عليك عند استخدام خدمات TeraBox أو في حالة وجود متطلبات معينة لديك، أن تقدم اسمك الحقيقي ورقم هويتك الصحيح وبصمة الوجه الخاصة بك، وذلك لاستكمال التحقق من حسابك، والذي يعتبر أمر ضروري من أجل تلبية المتطلبات الإلزامية للقوانين واللوائح أو لتوفير بعض المنتجات أو الخدمات أو لتعزيز مستوى الحماية الخاص بحسابك. ويمكننا القيام بمطابقة معلومات الاسم الحقيقي التي قدمته لنا مع المعلومات المقابلة التي تقوم المنظمات ذات السلطة بالاحتفاظ بها بما يتوافق مع القوانين واللوائح أو مع تلك التي تحتفظ بها الوكالات المصرح بها من قبل الهيئات الحكومية، وذلك إما أن يكون من أجل التأكد من دقة المعلومات التي قد قدمتها لنا واكتمالها، أو يكون من أجل ضمان أمان الحساب الخاص بك.

يرجى العلم أنه يتم جمع المعلومات التي تم ذكرها أعلاه من أجل تقديم خدمة موثوقة وآمنة ومن أجل أغراض تجارية مشروعة تماماً. وقبل اجراء أي عملية معالجة لمعلوماتك من أجل غرض ثالث غير تلك السببين، سنقوم بلا شك نحن أو شركاؤنا بالتواصل المسبق معك والحصول على موافقتك أولاً.

كما يجب التنويه أنك توافق على أننا سنقوم من خلال التقنيات الخاصة بنا أو التقنيات الخاصة بالوكيل، بجمع ودمج، وتحديد وتحليل، ورسم ومعالجة المعلومات الشخصية التي تقدمها إلينا بشكل نشط أو سلبي أثناء استخدامك الخدمة الخاصة بنا، كما توافق كذلك على تشكيل أنواع مختلفة وتفاصيل مختلفة من معلومات التسمية التي يمكن أن تعكس عاداتك السلوكية واهتماماتك وهواياتك وحالتك الائتمانية وغير ذلك من الخصائص الأخرى (المشار إليها فيما يلي باسم "معلومات التسمية"). وأننا سنستخدم معلومات التسمية تلك من أجل اتخاذ القرارات التلقائية في سياق سيناريوهات معينة وأغراض محددة، وذلك لتزويدك بمعلومات عرض مخصصة لك و/ أو معلومات تسويق تجارية قد تجذب انتباهك.

وبالطبع لديك كامل الحق في رفض خدمة تقنية القرار الآلي التي نقوم بتنفيذها، وفي تلك الحالة يمكنك التواصل معنا من خلال معلومات الاتصال المعلن عنها في هذه الاتفاقية أو من خلال الخيارات الأخرى ذات الصلة المعلن عنها في المنتجات والخدمات، وتطلب منا إيقاف هذه الخدمة. وفي الوقت نفسه، سنقوم بتنفيذ ذلك، طبقاً لكل من اللوائح الوطنية أو الإقليمية ذات الصلة أو المتطلبات التنظيمية المتعلقة بشأن حظر اتخاذ القرار الآلي.

قد نستخدم بيانات حسابك لأغراض التسويق، ونرسل لك من وقت لآخر معلومات حول المنتجات الجديدة والترقيات والمواد التسويقية الأخرى من TeraBox. يمكنك اختيار إلغاء الاشتراك في تلقي المواد التسويقية في أي وقت، عن طريق النقر على رابط "إلغاء الاشتراك" في أي رسائل بريد إلكتروني تتلقاها.

تقديم المعلومات الشخصية للطرف الثالث

يرجى العلم أنه لن يتم أبداً تقديم معلوماتك الشخصية إلى أي طرف ثالث دون الحصول على موافقة مسبقة منك، إلا في الحالات التالية:

(أ) أن يكون من الضروري أن نتعاون مع أياً من المنظمات الحكومية الوطنية أو الإقليمية أو مع أي من وكلائهم، من أجل مساعدتهم لأداء واجباتهم أو التزاماتهم وفقًا للقوانين واللوائح المعمول بها، وسوف يتم استبعاد هذا الإجراء في حالة كانت موافقتك مطلوبة.

(ب) وجود خطر جسيم يهدد حياة شخص ما أو ممتلكاته.

(ج) وجود حاجة خاصة لاستخدام تلك المعلومات لتحسين الصحة العامة أو تعزيز عملية النمو الصحي للشباب.

وفي حالة قيامنا بمشاركة معلوماتك الشخصية أو نقلها أو الكشف عنها في ظل تلك الظروف الاستثنائية التي تم ذكرها أعلاه، سنقوم باتباع مبادئ الحد الأدنى والضرورة للتمكن من حماية حقوقك ومصالحك المشروعة، كما سنقوم بالتسجيل التام لكل من: الأساس الخاص بمعالجة المعلومات ذات الصلة، والنطاق الخاص معالجة المعلومات، ومعلومات المستلم، إلخ، والتي تتضمن بالتحديد ما يلي:

(1) اسم وطرق التواصل التفصيلية الخاصين بمراقب البيانات ومسؤول حماية البيانات؛

(2) الهدف من عملية معالجة البيانات؛

(3) وصف أنواع البيانات الشخصية وأنواع الكيانات التي تستهدفها البياناتح؛

(4) الأنواع المستلمين الذين تم الإعلان عن البيانات الشخصية الخاصة بهم أو من المقرر أن يتم الإعلان عنها (ويتضمن ذلك المستلمين المتواجدين في دولة أو منظمة دولية تنتمي للطرف الثالث)؛

(5) السجل الخاص بنقل البيانات الشخصية إلى دول أو منظمات دولية تنتمي للطرف الثالث، بالإضافة إلى السجل الخاص بالضمانات المناسبة التي تم اتخاذها؛

(6) مسح الفترات المقدرة التي تم تحديدها لكل نوع من أنواع البيانات المختلفة؛

(7) وصف عام شامل لكل من إجراءات السلامة الفنية والتنظيمية.

المشاركة مع مستخدم آخر

عندما استخدامك لمميزات تعاون الفريق أو مشاركة الملفات التي يقدمها لك TeraBox، ستعرض خدماتنا معلومات الاسم المستعار الخاص بك والمعلومات الخاصة بجهازك وعنوان بريدك الإلكتروني، بالإضافة إلى معلومات الاستخدام، إلى المستخدمين الآخرين الذين يتعاونون معك أو الذين اخترت مشاركتهم معك بناءً على حقوقك. ومن شأن هذا أن يساعدك على القيام بعملية المزامنة مع الفريق الذي تنضم إليه، كما يمكن المستخدمين الآخرين من مشاركة الملفات والمجلدات معك.

مشاركة المعلومات الخاصة بك مع الطرف الثالث

يمكننا الاستعانة بعض الأطراف الثالثة الموثوقة بها (مثل دعم العملاء ومقدمي خدمات تكنولوجيا المعلومات-IT -) للقيام بمساعدتنا على تقديم خدماتنا وتحسينها والحفاظ عليها والترويج لها بشكل أفضل بكثير. وسوف تتمتع هذه الأطراف الثالثة بالحق في الوصول إلى المعلومات الخاصة بك لتتمكن من أداء المهام بالنيابة عنا، وسوف نتحمل المسؤولية عن معالجة معلوماتك من قبل الأطراف الثالثة وفقًا للتعليمات الخاصة بنا.

كما يمكننا مشاركة كل من: البنية التحتية والأنظمة والتقنيات مع الشركات التابعة لـ Flextech، وذلك من أجل تقديم هذه الخدمات وتحسينها والحفاظ عليها والترويج لها. ومن المقرر أن تستخدم هذه الشركات ذات الصلة المعلومات الخاصة بك معنا، كما ستستخدم أيضاً المعلومات التي قمت تم ذكرها أعلاه في قسم "محتوى المعلومات التي يتم جمعها والغرض من جمعها" من اجل الأغراض الموضحة في نفس الجزء. وسوف نتحمل بشكل كامل مسؤولية السماح لتلك الشركات باستخدام المعلومات الخاصة بك.

بمقدورك القيام باختيار تسجيل الدخول بحساب TeraBox الخاص بك من خلال خدمة طرف ثالث. وعند تسجيل الدخول باستخدام هذه الخدمات، فإنك بذلك تسمح لنا ولهذه الأطراف الثالثة بالقيام بتبادل المعلومات الموضحة في قسم "محتوى المعلومات التي يتم جمعها والغرض من جمعها" الموجود في سياسة الخصوصية هذه، وذلك حتى نتمكن تلك الأطراف الثالثة من تقديم خدماتها وتحسينها والحفاظ عليها وتعزيزها بمساعدتنا. وفي هذه الحالة، سيكون استخدام معلوماتك خاضع لسياسة الخصوصية وشروط الخدمة الخاصة بخدمة الطرف الثالث التي تختار تسديل الدخول من خلالها.

يمكننا إنشاء آلية مخرجات خاصة بنقل البيانات عبر الحدود استناداً إلى متطلبات اللائحة العامة لحماية البيانات (GDPR)، والقيام بتحديث تلك الآليات العابرة للحدود في الوقت المناسب بناءً على متطلبات اللائحة العامة لحماية البيانات (GDPR). مع العلم أن أي معالجة للبيانات الشخصية ستتم بما يتوافق المبادئ الأساسية للائحة العامة لحماية البيانات (GDPR)، أو ستتم من خلال الحصول بشكل مسبق على موافقة صاحب البيانات، أو ستكون تلبي أسباب مشروعة الأخرى. وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، سيتم وضع آليات إضافية لحماية البيانات، وذلك من أجل تلبية متطلبات معالجة البيانات الأساسية الخاصة باللائحة العامة لحماية البيانات.

كيفية حماية المعلومات وتخزينها

نمتلك فريق يبذل قصارى جهده للحفاظ على أمان المعلومات الخاصة بك واختبار الثغرات الأمنية التي قد تظهر. وبالإضافة إلى وجود عوامل الأمان مثل: المصادقة الثنائية، و تعطيل تشفير الملفات، وظهور التنبيهات عند ارتباط الأجهزة والتطبيقات الجديدة بحسابك، نحن لا نتوانى عن العمل من أجل الحفاظ على أمان المعلومات الخاصة بك. ونعمم تقنية آلية غرضها اكتشاف السلوكيات والمحتويات المريبة التي قد تلحق الضرر بخدماتنا أو بك أو بأي من المستخدمين الآخرين.

عند قيامك بإنشاء حساب في TeraBox، سيتم الاحتفاظ بالمعلومات التي تخزنها على خدماتنا طالما أن حسابك مازال موجود أو مازلنا نحتاج إلى تقديم الخدمة لك. وفي حالة كنت ترغب في حذف حسابك لدينا، فنرجو أن تتواصل معنا عبر البريد إلكتروني [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com)، وتعلمنا برغبتك في حذف معلوماتك وسنقوم بتنفيذ ذلك في غضون 30 يومًا من تلقي الطلب، ولكن، إذا: (1) لم نحذف المعلومات الخاصة بحسابك حتى التحقق من هوية المستخدم الخاصة بك، (2) تأخرت عملية الحذف من خوادمنا ومن تخزين النسخ الاحتياطية لدينا، (3) وجود حالة ضرورة، حينها يجوز لنا الاحتفاظ بتلك المعلومات إذا لزم الأمر وذلك امتثالاً لالتزاماتنا القانونية أو لحل النزاعات أو لتنفيذ حقوقنا المنصوص عليها في العقد.

سيتم احتفاظنا بمعلوماتك الشخصية طوال فترة تقديمنا للخدمة، ولكن في حالة تضمن القوانين واللوائح على أحكام مختلفة بشأن فترة الاحتفاظ بالمعلومات، أو موافقتك بقيامنا بالاحتفاظ بالمعلومات الخاصة بك لفترة أطول، أو وجود ضرورة لضمان سلامة وجودة خدماتنا، أو وجود الحاجة لتحقيق هدف حل النزاعات، أو وجود أمر يصعب تحقيقه من الناحية التقنية وغير ذلك من الظروف الأخرى، سيتم مد الفترة التي سنبقي فيها معلوماتك لدينا بعد انتهاء فترة الاحتفاظ بالمعلومات المذكورة أعلاه، وذلك وفقًا للقانون أو الاتفاقية ضمن نطاق معقول.

وبعد انتهاء فترة الاحتفاظ بالمعلومات الخاصة بك، سيتم حذف كافة معلوماتك الشخصية أو جعلها مجهولة الهوية وفقًا للقانون.

ويمكننا القيام بجمع معلومات المستخدمين واستخدامها وتخزينها ونقلها وفقًا لمبدأ "التقليل إلى الحد الأدنى"، ولكن سيتم إبلاغك بالغرض من استخدام المعلومات ذات الصلة والنطاق التي ستستخدم فيه من خلال اتفاقية المستخدم وسياسة الخصوصية، إلى جانب اللوائح ذات الصلة والنوافذ المنبثقة والإشعارات.

نحن نهتم اهتماماً جاد بأمن المعلومات. ولهذا أنشأنا فريقًا خاصًا ليكون مسؤول عن عملية تطوير وتطبيق مجموعة التقنيات وإجراءات الأمان المختلفة، كما أننا نجري فحوصات أمنية على كل من قادة الإدارة الأمنية والموظفين العاملين في المناصب الكبرى المتعلقة بالأمن، وفي الوقت نفسه قد أنشأنا نظام متكامل خاص بإدارة أمن المعلومات وكما وضعنا آلية للتعامل مع الحوادث الأمنية الداخلية. وبهذا فإننا سنخزن المعلومات الشخصية الخاصة بك ونحميها من خلال التدابير الأمنية المثلى والوسائل التقنية المناسبة التي تتوافق مع معايير الصناعة، وذلك لتجنب ضياعها أو الوصول غير المصرح به لها أو الإفصاح العلني عنها أو استخدامها بشكل غير مناسب أو تلفها أو فقدها أو ترسيبها. كما أننا سنتخذ كافة الإجراءات العملية العقلانية لحماية معلوماتك الشخصية. وبجانب هذا، سوف نستخدم تقنية التشفير من أجل ضمان سرية البيانات، وسوف نستخدم أيضاً آليات حماية موثوقة لمن أجل حماية البيانات من الهجمات التي قد تضر بها.

وسنقوم بتدريب وتقييم وعي الموظفين فيما يتعلق بأمان البيانات والقدرات الأمنية، وذلك لتعزيز وعيهم بأهمية حماية المعلومات الشخصية الخاصة بالمستخدمين. وبالإضافة إلى ذلك يتم إجراء مصادقة للهوية ومراقبة سلطة الموظفين المعنين بالتعامل مع المعلومات الشخصية، وتوقيع اتفاقات السرية مع كل من الموظفين وشركاء التعاون الذي يتعاملون بشكل مباشر بمعلوماتك الشخصية، والقيام بتوضيح مسؤوليات العمل وقواعد السلوك لهم، والتأكد من أن الموظفين المصرح لهم فقط هم من لديهم إمكانية الوصول إلى المعلومات الشخصية الخاصة بك. وفي حالة حدوث أي انتهاك لاتفاقيات السرية تلك، سيتم على الفور وبدون تردد إنهاء علاقة التعاون مع الشركة المنتهكة، كما سيتم مقاضاتهم طبقا للمسؤوليات القانونية ذات الصلة المتفق عليها، وبالطبع سيُطلب أيضًا من الموظفين الذين كان لديهم صلاحية الوصول إلى المعلومات الشخصية الاستمرار في الحفاظ على سرية تلك المعلومات حتى بعد ترك وظائفهم.

وهنا نؤكد عليك عزيزي المستخدم أن الإنترنت لا يعتبر بيئة آمنة تمامًا، ولذا عندما تتعامل مع مستخدمين آخرين من خلال برنامج اجتماعي تابع لطرف ثالث مُدرج في TeraBox أو من خلال البريد الإلكتروني أو الرسائل القصيرة وما إلى ذلك من الوسائل الأخرى وتشارك معهم معلومات حول موقعك الجغرافي أو معلومات التتبع الخاصة بك، لن يكون من المؤكد حينها أن يلتزم البرنامج التابع للطرف الثالث هذا بالتشفير الكامل لنقل المعلومات، أو أنه سيهتم بضمان أمان معلوماتك الشخصية.

كما نرجو أيضًا أن تتفهم أنه في مجال صناعة الإنترنت، حتى لو بذلنا قصارى جهدنا لتعزيز تدابير الأمان الخاصة بنا سيكون من المستحيل ضمان أمان المعلومات بنسبة 100%، وذلك نظرًا للتطور السريع للتكنولوجيا والقيود الخاصة بها والاحتمالية الدائمة بوجود وسائل للهجوم الضار بأنواعها المختلفة. كما يرجى العلم أن أنظمة وشبكات اتصال التي تستخدمها للتعامل مع منتجاتنا و/ أو خدماتنا قد تحدث بها مشكلات أمنية في دوائر خارجة عن سيطرتنا.

وطبقاً لنظام إدارة الأمن الخاص بنا، يتم تصنيف حوادث تسرب أو تلف أو ضياع المعلومات الشخصية على أنها أخطر الحوادث الأمنية. وبمجرد وقوع أي حادث منها، سيتم على الفور بدء تنفيذ أعلى خطة طوارئ بالشركة، وسيتم التعامل مع من قبل فريق الاستجابة للطوارئ الذي يتم تشكيله من إدارات متعددة.

ومن المقرر القيام بصياغة خطة طوارئ خاصة بحوادث أمان الشبكات، وذلك لتوفر القدرة على التعامل الفوري مع ثغرات النظام وفيروسات الكمبيوتر وهجوم الشبكات وحوادث الاختراق وغيرهم من المخاطر الأمنية الأخرى، والإجراءات العلاجية وإبلاغ السلطات المختصة وفقًا للوائح. وفي حالة وقوع حادث يهدد الأمن الشبكات، سيتم على الفور بدء تنفيذ خطة طوارئ المعنية، واتخاذ كافة التدابير المناسبة، وإبلاغ السلطات المختصة وفقًا للوائح ذات الصلة.

ولأن تسرب وتلف وفقد المعلومات الشخصية للمستخدمين من أخطر الحوادث الأمنية على مستوى الشركة، فنحن مسؤولين عن تنظيم تدريب بشكل دوري للموظفين على التدريبات الأمنية المتعلقة، وذلك من أجل منع حدوث مثل تلك الحوادث الأمنية الخطيرة. وفي حالة حدوث حادث مؤسف منهم، سيتم على الفور بدء تنفيذ خطة الاستجابة للطوارئ، وتشكيل فريق استجابة للطوارئ، وذلك من أجل تتبع السبب الذ أدى إلى وقوع الحادث وتقليل الضرر الناجم في أسرع وقت ممكن.

وبحالة وقوع حادث مؤسف يتعلق بأمن المعلومات الشخصية الخاصة بك، سنقوم فوراً بإبلاغك وفقًا لمتطلبات القوانين واللوائح بكل من: الظروف الأساسي للحادث والتأثير المحتمل لذلك الحادث الأمني، بالإضافة إلى التدابير التي اتخذناها أو سنتخذها للتعامل معه، وتقديم اقتراحات متعلقة بالمخاطر التي يمكنك منعها وتقليلها بنفسك، وغير ذلك من التدابير الإصلاحية التي يمكنك اتباعها، إلخ. وسيتم ذلك الإبلاغ الفور بالمعلومات ذات الصلة من خلال إشعارات الموقع أو الرسائل القصيرة أو المكالمات الهاتفية أو البريد الإلكتروني أو غير ذلك من معلومات الاتصال الأخرى التي كنت قد قدمتها لنا. وفي حالة تعثر إبلاغ كل مستخدم على حدى بالواقعة حينها، فسوف يتم الإعلان العام عنها بطريقة فعالة وعقلانية. كما أننا في الوقت نفسه، سنقوم وفقًا لمتطلبات السلطات التنظيمية بالمبادرة بالإبلاغ الفوري عن أي حوادث تتعلق بأمن المعلومات الشخصية. ويرجى العلم أنه وفقًا للقوانين واللوائح، إذا كانت الإجراءات التي سنقوم باتخاذها يمكنها أن تتجنب بشكل فعال الضرر الذي نجم عن حوادث تسريب وفقدان المعلومات والعبث بها، فبإمكاننا اختيار عدم إبلاغك بتلك الحوادث، ما لم تحتم السلطة التنظيمية علينا إبلاغك.

وأننا سوف نتخذ من متطلبات اللائحة العامة لحماية البيانات (GDPR) مرجع لنا، ونقوم بتحديد تدابير الأمان التقنية الملائمة بناءً على كل من: طبيعة البيانات التي تتم معالجتها ونطاقها وسياقها والغرض منها، بالإضافة إلى المخاطر التي يتعرض لها الأفراد. وبجانب ذلك سوف يتم إجراء الاختبارات والتقييمات بشكل منتظم لهذه التدابير المتخذة، وذلك للحفاظ على فاعليتها.

وعند وقع حادث تسريب للبيانات، سنقوم في أسرع وقت بإبلاغ الأشخاص المعنيين المتأثرين بالحادث، كما سنقوم في غضون 72 ساعة بإبلاغ الإدارة المختصة ذات الصلة. وفي حالة تعذر تقديم التقرير المتعلق في غضون 72 ساعة، فسيتم شرح سبب تأخير التقرير.

وبالتأكيد نحن نتخذ كافة التدابير الفنية والتنظيمية المناسبة لتحقيق هدف حماية البيانات، وذلك مثل: تقليل البيانات إلى الحد الأدنى وإدماج الضمانات اللازمة في عملية معالجة البيانات، وذلك من أجل حماية حقوق موضوعات البيانات، وضرورة التأكد من أن معالجة البيانات تتم لأغراض معينة.

مكان تخزين ومعالجة المعلومات الخاصة بك

عند تقديم خدماتنا، نقوم بتخزين ومعالجة ونقل معلومات المستخدمين في اليابان، وبموجب هذا أنت توافق على تقديم معلوماتك لتلك الجهة. كما أيضًا أن يتم التخزين المحلي للمعلومات الخاصة على الجهاز الذي تستخدمه للوصول إلى الخدمة.

كيفية التحكم في المعلومات الخاصة بك والوصول إليها

نضمن لك أنه بإمكانك ممارسة الحقوق التالية مع معلوماتك الشخصية، وذلك وفقًا للقوانين واللوائح والمعايير والممارسات الشائعة للبلدان والمناطق ذات الصلة، وفي حالة كان لديك أي أسئلة أو مطالبات تتعلق بممارسة الحقوق، يمكنك أيضًا التواصل معنا على البريد الإلكتروني [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com). كما يمكنك أن تقوم بعرض أو تغيير أو تحميل أو حذف أو مشاركة معلوماتك من خلال حساب TeraBox الخاص بك.

1\. حق الحصول على معلومات

عند رغبتك في معرفة نطاق حصول TeraBox على معلوماتك الشخصية ونطاق قيامه بتخزينها ومشاركتها، أو معرفة الغرض من معالجة TeraBox لمعلوماتك الشخصية، يمكنك حينها التواصل معنا للحصول على المعلومات ذات الصلة.

2\. حق التصحيح والاستكمال

عند اكتشاف خطأ في معلوماتك الشخصية التي تمت معالجتها بواسطتنا، فيحق لك القيام بتصحيح تلك المعلومات الخاطئة أو غير الكاملة. وبعد انتهائك من اجراء التحقق من الهوية، يمكنك إرسال طلبك للتصحيح أو الاستكمال إلينا من خلال قسم الملاحظات والإبلاغ عن الأخطاء أو من خلال معلومات الاتصال المذكورة أعلاه. وسنعاود الاتصال بك في أسرع وقت بعد استلامنا طلبك.

3\. حق الحذف

يمكنك أن تطلب من شركتنا حذف المعلومات الشخصية الخاصة بك في ظل أياً من الظروف التالية:

إذا قمنا بمعالجة معلوماتك الشخصية بشكل ينتهك القوانين واللوائح أو الاتفاق الذي عقدناه معك؛

إذا لم يعد الغرض من المعالجة ضرورياً، سواء كان قد تم تحقيق غرض المعالجة بالفعل، أو تعذر تحقيقه؛

إذا توقفنا عن تقديم المنتجات أو الخدمات، أو انتهت فترة الاحتفاظ بالمعلومات المتفق عليها؛

إذا سحبت موافقتك عن الاتفاقية؛

وإذا وجِدت أية ظروف أخرى منصوص عليها في القوانين واللوائح الإدارية.

وعند حذف المعلومات من خدماتنا، قد لا يتم على الفور حذف المعلومات المقابلة من نظام النسخ الاحتياطي، على أن يتم حذفها بشكل كامل عند تحديث النسخة الاحتياطية. ويرجى العلم والفهم بأنه إذا لم تنته فترة الاحتفاظ بالمعلومات المنصوص عليها في القوانين واللوائح الإدارية أو الموضحة في سياسة الخصوصية هذه، أو كان من الصعب حذف المعلومات الشخصية من الناحية التقنية، فإننا سنتوقف عن معالجة هذه المعلومات ولكننا سنستمر في الإبقاء عليها واتخاذ الإجراءات الأمنية اللازمة لحمايتها.

4\. سحب الموافقة

تتطلب كل وظيفة من وظائف العمل بعض المعلومات الشخصية الأساسية حتى يتم تنفيذها. ومن حقك أن تقوم بمنح الموافقة والتفويض أو سحبهما في أي وقت، وذلك فيما يتعلق بجمع واستخدام المعلومات الشخصية التي تُجمع بشكل إضافي.

ويمكنك مباشرة إغلاق أذونات النظام في جهازك، مثل أذونات الوصول إلى دليل الهاتف وألبوم الصور والكاميرا وغيرهم، كما يمكنك أيضاً تغيير نطاق الموافقة أو سحب التفويض الخاص بك.

وبعد سحب الموافقة، لن نتمكن من الاستمرار في الاستمتاع بالخدمات المقابلة لسحب موافقتك، كما أننا بالطبع لن نستمر في استخدام معلوماتك الشخصية ذات الصلة. ولكن قرارك بسحب الموافقة لن يكون له القدرة على التأثير على عملية معالجة معلوماتك الشخصية التي بدأ تنفيذها بناءً على موافقتك السابقة.

5\. حق الإلغاء

يمكنك إلغاء الحساب الذي قمت بتسجيله سابقاً. يمكنك إلغاء حسابك على برنامج TeraBox من خلال اتباع الخطوات التالية:

\[صورة الحساب\] – \[القائمة\] – \[الإعدادات\] – \[مركز الأمان\] – \[إلغاء الحساب\].

وبمجرد إلغاء حسابك، لن تكون قادرًا على استخدام خدمات برنامج Tearbox، لذا يُرجى توخي الحذر أثناء القيام بهذه العملية. وحرصًا منّا على حماية الحقوق والمصالح المشروعة الخاصة بك أو بالآخرين، سنقوم نحن باتخاذ القرار الذي سيحدد ما إذا كان سيتم الموافقة على طلب الإلغاء الخاص بك أم لا بناءً على استخدامك، فعلى سبيل المثال إن كانت العضوية الخاصة بك لم تنتهي بعد، أو ما زالت هناك بعض المواد الموجودة بحسابك، فلن نؤيد طلب على الفور. وبعد إلغاء حسابك، سنتوقف عن تقديم المنتجات والخدمات لك وسنحذف معلوماتك الشخصية وفقًا لمتطلباتك ما لم تنص القوانين والأنظمة على خلاف ذلك.

6\. حق النسخ وحق النقل

يحق لك نسخ المعلومات الشخصية التي قمنا بجمعها. كما يمكنك أيضًا أن تطلب منا نقل معلوماتك الشخصية إلى كيانات أخرى تحددها أنت إن كان هذا ممكنًا من الناحية التقنية، وذلك بما يطابق الشروط الواردة في القوانين واللوائح وبما يتوافق مع التوجيهات والشروط التي يتم تحديدها من قبل السلطات المختصة ذات الصلة.

وعند ممارستك للحقوق المتعلقة بكيانات المعلومات الشخصية المذكورة أعلاه، سنقوم في أسرع وقت ممكن بالمزامنة مع الأطراف الثالثة ذات الصلة، وذلك لضمان تحقيق حقوقك المذكورة أعلاه وفقًا للوائح والمتطلبات التنظيمية والإمكانية التقنية.

عندما يكون من الواضح أن طلبك غير معقول أو يتجاوز حدود الضرورة، وخاصة إذا كان الطلب مُكرر، فيمكننا:

(أ) فرض رسوم معقولة معينة تغطي المصروفات الإدارية الخاصة بتقديم المعلومات أو إجراء الاتصالات أو الإجراءات المقابلة؛ أو

(ب) رفض تنفيذ هذا الطلب.

ويمكنك التحكم في المعلومات الشخصية الخاصة بك المُحتفظ بها وفي كيفية جمعها واستخدامها ومشاركتها، وذلك وفقًا لـ (قانون حماية المعلومات الشخصية الياباني) ("المعلومات الشخصية المُحتفظ بها"). فعلى سبيل المثال، بإمكانك:

(‌أ) طلب الكشف عن المعلومات الشخصية المُحتفظ بها والتي يمكن أن تحدد هويتك

(‌ب) طلب القيام بتصحيح أو إضافة أو حذف المعلومات الشخصية الخاصة بك التي يمكن أن تحدد هوية الأفراد في حالة كونها معلومات خاطئة.

(‌ج) في حالة تم الحصول على المعلومات الشخصية المُحتفظ بها من قبلنا بشكل غير قانوني، أو استخدمنا المعلومات الشخصية المُحتفظ بها، فبرجاء حذف المعلومات الشخصية المُحتفظ بها أو التوقف فوراً عن استخدامها.

(‌د) في حالة أن قدمنا معلوماتك الشخصية المُحتفظ بها إلى طرف ثالث بشكل غير قانوني، فبرجاء التوقف فورًا عن تقديم معلوماتك الشخصية المحتفظ بها.

التغيير

عند تنفيذ إعادة تنظيم أو اندماج Flextech أو الاستحواذ عليها أو بيع أصولها، من الممكن أن يتم نقل معلوماتك إلى الكيان الباقي أو المستحوذ أو اللاحق الذي سيتولى الشركة نتيجة للصفقة. وحينها سيتم بكل تأكيد إخطارك بأي صفقة من هذا القبيل (عبر رسالة يتم إرسالها إلى عنوان البريد الإلكتروني المرتبط بحسابك مثلاً) وتقديم لك الخيارات المتاحة أمامك حينها.

من الوارد أن يتم إحداث تعديلات بسياسة الخصوصية هذه من وقت لآخر، وسيتم دائماً نشر أحدث إصدار من الاتفاقية على موقع TeraBox الإلكتروني. وفي حالة وجود أي تعديل قد يؤثر بشكل أساسي على حقوقك، سوف نقوم بإخطارك به.

تواصل معنا:

عند امتلاكك لأي أسئلة أو مخاوف بشأن TeraBox وخدماته وحقوق الخصوصية الخاصة، برجاء التواصل معنا عبر البريد الإلكتروني: [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com).

Política de Privacidade do TeraBox

Política de Privacidade do TeraBox

Conteúdo e finalidade da coleta de informações

Fornecimento de informações pessoais a terceiros

Compartilhar com outros usuários

Podemos compartilhar suas informações com terceiros

Como protegemos e armazenamos suas informações

Onde armazenamos e processamos suas informações

Como você controla e acessa suas informações

{{ $t('termsOfServicePrivacyPolicy.age.title') }}

Alteração

Contate-nos:

Política de Privacidade do TeraBox

Data de Lançamento: 18 de abril de 2023

Data de Entrada em Vigor: 18 de abril de 2023

Obrigado por usar o TeraBox! O TeraBox é fornecido a você pela Flextech Inc. (“Flextech” ou “Nós”). Dedicamo-nos à proteção de sua privacidade. Esta Política de Privacidade define como coletamos, armazenamos, processamos, compartilhamos e usamos suas informações quando você usa nosso site, software e serviço ("serviços").

Coletaremos e usaremos suas informações pessoais de acordo com os princípios de legalidade, justiça e necessidade. Especificamente, coletamos e processamos suas informações pessoais para fornecer a você as funções de negócios correspondentes. Nas funções correspondentes, se você fornecer informações pessoais de terceiros, por favor, certifique-se de obter a autorização do titular relevante, e nos reservamos o direito de verificar a fonte legal de tais informações pessoais a qualquer momento.

Seguiremos rigorosamente os requisitos das leis, e regulamentos e solicitaremos seu consentimento separado em circunstâncias específicas. Além desta Política de Privacidade, também podemos explicar nossas regras para processar suas informações pessoais através de notificações em páginas de produtos, janelas pop-up, empurrão de informações, etc.. O processamento de informações pessoais correspondentes a funções de negócios específicas estará sujeito a regras específicas, que têm o mesmo efeito desta Política de Privacidade.

Atenção: Nas seguintes situações, a coleta, uso, compartilhamento, transferência e divulgação pública de informações pessoais não requerem sua autorização e consentimento prévios:

Diretamente relacionado com a segurança nacional e a segurança da defesa nacional;

Necessário para a celebração e cumprimento de um contrato em que o indivíduo seja parte;

Necessário para o cumprimento de deveres ou obrigações legais;

Necessário para responder a uma emergência de saúde pública ou para proteger a vida, a saúde e os bens de pessoas físicas em uma situação de emergência;

Diretamente relacionado à investigação criminal, acusação, julgamento e execução de sentença;

Para proteger seus direitos e interesses legais importantes ou de outro indivíduo, como a vida ou a propriedade, mas é difícil obter seu consentimento;

Coletar informações pessoais que você tenha divulgado ao público por conta própria ou que tenham sido legalmente divulgadas, dentro de limites razoáveis de acordo com as disposições de leis e regulamentos;

Coletar suas informações pessoais de divulgações públicas lícitas, tais como relatórios de notícias legais, divulgação de informações governamentais e outras fontes, dentro de limites razoáveis de acordo com as disposições de leis e regulamentos;

Realizar reportagens, supervisão da opinião pública e outros atos para interesse público, e processar informações pessoais dentro de limites razoáveis;

Quando é necessário que uma instituição de pesquisa acadêmica realize pesquisas estatísticas ou acadêmicas com base em interesses públicos e quando os resultados da pesquisa ou descrição acadêmica são disponibilizados ao público, as informações pessoais contidas nos resultados são desidentificadas;

Outras circunstâncias estipuladas por leis e regulamentos relevantes.

Conteúdo e finalidade da coleta de informações

A tabela abaixo lista os tipos de informações que você nos envia ao usar estes serviços, e as finalidades para as quais podemos usá-las. Coletamos e usamos as seguintes informações para fornecer, otimizar, proteger e promover nossos serviços.

| Tipo de informação | Finalidade de coleta |
| --- | --- |
| Informação de conta. Coletaremos o endereço de e-mail, número de telefone e outras informações que você nos fornecer ao realizar algumas operações (como registrar conta) (se você usar a conta SNS para fazer login, receberemos seu apelido e dados de imagem de perfil de SNS), e associe estas informações à sua conta. | Podemos usar estas informações para identificá-lo como o proprietário da conta, e para proteger a segurança de sua conta. Podemos coletar estas informações quando você faz login na sua conta. |
| Materiais de usuário. Materiais que você armazena no TeraBox, como arquivos, documentos, fotos, vídeo e áudio (“Materiais de Usuário”). | Podemos armazenar, processar e transmitir Materiais de Usuário e informações relacionadas a eles para garantir a operação adequada dos serviços e permitir que você colabore com outras pessoas e trabalhe em múltiplos dispositivos e serviços. Essas informações relacionadas incluem suas informações de arquivo de configuração, tamanho de arquivo, data e hora de upload e atividade de uso. |
| Informações de uso. Informações sobre como usar os serviços, incluindo operações realizadas na conta, como edição, visualização, criação e movimentação de arquivos ou pastas. | Podemos usar estas informações para fornecer, melhorar e promover os serviços, e para proteger os usuários do TeraBox. |
| Informações de dispositivo. Informações sobre o dispositivo usado para acessar os serviços, como endereço IP, navegador e informações do dispositivo, páginas da web visitadas antes de acessar TeraBox, identificadores associados ao dispositivo e informações de localização dependendo das configurações do dispositivo. | Podemos usar estas informações para melhorar e proteger nossos serviços. |
| Cookies. Quando você visita o TeraBox, um pequeno texto enviado ao seu navegador pelo site. Você pode configurar seu navegador para não aceitar cookies, mas isso pode afetar a funcionalidade dos serviços. | Podemos usar cookies e tecnologias semelhantes para fornecer, melhorar, proteger e promover os serviços. Cookies nos permitem lembrar seu nome de usuário, entender seu uso de serviços, e melhorar os serviços de acordo com estas informações. Os provedores de serviços terceirizados com os quais colaboramos também podem usar cookies e tecnologias semelhantes. |
| Informações de contato. Você pode usar a função de compartilhamento do TeraBox para compartilhar seus dados e informações com contatos, números de celular, endereços de e-mail (como Facebook, Twitter) na agenda telefônica. As informações na agenda telefônica são informações pessoais e confidenciais. A recusa em fornecer essas informações apenas o impossibilitará de usar as funções acima, mas não afetará o uso normal de outras funções do TeraBox e serviços relacionados. | Você pode optar por permitir que o TeraBox acesse suas informações de contato para facilitar determinadas operações, como compartilhar e colaborar com outras pessoas em processar seus dados, enviar mensagens e convidar outras pessoas para usar os serviços do TeraBox através de enviar e-mail. Esta operação requer que você habilite as permissões da agenda telefônica. Armazenaremos essas informações em nossos servidores para seu uso. Por favor, considere bem a confiabilidade do destinatário da mensagem antes de compartilhar. Ao mesmo tempo, recomendamos que você verifique as declarações de privacidade das redes sociais ou provedores de serviços terceirizados para entender como eles lidam com suas informações, para tomar decisões prudentes. |
| Prancheta. Quando você registra uma conta Terabox através do código de convite de outra pessoa, acessa links de arquivos compartilhados por outros usuários, adiciona amigos através de uma senha ou obtém serviços de adesão através de um código de resgate, leremos as informações da sua área de transferência. | Acessaremos as informações da área de transferência para ajudá-lo a abrir o arquivo correspondente ao link, identificar o usuário correspondente à senha e ao código de convite, ou para resgatar serviços de membros para você. Nunca leremos sua área de transferência para qualquer outro propósito. |

Você pode criar a conta do TeraBox através do número do seu celular, e preencher as informações da sua conta.

Para atender aos requisitos obrigatórios de leis e regulamentos, para fornecer as necessidades de produtos ou serviços ou com base em sua demanda por proteção aprimorada de conta, quando usar determinados serviços do TeraBox ou tiver mais outras necessidades, você precisa de fornecer seu nome verdadeiro, número de ID e informações faciais para concluir a autenticação da conta. Para verificar a exatidão e integridade das informações que você fornece ou para proteger a segurança de sua conta, podemos comparar e verificar as informações de nome real que você fornece ao TeraBox com suas informações correspondentes armazenadas por instituições permitidas por leis e regulamentos ou autorizadas por agências governamentais.

As informações acima são coletadas para fornecer serviços confiáveis e seguros e para fins comerciais legítimos. Nós ou nossos parceiros solicitaremos seu consentimento prévio antes de processar suas informações para qualquer outra finalidade.

Você concorda que iremos agregar, identificar, analisar, perfilar ou processar posteriormente as informações pessoais que você fornecer de forma ativa ou passiva neste serviço através da nossa própria tecnologia ou da parte confiada, e informações de rótulo de vários tipos e diferentes granularidades que podem refletir seus hábitos de comportamento, hobbies ou status de crédito (doravante referido como "informações de rótulo"). Usaremos informações de rótulo para cenários e propósitos específicos para tomar decisões automatizadas e enviar informações de exibição personalizadas e/ou informações de marketing comercial para você.

Você tem o direito de recusar nossos serviços técnicos de tomada de decisão automatizada. Você pode entrar em contato conosco através das informações de contato publicadas neste acordo ou solicitar que paremos através dos interruptores relevantes no serviço do produto. Ao mesmo tempo, de acordo com as leis e regulamentos ou requisitos regulamentares de países ou regiões relevantes sobre a proibição de tomada de decisão automatizada, também implementaremos conforme os requisitos.

Podemos usar os seus Dados da Conta para fins de marketing e enviar informações sobre novos produtos, atualizações e outros materiais de marketing de TeraBox para você ocasionalmente. Você pode optar por não receber os materiais de marketing a qualquer momento, clicando no link "cancelar assinatura" em qualquer e-mail que receber.

Fornecimento de informações pessoais a terceiros

Não forneceremos informações pessoais a terceiros sem o seu consentimento prévio, a menos que seja necessário para qualquer uma das seguintes circunstâncias:

(a) Devemos cooperar com organizações governamentais nacionais ou regionais ou seus agentes para desempenhar suas funções ou obrigações de acordo com as leis e regulamentos aplicáveis. Se seu consentimento for necessário, tal desempenho pode ser excluído;

(b) Existe um risco significativo para a vida ou propriedade de alguém;

(c) Existe uma necessidade particular de melhorar a saúde pública ou promover o desenvolvimento saudável da juventude;

Para o compartilhamento, transferência ou divulgação de suas informações pessoais sob as exceções acima mencionadas, registraremos a base para processar as informações relevantes, o escopo das informações de processamento e as informações do destinatário, incluindo os seguintes conteúdos, e seguiremos o princípio de mínimo e necessário para proteger seus direitos e interesses legítimos.

(1) Nome e detalhes de contato do controlador de dados, oficial de proteção de dados;

(2) Finalidade do processamento de dados;

(3) Descrição do tipo de titular dos dados e do tipo de dados pessoais;

(4) Tipos de destinatários a quem os dados pessoais foram ou serão divulgados (incluindo destinatários localizados em países terceiros ou organizações internacionais);

(5) Registros das transferências de dados pessoais para países terceiros ou organizações internacionais e registros das salvaguardas adequadas;

(6) Prazos estimados para exclusão de diferentes tipos de dados;

(7) Descrição geral das medidas de segurança técnicas e organizacionais.

Compartilhar com outros usuários

Quando você usa as funções de colaboração em equipe ou compartilhamento de arquivos fornecidas pelo TeraBox, nossos serviços exibem seu apelido, dispositivo, endereço de e-mail e informações de uso para outros usuários que cooperam com você ou optam por compartilhar com você de acordo com suas permissões. Isso ajudará você a sincronizar com as equipes às quais deseja juntar-se, e ajudará outros usuários a compartilhar arquivos e pastas com você.

Podemos compartilhar suas informações com terceiros

Podemos usar terceiros confiáveis (como suporte ao cliente e provedores de serviços de TI) para nos ajudar a fornecer, otimizar, proteger e promover melhor nossos serviços. Estes terceiros podem acessar as suas informações para executar tarefas em nosso nome, e continuamos sendo responsáveis pelo processamento de suas informações pelo terceiro de acordo com nossas instruções.

Podemos compartilhar infraestrutura, sistemas e tecnologia com afiliadas da Flextech para fornecer, melhorar, proteger e promover estes serviços. Estas afiliadas compartilharão suas informações conosco e usarão as informações que você listou na seção "Conteúdo e finalidade da coleta de informações" para as finalidades descritas na mesma. Seremos responsáveis pelo uso de suas informações por essas empresas.

Você pode optar por se conectar à sua conta do TeraBox através do serviço terceirizado. Através de conectar tais serviços, você permite que estes terceiros e nós troquemos as informações listadas na seção "Conteúdo e finalidade da coleta de informações" desta Política de Privacidade para que estes terceiros e nós possamos fornecer, melhorar, proteger e promover seus serviços. Nesses casos, o uso de suas informações será regido pela política de privacidade e pelos termos de serviço elaborados pelo serviço terceirizado através do qual você optar por se conectar.

Estabeleceremos o mecanismo de exportação para transferência de dados transfronteiriça com referência aos requisitos de GDPR, e atualizaremos oportunamente seu mecanismo transfronteiriço com base nos requisitos de GDPR. Qualquer processamento de dados pessoais atenderá às disposições dos princípios fundamentais de GDPR, obterá o consentimento válido do titular dos dados ou satisfará outros motivos legítimos. Além disso, configurará o mecanismo adicional para proteger os dados, de modo a atender aos requisitos substantivos de GDPR para processamento de dados.

Como protegemos e armazenamos suas informações

Temos uma equipe dedicada a manter suas informações seguras e testar vulnerabilidades. Além da dupla autenticação, criptografia de arquivos proibida e alertas quando novos dispositivos e aplicativos vinculam sua conta, continuamos trabalhando com esforço para garantir a segurança de suas informações. Implantamos tecnologias automatizadas para detectar comportamento e conteúdo abusivos que possam prejudicar nossos serviços, você ou outros usuários.

Quando você se registra uma conta do TeraBox, nós reteremos as informações que você armazena em nossos serviços enquanto sua conta existir ou enquanto precisarmos de fornecer-lhe os serviços. Se você deseja excluir sua conta, por favor, envie e-mail para [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) para excluir suas informações, e concluiremos isso em até 30 dias após o recebimento de sua solicitação; No entanto, se: (1) não excluirmos ou deletarmos as informações de sua conta antes de verificar sua identidade de usuário; (2) a exclusão de nossos servidores e armazenamento de backup pode ser atrasada, (3) se necessário, podemos reter essas informações para cumprir nossas obrigações legais, resolver disputas ou fazer valer nossos direitos sob os termos do contrato.

Armazenamos suas informações pessoais dentro do período necessário para fornecer serviços, mas sob as circunstâncias, como as leis e regulamentos têm outras disposições sobre o período de armazenamento, você concorda em reter um período mais longo, garantir a segurança e a qualidade dos serviços, atingir o objetivo da resolução de disputas, tecnicamente difícil de realizar, etc., após o término do período de armazenamento acima mencionado, estenderemos o período de armazenamento de acordo com a lei, o acordo ou dentro de um escopo razoável.

Depois que o período de armazenamento for excedido, excluiremos ou anonimizaremos suas informações pessoais de acordo com a lei. Coletaremos, usaremos, armazenaremos e transmitiremos as informações de usuário com base no princípio de "minimização", e informaremos sobre a finalidade e o escopo de uso de informações relevantes através do acordo de usuário e da política de privacidade, bem como regras relacionadas, janelas pop-up , notificações, etc..

Prestamos muita atenção à segurança da informações. Criamos uma equipe dedicada responsável pelo desenvolvimento e aplicação de várias tecnologias e procedimentos de segurança, etc.. Conduziremos verificações de antecedentes de segurança da pessoa responsável pela gestão de segurança e do pessoal em posições-chave de segurança, e estabelecemos um sistema abrangente de gestão de segurança da informação e um mecanismo interno de tratamento de incidentes de segurança, etc.. Tomaremos medidas de segurança padrão do setor e meios técnicos apropriados para armazenar e proteger suas informações pessoais contra perda, acesso não autorizado, divulgação pública, uso, destruição, omissão ou vazamento. Tomaremos todas as medidas razoáveis e viáveis para proteger suas informações pessoais. Usaremos tecnologia de criptografia para garantir a confidencialidade dos dados; Usaremos mecanismos de proteção confiáveis para evitar ataques maliciosos aos dados.

Realizaremos formação de conscientização de segurança de dados e, treinamento e avaliação de capacidade de segurança aos funcionários para fortalecer a conscientização dos funcionários sobre a importância de proteger informações pessoais. Conduziremos autenticação de identidade e controle de permissões para funcionários que lidam com informações pessoais, e assinaremos acordos de confidencialidade com funcionários e parceiros que tenham acesso às suas informações pessoais, esclarecemos as responsabilidades de trabalho e o código de conduta para garantir que apenas pessoas autorizadas possam acessar informações pessoais. Caso haja qualquer violação do acordo de confidencialidade, a relação de cooperação com a empresa será rescindida imediatamente, e a responsabilidade legal relevante será responsabilizadas. Os funcionários que tiverem acesso a informações pessoais também devem ter os requisitos de confidencialidade quando deixarem o cargo.

Nós o lembramos de prestar atenção que a Internet não é um ambiente absolutamente seguro. Quando você interage com outros usuários através do software social de terceiros, e-mail, SMS, etc. incorporado no TeraBox com sua geolocalização ou informações sobre o paradeiro, é incerto se o software de terceiros está criptografando totalmente a transmissão das informações, portanto tenha cuidado para garantir a segurança de suas informações pessoais.

Pedimos também que você compreenda que na indústria da Internet, devido às limitações e ao rápido desenvolvimento da tecnologia e à possibilidade de vários ataques maliciosos, mesmo que façamos o nosso melhor para reforçar as medidas de segurança, é impossível garantir sempre 100% segurança das informações. Por favor, entenda que os sistemas e redes de comunicação que você usa ao usar nossos produtos e/ou serviços podem ter problemas de segurança em outros links fora de nosso controle.

De acordo com nosso sistema de gerenciamento de segurança, o vazamento, destruição ou perda de informações pessoais é listado como o incidente de segurança mais grave. Uma vez ocorrido, o plano de emergência de mais alto nível da empresa será acionado e uma equipe conjunta de resposta a emergências será formada por vários departamentos para lidar com isso.

Formularemos planos de emergência para incidentes de segurança de rede e lidaremos com vulnerabilidades do sistema, vírus de computador, ataques de rede, invasões de rede e outros riscos de segurança de forma oportuna. No caso de um incidente que coloque em risco a segurança da rede, ativaremos imediatamente o plano de emergência, tomaremos as medidas corretivas correspondentes e informaremos as autoridades competentes de acordo com os regulamentos.

Vazamento, destruição e perda de informações pessoais são os principais incidentes de segurança no nível da empresa. Seremos responsáveis por organizar regularmente os membros do grupo de trabalho para conduzir exercícios de segurança para evitar que tais incidentes de segurança aconteçam. No caso de um incidente infeliz, acionaremos o plano de emergência de acordo com a prioridade máxima, formaremos uma equipe de resposta a emergências para rastrear a causa e reduzir os danos no menor tempo possível.

Após a ocorrência de um incidente infeliz de segurança de informações pessoais, de acordo com o requisitos de leis e regulamentos, nós o informaremos oportunamente sobre a situação básica e o possível impacto do incidente de segurança, as medidas de tratamento que tomámos ou tomaremos, sugestões de riscos que você pode prevenir e mitigar por conta própria, medidas corretivas para você, etc.. Iremos informá-lo oportunamente sobre a situação relacionada ao incidente através de notificação no site, notificação por SMS, chamada telefônica, e-mail e outros detalhes de contato que você reservou, e se for difícil informá-lo individualmente, tomaremos medidas razoáveis e eficazes para fazer anúncios. Ao mesmo tempo, também relataremos ativamente o tratamento de incidentes de segurança de informações pessoais de acordo com os requisitos das autoridades reguladoras. Por favor, entenda que, de acordo com as leis e regulamentos, se as medidas que tomamos puderem efetivamente impedir o vazamento, adulteração e perda de informações que causem danos, podemos optar por não notificá-lo sobre o incidente de segurança de informações pessoais, a menos que o departamento de supervisão exija notificação para você.

Faremos referência aos requisitos de GDPR, selecionaremos medidas técnicas de proteção de segurança apropriadas com base na natureza, escopo, contexto e finalidade do processamento de dados e nos riscos para os indivíduos, e conduziremos testes e avaliações regulares para manter a eficácia das medidas tomadas.

Quando ocorrer um vazamento de dados, notificaremos as pessoas afetadas pelo vazamento de informações o mais rápido possível e, dentro de 72 horas, reportaremos à autoridade competente relevante. Quando o relatório não puder ser feito dentro de 72 horas, explicaremos as razões de atraso no relatório.

Implementamos medidas técnicas e organizacionais adequadas para atingir os objetivos de proteção de dados, como a minimização de dados e a integração das salvaguardas necessárias no processamento de dados, a fim de proteger os direitos dos titulares de dados e, por padrão, garantir que os dados processados para uma finalidade específica sejam necessário.

Onde armazenamos e processamos suas informações

Ao fornecer os serviços, podemos armazenar, processar e transferir suas informações no Japão, e você concorda em fornecer suas informações. Suas informações também podem ser armazenadas no dispositivo de armazenamento local que você usa para acessar os serviços.

Como você controla e acessa suas informações

De acordo com as leis, regulamentos, padrões e práticas comuns dos países e regiões relevantes, garantimos que você exerça os seguintes direitos com relação às suas próprias informações pessoais. Se você tiver alguma dúvida ou reclamação sobre o exercício dos direitos, também entrar em contato conosco através de [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com). Você pode visualizar, alterar, baixar, excluir ou compartilhar suas informações de sua conta do TeraBox.

1\. Direito de acesso

Quando você quiser saber o escopo de suas informações pessoais adquiridas, armazenadas, compartilhadas, etc. pelo TeraBox ou as finalidades para as quais suas informações pessoais são processadas, você pode entrar em contato conosco para obter o conteúdo relevante.

2\. Direito de correção e complemento

Quando você descobrir que as informações pessoais que processamos sobre você estão erradas, você tem o direito de corrigir as informações erradas ou incompletas. Depois de verificar sua identidade, você pode nos submeter sua solicitação de correção ou complemento através de feedback e relatório de erros ou das informações de contato mencionadas acima. Depois de recebermos sua solicitação, daremos um feedback o mais rápido possível.

3\. Direito de exclusão

Você pode nos solicitar a exclusão de suas informações pessoais nas seguintes circunstâncias:

Se processarmos suas informações pessoais em violação de leis e regulamentos ou de nosso acordo com você;

Se nosso objetivo de processamento foi alcançado, não pode ser alcançado ou não é mais necessário para alcançar o objetivo de processamento;

Se deixarmos de fornecer produtos ou serviços ou se o período de armazenamento tiver expirado;

Se você retirar seu consentimento;

Outras circunstâncias estipuladas por leis e regulamentos administrativos.

Depois de excluir as informações de nossos serviços, não podemos excluir as informações correspondentes no sistema de backup imediatamente, mas excluiremos as informações quando o backup for atualizado. Por favor, saiba e entenda que, se o período de armazenamento estipulado por leis, regulamentos administrativos ou descrito nesta política de privacidade não tiver expirado, ou se for tecnicamente difícil excluir informações pessoais, pararemos de processamentos excepto armazenamento e tomada das medidas de proteção de segurança necessárias.

4\. Retirada do consentimento

Cada função de negócios requer algumas informações pessoais básicas para ser concluída. Para a coleta e uso de informações pessoais coletadas adicionalmente, você pode dar ou retirar sua autorização e consentimento a qualquer momento.

Você pode fechar diretamente as permissões do sistema, como contatos, álbum de fotos, câmeras, etc. no sistema do dispositivo, alterar o escopo do consentimento ou retirar sua autorização.

Se você retirar seu consentimento, não poderemos mais lhe fornecer os serviços correspondentes à retirada do seu consentimento, e não utilizaremos mais suas informações pessoais correspondentes. No entanto, sua decisão de retirar seu consentimento não afetará o processamento anterior de informações pessoais realizado com base em seu consentimento.

5\. Direito de anulação

Você pode anular a conta registrada anteriormente. Você também pode anular sua conta no TeraBox através do seguinte caminho:

\[Imagem do perfil da conta\] - \[Menu\] - \[Configurações\] - \[Centro de segurança\] - \[Anulação da conta\].

Uma vez anulada sua conta, você não poderá usar os serviços dos produtos do Tearbox, portanto, por favor opere com cuidado. A fim de proteger os direitos e interesses legítimos de você ou de outras pessoas, julgaremos se devemos apoiar sua solicitação de anulação com base em seu uso. Por exemplo, se você tiver benefícios de Premium não consumidos ou ainda houver dados em sua conta, não apoiaremos imediatamente à sua solicitação. A menos que estipulado de outra forma por leis e regulamentos, deixaremos de lhe fornecer produtos e serviços depois de anular sua conta, e excluiremos suas informações pessoais de acordo com suas necessidades.

6\. Direitos de cópia e portabilidade

Você tem o direito de copiar suas informações pessoais que coletamos. Nas condições estipuladas por leis e regulamentos, e em conformidade com as instruções e condições estipuladas pelas autoridades competentes relevantes, se for tecnicamente viável, você também pode nos solicitar a transferência de suas informações pessoais para outros titulares designados por você.

Quando você exerce os direitos relevantes do titular de informações pessoais mencionado acima, também sincronizaremos com o terceiro relevante o mais rápido possível para garantir que seus direitos mencionados acima sejam realizados em conformidade com leis e regulamentos, requisitos regulamentares e viabilidade técnica.

Quando sua solicitação for claramente injustificada ou exceder o limite necessário, especialmente quando a solicitação for repetida, poderemos:

(a) Combinado com os custos administrativos de fornecer informações, comunicações ou ações correspondentes, cobrar uma determinada taxa razoável; ou

(b) Recusar em agir pela solicitação.

Você pode controlar as informações pessoais que retém e seus métodos de coleta, uso e compartilhamento de acordo com a Lei Japonesa de Proteção de Informações Pessoais ("Informações Pessoais Retidas"). Por exemplo, você pode:

a. Solicitar a divulgação das informações pessoais retidas que possam identificá-lo.

b. Solicitar a correção, adição ou exclusão do conteúdo das informações pessoais retidas quando o conteúdo das informações pessoais retidas que podem identificar um indivíduo não for verdadeiro.

c. Se suas informações pessoais retidas forem obtidas ilegalmente por nós, ou se estivermos usando suas informações pessoais retidas, por favor, exclua ou pare de usar suas informações pessoais retidas imediatamente.

d. Se fornecermos ilegalmente suas informações pessoais retidas a terceiros, por favor, pare de fornecer suas informações pessoais retidas imediatamente.

Alteração

No caso de reorganização, fusão ou aquisição da Flextech ou venda de nossos ativos, suas informações podem ser transferidas para a entidade sobrevivente, adquirente ou sucessora desta transação. Iremos notificá-lo sobre qualquer transação deste tipo (por exemplo, por mensagem para o endereço de e-mail associado à sua conta), e descrever suas opções nesse caso.

Esta política de privacidade pode ser alterada de tempos em tempos. Publicaremos a versão mais recente no site do TeraBox. Nós o notificaremos se tais alterações afetarem materialmente seus direitos.

Contate-nos:

Se você tiver qualquer dúvida ou preocupação sobre TeraBox, nossos serviços e privacidade, por favor, entre em contato conosco através de [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com).

Chính sách về quyền riêng tư TeraBox

Chính sách về quyền riêng tư TeraBox

Nội dung và mục đích của việc thu thập thông tin

Cung cấp thông tin cá nhân cho bên thứ 3

Chia sẻ với người dùng khác

Chúng tôi có thể sẽ chia sẻ thông tin của bạn cho bên thứ 3

Chúng tôi bảo vệ và lưu trữ thông tin của bạn như thế nào

Chúng tôi lưu trữ và xử lý thông tin của bạn ở đâu

Bạn kiểm soát và truy cập thông tin của mình như thế nào

{{ $t('termsOfServicePrivacyPolicy.age.title') }}

Thay đổi

Liên hệ chúng tôi:

Chính sách về quyền riêng tư TeraBox

Thời gian công bố: ngày 18 tháng 4 năm 2023

Thời gian có hiệu lực: ngày 18 tháng 4 năm 2023

Cảm ơn bạn sử dụng TeraBox! TeraBox do Flextech Inc. (“Flextech” hoặc “Chúng tôi”) cung cấp đến bạn. Chúng tôi nỗ lực hết sức để bảo vệ sự riêng tư của bạn. Chính sách bảo mật này quy định chúng tôi sẽ thu thập, lưu trữ, xử lý, chia sẻ và sử dụng thông tin của bạn như thế nào khi bạn sử dụng trang web, phần mềm và dịch vụ (“Dịch vụ”) của chúng tôi.

Chúng tôi sẽ thu thập và sử dụng thông tin cá nhân của bạn tuân theo nguyên tắc hợp pháp, chính đáng và cần thiết. Cụ thể, chúng tôi sẽ thu thập và xử lý thông tin cá nhân của bạn để cung cấp cho bạn các tính năng nghiệp vụ tương ứng. Trong tính năng tương ứng, nếu như bạn cung cấp thông tin cá nhân của người khác, bạn vui lòng đảm bảo rằng đã được chủ thể liên quan cho phép, chúng tôi có quyền lưu giữ và kiểm tra nguồn gốc hợp pháp của thông tin cá nhân đó bất cứ lúc nào.

Chúng tôi sẽ tuân thủ nghiêm ngặt theo các yêu cầu quy định của pháp luật, và sẽ xin phép sự đồng ý riêng của bạn trong trường hợp cụ thể. Ngoài chính sách quyền riêng tư này, chúng tôi có thể sẽ giải thích cho bạn quy tắc chúng tôi xử lý thông tin cá nhân của bạn thông qua các phương thức như quảng cáo trên trang sản phẩm, cửa sổ nhắc nhở, giới thiệu thông tin..., tình hình xử lý thông tin cá nhân tương ứng với tính năng nghiệp vụ cụ thể sẽ lấy quy tắc cụ thể làm chuẩn, quy tắc cụ thể có hiệu lực tương đương với chính sách quyền riêng tư này.

Vui lòng chú ý：Trong các trường hợp dưới đây, việc thu thập, sử dụng, chia sẻ, chuyển nhượng và tiết lộ công khai thông tin cá nhân không cần có được sự cho phép và đồng ý trước của bạn:

Liên quan trực tiếp đến an ninh quốc gia, an ninh quốc phòng;

cần thiết cho việc ký kết, thực hiện hợp đồng trong đó cá nhân là một bên đương sự;

cần thiết cho việc thực hiện trách nhiệm hoặc nghĩa vụ theo quy định của pháp luật;

cần thiết cho việc ứng phó với tình trạng y tế công cộng khẩn cấp, hoặc để bảo vệ sức khỏe, tính mạng và an toàn tài sản của công dân trong các trường hợp khẩn cấp;

liên quan trực tiếp đến điều tra phạm tội, truy tố, xét xử và thi hành án...;

để bảo vệ quyền lợi hợp pháp quan trọng về tính mạng, tài sản... của bạn hoặc người khác nhưng lại rất khó được sự đồng ý của bản thân người đó;

thu thập thông tin cá nhân bạn tự công khai cho công chúng hoặc đã công khai hợp pháp trong phạm vi hợp lý theo quy định của pháp luật;

thu thập thông tin của bạn trong phạm vi hợp lý từ thông tin được tiết lộ công khai hợp pháp theo quy định của pháp luật, như các kênh đưa tin tức hợp pháp, thông tin chính phủ công khai...;

thực hiện các hành vi vì lợi ích công cộng như đưa tin tức, giám sát dư luận, xử lý thông tin cá nhân trong phạm vi hợp lý;

tổ chức nghiên cứu khoa học cần thiết để triển khai thống kê hoặc nghiên cứu khoa học trên cơ sở lợi ích công cộng, và khi cung cấp kết quả nghiên cứu khoa học hoặc mô tả cho bên ngoài, thông tin cá nhân có trong kết quả sẽ được xử lý loại bỏ nhận dạng;

các trường hợp khác theo quy định của pháp luật và các quy định có liên quan.

Nội dung và mục đích của việc thu thập thông tin

Bảng dưới đây đã liệt kê ra những loại hình thông tin mà bạn cung cấp cho chúng tôi khi sử dụng những dịch vụ này, và mục đích mà chúng ta có thể sử dụng những thông tin này. Chúng tôi thu thập và sử dụng những thông tin sau để cung cấp, tối ưu hóa, bảo vệ và mở rộng dịch vụ của chúng tôi.

| Loại hình thông tin | Mục đích thu thập |
| --- | --- |
| Thông tin tài khoản. Chúng tôi sẽ thu thập những thông tin như địa chỉ Email, số điện thoại bạn cung cấp cho chúng tôi khi thực hiện một số thao tác (như đăng ký tài khoản) (nếu bạn dùng tài khoản SNS đăng nhập hoặc đăng ký thì chúng tôi sẽ nhận được nickname và dữ liệu ảnh hồ sơ SNS của bạn), đồng thời tiến hành liên kết những thông tin này với tài khoản của bạn. | Chúng tôi có thể dùng những thông tin này để xác nhận bạn là người sở hữu của tài khoản và bảo vệ sự an toàn cho tài khoản của bạn. Chúng tôi có thể sẽ thu thập những thông tin này khi bạn đăng nhập vào tài khoản của mình. |
| Tư liệu người dùng. Tài liệu bạn lưu trữ trong TeraBox như tệp, tài liệu, hình ảnh, video và âm thanh ("Tài liệu người dùng"). | Chúng tôi có thể sẽ lưu trữ, xử lý và truyền tải tài liệu người dùng và thông tin liên quan để đảm bảo vận hành thích hợp của dịch vụ, đồng thời cho phép bạn hợp tác với người khác, và thực hiện làm việc trên nhiều thiết bị và dịch vụ. Thông tin liên quan này bao gồm thông tin tệp, kích thước tệp, ngày giờ tải lên và hoạt động sử dụng của bạn. |
| Thông tin tình hình sử dụng. Thông tin liên quan đến sử dụng dịch vụ như thế nào, bao gồm thao tác thực hiện trong tài khoản như biên tập, xem, tạo mới và di chuyển tệp hoặc thư mục. | Chúng tôi có thể sử dụng những thông tin này để cung cấp, cải tiến và phát triển dịch vụ, đồng thời bảo vệ người dùng TeraBox. |
| Thông tin thiết bị. Các thông tin liên quan đến truy cập dịch vụ của thiết bị như địa chỉ IP, thông tin trình duyệt và thiết bị, trang web, mã đánh dấu liên kết với thiết bị và thông tin định vị quyết định vào cài đặt của thiết bị trước khi truy cập vào TeraBox. | Chúng tôi có thể sử dụng những thông tin này để cải thiện và bảo vệ dịch vụ của chúng tôi. |
| Cookies. Khi bạn truy cập vào TeraBox, sẽ có một đoạn văn bản ngắn được trang web gửi vào trình duyệt của bạn. Bạn có thể cài đặt trình duyệt không tiếp nhận cookies, nhưng như vậy sẽ có thể ảnh hưởng đến tính năng của dịch vụ. | Chúng tôi có khả năng sẽ dùng cookies và công nghệ tương tự để cung cấp, cải thiện, bảo vệ và quảng bá dịch vụ. Cookies giúp chúng tôi có thể ghi nhớ tên tài khoản của bạn, tìm hiểu cách sử dụng dịch vụ của bạn và dựa vào những thông tin này để cải tiến dịch vụ. Nhà cung cấp dịch vụ bên thứ 3 hợp tác với chúng tôi cũng có thể sử dụng cookies và công nghệ tương tự. |
| Phương thức liên hệ. Bạn có thể sử dụng tính năng chia sẻ của TeraBox để chia sẻ dữ liệu và thông tin của bạn với người liên hệ trong danh bạ điện thoại, số điện thoại di động, địa chỉ e-mail (như Facebook, Twitter). Thông tin danh bạ là thông tin cá nhân nhạy cảm. Từ chối cung cấp thông tin này sẽ chỉ khiến bạn không thể sử dụng tính năng nêu trên, nhưng sẽ không ảnh hưởng đến việc sử dụng bình thường các tính năng và dịch vụ liên quan khác của TeraBox. | Bạn có thể lựa chọn cho phép TeraBox truy cập thông tin liên hệ của bạn để tiện cho một số thao tác, ví dụ như chia sẻ và hợp tác với người khác xử lý dữ liệu của bạn, gửi tin nhắn và mời người khác sử dụng dịch vụ TeraBox thông qua việc gửi e-mail. Thao tác này yêu cầu bạn mở quyền truy cập danh bạ. Chúng tôi sẽ lưu trữ những thông tin này trên máy chủ của chúng tôi và cung cấp cho bạn sử dụng. Trước khi chia sẻ, vui lòng xem xét kỹ về độ tin cậy của người nhận thông tin. Đồng thời, chúng tôi khuyên bạn nên kiểm tra tuyên bố về quyền riêng tư của trang mạng xã hội hoặc nhà cung cấp dịch vụ bên thứ ba để hiểu họ xử lý thông tin của bạn như thế nào, nhằm đưa ra các quyết định thận trọng. |
| Clipboard. Khi bạn đăng ký tài khoản Terabox bằng mã mời của người khác, truy cập các liên kết tệp được chia sẻ bởi người dùng khác, thêm bạn bằng mật khẩu hoặc đổi dịch vụ thành viên bằng mã đổi, chúng tôi sẽ đọc thông tin trong bảng sao chép của bạn. | Chúng tôi sẽ truy cập thông tin clipboard để giúp bạn mở tệp tương ứng với liên kết, xác định người dùng tương ứng với mật khẩu và mã mời, hoặc để đổi dịch vụ thành viên cho bạn. Chúng tôi sẽ không bao giờ đọc clipboard của bạn với bất kỳ mục đích nào khác. |

Bạn có thể tạo mới tài khoản TeraBox bằng số điện thoại di động, đồng thời bạn có thể hoàn thiện thông tin tài khoản của mình.

Để đáp ứng yêu cầu bắt buộc theo quy định của pháp luật, cần thiết cho việc cung cấp sản phẩm hoặc dịch vụ hay là dựa trên nhu cầu tăng cường cấp độ bảo vệ tài khoản của bạn, bạn cần cung cấp họ tên thật, số căn cước công dân, thông tin khuôn mặt để hoàn thành xác thực tài khoản khi bạn sử dụng một số dịch vụ của TeraBox hoặc khi bạn có yêu cầu thêm. Để xác minh tính chính xác và tính hoàn chỉnh của thông tin bạn cung cấp, hoặc đảm bảo an toàn tài khoản của bạn, chúng tôi có thể sẽ thực hiện đối chiếu, kiểm chứng thông tin tên thật mà bạn cung cấp cho TeraBox với thông tin tương ứng của bạn được lưu trữ bởi tổ chức được quy định của pháp luật cho phép hoặc tổ chức được cơ quan chính quyền ủy quyền.

Thu thập những thông tin trên là để cung cấp dịch vụ một cách an toàn, đáng tin cậy và mục đích kinh doanh hợp pháp. Khi xử lý thông tin của bạn với bất kỳ mục đích nào khác, chúng tôi hoặc đối tác hợp tác của chúng tôi sẽ nhận được sự đồng ý của bạn trước.

Bạn đồng ý rằng chúng tôi sẽ thực hiện tổng hợp, nhận diện, phân tích, lập hồ sơ hoặc xử lý thêm các thông tin cá nhân mà bạn chủ động hoặc bị động cung cấp trong dịch vụ này thông qua công nghệ của chúng tôi hoặc của bên được ủy thác, đồng thời hình thành "thông tin riêng" với nhiều chủng loại và mức độ chi tiết khác nhau có thể phản ánh đặc trưng thói quen hành vi, sở thích hoặc tình trạng tín dụng... của bạn (dưới đây gọi tắt là "thông tin riêng"), chúng tôi sẽdùng "thông tin riêng" cho các trường hợp và mục đích cụ thể để đưa ra quyết định tự động hoá, giới thiệu cho bạn thông tin hiển thị cá nhân hóa và/hoặc thông tin kinh doanh của doanh nghiệp.

Bạn có quyền từ chối việc chúng tôi thực hiện dịch vụ công nghệ quyết định tự động hoá, bạn có thể liên hệ với chúng tôi thông qua phương thức liên hệ công bố trong thỏa thuận này hoặc thông qua đóng mở liên quan trong dịch vụ sản phẩm yêu cầu chúng tôi dừng lại. Đồng thời căn cứ theo quy định pháp luật hoặc yêu cầu giám sát quản lý của quốc gia hoặc vùng lãnh thổ liên quan về việc nghiêm cấm đưa ra quyết định tự động hoá, chúng tôi cũng sẽ chấp hành theo yêu cầu.

Chúng tôi có thể sử dụng Dữ liệu tài khoản của bạn cho mục đích tiếp thị và gửi cho bạn thông tin về sản phẩm mới, nâng cấp và tài liệu tiếp thị khác của TeraBox theo thời gian. Bạn có thể lựa chọn không nhận tài liệu tiếp thị bất cứ lúc nào bằng cách nhấp vào liên kết "Hủy đăng ký" trong bất kỳ email nào bạn nhận được.

Cung cấp thông tin cá nhân cho bên thứ 3

Nếu không có sự đồng ý trước của bạn, chúng tôi sẽ không cung cấp thông tin cá nhân cho bất kỳ bên thứ ba nào, trừ khi được yêu cầu vì bất kỳ trường hợp nào sau đây:

(a) Chúng tôi bắt buộc phải hợp tác với cơ quan chính phủ quốc gia hoặc chính quyền địa phương hoặc người đại diện của họ, tùy theo quy định pháp luật phù hợp để thực hiện trách nhiệm và nghĩa vụ, nếu buộc phải nhận được sự đồng ý của bạn, có thể sẽ loại trừ các trách nhiệm và nghĩa vụ này;

(b) Gây nguy hiểm nghiêm trọng đến sinh mệnh hoặc tài sản của ai đó;

(c) Đặc biệt cần thiết để cải thiện sức khỏe cộng đồng hoặc giúp thanh niên phát triển lành mạnh;

Đối với việc chia sẻ, di chuyển hoặc tiết lộ thông tin cá nhân của bạn trong các trường hợp ngoại lệ nêu trên, chúng tôi sẽ thực hiện ghi lại cơ sở xử lý thông tin liên quan, phạm vi xử lý thông tin, thông tin bên tiếp nhận..., cụ thể bao gồm các nội dung dưới đây, đồng thời tuân thủ nguyên tắc tối thiểu, cần thiết để bảo vệ quyền lợi hợp pháp của bạn.

（1）Họ tên, phương thức liên hệ chi tiết của người kiểm soát dữ liệu, nhân viên bảo vệ dữ liệu；

（2）Mục đích xử lý dữ liệu；

（3）Mô tả về loại hình của chủ thể dữ liệu và loại hình dữ liệu cá nhân；

（4）Loại hình dữ liệu cá nhân đã bị tiết lộ hoặc sẽ bị tiết lộ cho bên tiếp nhận (bao gồm bên tiếp nhận ở nước thứ ba hoặc tổ chức quốc tế)；

（5）Ghi chép di chuyển dữ liệu cá nhân đến nước thứ ba hoặc tổ chức quốc tế và ghi chép giải pháp đảm bảo thích hợp；

（6）Ước tính thời hạn xoá loại dữ liệu khác nhau；

（7）Mô tả chung về tính công nghệ và tính tổ chức của giải pháp an toàn。

Chia sẻ với người dùng khác

Khi bạn sử dụng tính năng hợp tác nhóm hoặc chia sẻ tệp do TeraBox cung cấp, dịch vụ của chúng tôi sẽ hiển thị biệt danh, thiết bị, địa chỉ e-mail và thông tin sử dụng của bạn cho người dùng mà bạn hợp tác hoặc dựa theo quyền hạn của bạn để lựa chọn chia sẻ với bạn. Điều này sẽ giúp bạn đồng bộ hóa với nhóm bạn muốn gia nhập, đồng thời giúp người dùng khác chia sẻ tệp và thư mục với bạn.

Chúng tôi có thể sẽ chia sẻ thông tin của bạn cho bên thứ 3

Chúng tôi có thể sẽ sử dụng một số bên thứ 3 đáng tin tưởng (như nhà cung cấp dịch vụ IT và hỗ trợ khách hàng), hỗ trợ chúng tôi cung cấp, tối ưu hóa, bảo vệ và quảng bá dịch vụ tốt hơn nữa. Các bên thứ 3 này có thể truy cập thông tin của bạn, đại diện cho chúng tôi để thực hiện nhiệm vụ, chúng tôi vẫn sẽ chịu trách nhiệm trong quá trình bên thứ 3 xử lý thông tin của bạn theo chỉ thị của chúng tôi.

Chúng tôi có thể chia sẻ cơ sở vật chất, hệ thống và công nghệ với những công ty liên kết với Flextech để cung cấp, cải tiến, bảo vệ và quảng bá những dịch vụ này. Những công ty liên kết này sẽ sử dụng thông tin của bạn cùng chúng tôi, và sẽ sử dụng những thông tin được nêu tại phần "Nội dung và mục đích của việc thu thập thông tin" cho các mục đích được liệt kê trong đó. Chúng tôi sẽ chịu trách nhiệm để những công ty này sử dụng thông tin của bạn.

Bạn có thể lựa chọn dùng dịch vụ bên thứ 3 liên kết với tài khoản TeraBox. Bằng cách liên kết dịch vụ như vậy, bạn cho phép những bên thứ 3 này trao đổi những thông tin được nêu tại phần "Nội dung và mục đích của việc thu thập thông tin" trong chính sách bảo mật này với chúng tôi, để những bên thứ 3 này có thể cung cấp, cải tiến, bảo vệ và nâng cấp dịch vụ của họ cùng chúng tôi. Trong những trường hợp này, việc sử dụng thông tin của bạn sẽ bị giới hạn bởi chính sách bảo mật và điều khoản dịch vụ được quy định trong dịch vụ bên thứ 3 mà bạn chọn liên kết đến.

Chúng tôi sẽ tham khảo yêu cầu của GDPR để thiết lập cơ chế truyền tải của truyền dữ liệu xuyên biên giới, đồng thời dựa trên yêu cầu của GDPR cập nhật kịp thời cơ chế xuyên biên giới. Việc thực hiện mọi xử lý về dữ liệu các nhân đều sẽ đáp ứng quy định nguyên tắc cơ bản của GDPR, được sự đồng ý có hiệu lực của chủ thể dữ liệu hoặc đáp ứng nguyên do sự việc hợp pháp khác. Ngoài ra sẽ còn thiết lập thêm các cơ chế để bảo vệ dữ liệu nhằm đáp ứng yêu cầu mang tính thực chất của GDPR đối với việc xử lý dữ liệu.

Chúng tôi bảo vệ và lưu trữ thông tin của bạn như thế nào

Chúng tôi có một đội ngũ tập trung vào việc đảm bảo an toàn thông tin của bạn và kiểm tra các lỗ hổng. Ngoài việc xác minh thân phận 2 bước, cấm đặt mật khẩu tệp và gửi thông báo khi có thiết bị mới và ứng dụng liên kết đến tài khoản của bạn, chúng tôi sẽ tiếp tục nỗ lực đảm bảo an toàn thông tin của bạn. Chúng tôi đã đặt sẵn công nghệ tự động hóa để kiểm tra rà soát những hành vi và nội dung có thể gây tổn hại đến dịch vụ của chúng tôi, bạn hoặc người dùng khác.

Khi bạn đăng ký tài khoản TeraBox, miễn là tài khoản của bạn còn tồn tại hoặc chúng tôi cần cung cấp dịch vụ cho bạn, chúng tôi sẽ lưu trữ những thông tin mà bạn lưu lại trên máy chủ của chúng tôi. Nếu bạn muốn xóa tài khoản của mình, vui lòng gửi Email đến [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com) để xóa thông tin của bạn, chúng tôi sẽ hoàn tất trong 30 ngày sau khi nhận được yêu cầu của bạn; nhưng nếu (1) trước khi xác minh thân phận người dùng của bạn, chúng tôi sẽ không xóa thông tin tài khoản của bạn; (2) xóa máy chủ của chúng tôi hoặc lưu trữ sao lưu có thể bị trễ, (3) nếu cần thiết, chúng tôi có thể lưu lại những thông tin này để tuân thủ theo nghĩa vụ pháp luật, giải quyết tranh chấp hoặc thực hiện quyền lợi của chúng tôi trong các mục của hợp đồng.

Chúng tôi sẽ lưu giữ thông tin cá nhân của bạn trong thời hạn cần thiết để cung cấp dịch vụ, nhưng trong các trường hợp quy định của pháp luật có quy định riêng đối với thời hạn lưu giữ, bạn đồng ý thời hạn lưu giữ dài hơn, bảo đảm an toàn và chất lượng của dịch vụ, nhằm đạt được mục đích giải quyết tranh chấp, khó hiện thực được về mặt công nghệ..., sau khi hết thời hạn lưu giữ nêu trên, chúng tôi sẽ kéo dài thời hạn lưu giữ dựa theo pháp luật, theo thỏa thuận hoặc trong phạm vi hợp lý.

Sau khi vượt quá thời hạn lưu giữ, chúng tôi sẽ xóa thông tin cá nhân của bạn hoặc thực hiện xử lý ẩn danh theo quy định của pháp luật

Chúng tôi sẽ thu thập, sử dụng, lưu trữ và truyền tải thông tin người dùng theo nguyên tắc "tối thiểu hóa", đồng thời thông báo cho bạn về mục đích và phạm vi sử dụng thông tin liên quan thông qua thỏa thuận người dùng, chính sách quyền riêng tư và quy tắc liên quan, cửa sổ thông tin, thông báo...

Chúng tôi rất chú trọng an toàn thông tin. Chúng tôi đã thành lập nhóm chuyên phụ trách và chịu trách nhiệm nghiên cứu phát triển và ứng dụng nhiều loại công nghệ và quy trình an toàn..., chúng tôi sẽ thực hiện thẩm tra lý lịch an toàn đối với người phụ trách quản lý an toàn và nhân viên giữ chức vụ an toàn quan trọng, chúng tôi đã thành lập hệ thống quản lý an toàn thông tin và cơ chế xử lý tình huống an toàn nội bộ hoàn thiện. Chúng tôi sẽ áp dụng các giải pháp an toàn và phương tiện kỹ thuật thích hợp và phù hợp với tiêu chuẩn ngành nghề để lưu trữ và bảo vệ thông tin cá nhân của bạn, để phòng chống việc thông tin của bạn bị mất, bị truy cập khi chưa được cho phép, tiết lộ công khai, sử dụng, huỷ hoại, bị mất hoặc bị lộ. Chúng tôi sẽ áp dụng mọi giải pháp hợp lý, khả thi để bảo vệ thông tin cá nhân của bạn. Chúng tôi sẽ sử dụng công nghệ mã hóa để đảm bảo tính bảo mật của dữ liệu; chúng tôi sẽ sử dụng cơ chế bảo vệ được tin cậy để phòng tránh dữ liệu bị tấn công với dụng ý xấu.

Chúng tôi sẽ thực hiện bồi dưỡng nhận thức về an toàn dữ liệu, đào tạo và kiểm tra đánh giá năng lực an toàn cho nhân viên, tăng cường nhận thức của nhân viên về tầm quan trọng của bảo vệ thông tin cá nhân. Chúng tôi sẽ thực hiện xác thực danh tính và kiểm soát quyền hạn đối với các nhân viên xử lý thông tin cá nhân, đồng thời ký kết thỏa thuận bảo mật với nhân viên, đối tác hợp tác tiếp xúc với thông tin cá nhân của bạn, làm rõ trách nhiệm chức vụ và quy tắc ứng xử, đảm bảo chỉ có nhân viên được ủy quyền mới có thể truy cập thông tin cá nhân. Nếu có hành vi vi phạm về thỏa thuận bảo mật sẽ ngay lập tức bị dừng quan hệ hợp tác với công ty, đồng thời sẽ bị truy cứu trách nhiệm pháp luật liên quan, yêu cầu bảo mật cũng được đưa ra đối với các nhân viên tiếp xúc với thông tin cá nhân khi họ rời khỏi chức vụ đảm nhiệm.

Chúng tôi nhắc bạn chú ý rằng, mạng internet không phải là môi trường an toàn tuyệt đối, khi bạn trao đổi thông tin vị trí địa lý hoặc tung tích của bạn với người dùng khác thông qua phần mềm mạng xã hội của bên thứ ba cài vào trong TeraBox, e-mail, tin nhắn... không chắc chắn phần mềm bên thứ ba có hoàn toàn mã hóa đối với việc truyền tải thông tin hay không, chú ý đảm bảo an toàn thông tin cá nhân của bạn.

Chúng tôi cũng mong bạn hiểu rằng, trong ngành mạng internet do hạn chế của công nghệ và sự phát triển nhanh chóng cùng với việc có thể tồn tại các loại phương thức tấn công với dụng ý xấu, cho dù chúng tôi cố gắng hết sức để tăng cường các giải pháp an toàn cũng không thể luôn luôn bảo đảm thông tin an toàn 100%. Bạn vui lòng hiểu rằng, hệ thống và mạng lưới thông tin mà bạn dùng khi sử dụng sản phẩm và/hoặc dịch vụ của chúng tôi có thể xuất hiện vấn đề an toàn ở các khâu khác nằm ngoài tầm kiểm soát của chúng tôi.

Dựa theo quy định quản lý an toàn của chúng tôi, sự việc rò rỉ, huỷ hoại hoặc bị mất thông tin cá nhân được liệt vào sự cố an toàn đặc biệt lớn, một khi xảy ra sẽ kích hoạt kế hoạch khẩn cấp cấp cao nhất của công ty, và do tổ ứng phó khẩn cấp liên hợp gồm nhiều bộ phận hợp thành xử lý.

Chúng tôi sẽ xây dựng kế hoạch ứng phó khẩn cấp sự cố an ninh mạng internet, kịp thời xử lý rủi ro an ninh như lỗ hổng hệ thống, virus máy tính, tấn công mạng internet, xâm nhập mạng..., khi xảy ra sự cố gây nguy hại đến an ninh mạng, chúng tôi sẽ lập tức kích hoạt kế hoạch ứng phó khẩn cấp, áp dụng giải pháp cứu chữa tương ứng, đồng thời báo cáo cơ quan chủ quản liên quan theo quy định.

Rò rỉ, huỷ hoại, bị mất thông tin cá nhân thuộc về sự cố an toàn đặc biệt lớn cấp công ty, chúng tôi sẽ phụ trách tổ chức cho thành viên tổ công tác thực hiện diễn tập phương án an toàn định kỳ, phòng chống sự cố an toàn như vậy xảy ra.

Nếu một khi không may xảy ra, chúng tôi sẽ kích hoạt kế hoạch ứng phó khẩn cấp theo cấp ưu tiên cao nhất, thành lập tổ ứng phó khẩn cấp, truy tìm nguyên nhân và giảm thiểu tổn thất trong thời gian ngắn nhất. Sau khi không may xảy ra sự cố an toàn thông tin cá nhân, chúng tôi sẽ dựa theo yêu cầu quy định của pháp luật, thông báo kịp thời tới bạn tình hình cơ bản và ảnh hưởng có thể gây ra của sự cố an toàn, các giải pháp xử lý chúng tôi đã áp dụng hoặc sắp áp dụng, kiến nghị để bạn có thể tự phòng chống và giảm bớt rủi ro, giải pháp cứu chữa cho bạn... Chúng tôi sẽ thông báo kịp thời cho bạn tình hình liên quan của sự cố thông qua phương thức liên hệ bạn để lại như thông báo trên trang web, thông báo tin nhắn, điện thoại,e-mail..., khi khó có thể thông báo lần lượt chúng tôi sẽ áp dụng phương thức hợp lý, hiệu quả để đăng thông báo. Đồng thời, chúng tôi cũng sẽ chủ động báo cáo tình hình xử lý sự cố an toàn thông tin cá nhân theo yêu cầu của cơ quan giám sát, quản lý. Bạn vui lòng hiểu rằng, dựa theo quy định của pháp luật, nếu như các giải pháp chúng tôi áp dụng có thể ngăn chặn có hiệu quả những nguy hại của việc rò rỉ, xuyên tạc, bị mất thông tin gây ra, chúng tôi có thể lựa chọn không thông báo cho bạn sự cố an toàn thông tin cá nhân này trừ khi cơ quan giám sát, quản lý yêu cầu thông báo cho bạn.

Chúng tôi sẽ tham khảo yêu cầu của GDPR, lựa chọn giải pháp bảo vệ an toàn kỹ thuật trên cơ sở tính chất, phạm vi, bối cảnh và mục đích của xử lý dữ liệu cùng với rủi ro gây ra đối với cá nhân, đồng thời tiến hành kiểm tra và đánh giá định kỳ để duy trì tính hiệu quả của giải pháp được áp dụng.

Sau khi xảy ra rò rỉ dữ liệu, chúng tôi sẽ nhanh chóng thông báo cho nhóm người liên quan chịu ảnh hưởng của việc rò rỉ thông tin, đồng thời chúng tôi sẽ báo cáo cho cơ quan chủ quản liên quan trong vòng 72 giờ. Khi không thể báo cáo trong vòng 72 giờ, sẽ giải thích nguyên nhân trì hoãn việc báo cáo. Chúng tôi áp dụng kỹ thuật và giải pháp tổ chức thích hợp để thực hiện mục tiêu bảo vệ dữ liệu, như tối thiểu hóa dữ liệu và kết hợp các giải pháp bảo đảm cần thiết vào trong quá trình xử lý dữ liệu để bảo vệ các quyền lợi của chủ thể dữ liệu, trong tình huống mặc định, việc đảm bảo xử lý dữ liệu cho mục đích đặc biệt là cần thiết.

Chúng tôi lưu trữ và xử lý thông tin của bạn ở đâu

Khi cung cấp dịch vụ, chúng tôi có thể lưu trữ, xử lý và truyền tải thông tin của bạn tại Nhật Bản, hơn nữa bạn cần đồng ý cung cấp thông tin của bạn. Thông tin của bạn cũng có thể lưu trữ cục bộ trên thiết bị được dùng cho truy cập dịch vụ.

Bạn kiểm soát và truy cập thông tin của mình như thế nào

Theo pháp luật, quy định, tiêu chuẩn và phương pháo thông dụng của quốc gia, vùng lãnh thổ liên quan, chúng tôi đảm bảo bạn có thể thực hiện các quyền lợi sau đối với thông tin cá nhân của mình, nếu bạn có thắc mắc hoặc ý kiến về việc thực hiện quyền lợi, bạn có thể liên hệ với chúng tôi thông qua [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com). Bạn có thể xem, chỉnh sửa, tải xuống, xóa hoặc chia sẻ thông tin của mình trong tài khoản TeraBox.

1.Quyền tra cứu

Khi bạn muốn tìm hiểu phạm vi TeraBox thu thập, lưu giữ, chia sẻ... thông tin cá nhân của bạn hoặc mục đích xử lý thông tin cá nhân của bạn, bạn có thể liên hệ với chúng tôi để nhận được nội dung liên quan.

2.Quyền đính chính và bổ sung

Khi bạn phát hiện chúng tôi xử lý thông tin cá nhân của bạn bị sai, bạn có quyền đính chính đối với thông tin sai hoặc không hoàn chỉnh, sau khi thực hiện kiểm chứng danh tính của bạn, bạn có thể nộp đăng ký đính chính hoặc bổ sung cho chúng tôi thông qua phương thức phản hồi và báo lỗi hoặc phương thức liên hệ công bố nêu trên. Sau khi nhận được đăng ký của bạn, chúng tôi sẽ nhanh chóng phản hồi tới bạn.

3\. Quyền xóa bỏ

Trong các trường hợp dưới đây, bạn có thể đưa ra yêu cầu chúng tôi xóa thông tin cá nhân:

Nếu như chúng tôi xử lý thông tin cá nhân của bạn vi phạm quy định của pháp luật hoặc thỏa thuận với bạn;

Nếu như mục đích xử lý của chúng tôi đã thực hiện được, không thể thực hiện hoặc mục đích thực hiện xử lý không còn cần thiết;

Nếu như chúng tôi dừng cung cấp sản phẩm hoặc dịch vụ, hoặc thời hạn lưu giữ đã hết;

Nếu như bạn rút lại việc đồng ý;

Các trường hợp khác theo quy định của pháp luật và quy định hành chính.

Sau khi bạn xóa thông tin trong dịch vụ của chúng tôi, chúng tôi có thể sẽ không ngay lập tức xóa thông tin tương ứng trong hệ thống sao lưu, nhưng sẽ xóa những thông tin này khi cập nhật sao lưu. Bạn vui lòng biết và hiểu rằng, nếu như thời hạn lưu giữ theo quy định của pháp luật, quy định hành chính hoặc mô tả trong chính sách quyền riêng tư này chưa hết, hoặc việc thực hiện xóa thông tin cá nhân gặp khó khăn về mặt kỹ thuật, chúng tôi sẽ dừng xử lý ngoại trừ việc lưu trữ và áp dụng các giải pháp bảo vệ an toàn cần thiết.

4\. Rút lại việc đồng ý

Mỗi một tính năng nghiệp vụ đều cần một số thông tin cá nhân cơ bản mới có thể hoàn thành. Đối với việc thu thập và sử dụng thông tin cá nhân thu thập thêm, bạn có thể cho phép hoặc thu hồi đồng ý ủy quyền của bạn bất cứ lúc nào.

Bạn có thể trực tiếp đóng các quyền hạn hệ thống như danh bạ, bộ sưu tập, máy ảnh... trên hệ thống của thiết bị, thay đổi phạm vi đồng ý hoặc rút lại ủy quyền của bạn.

Sau khi bạn rút lại đồng ý, chúng tôi sẽ không thể tiếp tục cung cấp cho bạn các dịch vụ tương ứng với việc rút lại đồng ý, cũng sẽ không sử dụng thông tin cá nhân tương ứng của bạn nữa. Nhưng quyết định rút lại đồng ý của bạn sẽ không ảnh hưởng đến việc xử lý thông tin cá nhân được triển khai trên cơ sở bạn đồng ý trước đó.

5.Quyền hủy bỏ

Bạn có thể hủy bỏ tài khoản đăng ký trước đó. Bạn còn có thể hủy bỏ tài khoản TeraBox thông qua các cách sau:

\[Hình đại điện tài khoản\] -\[Menu\]-\[Cài đặt\]-\[Trung tâm an toàn\]-\[Hủy bỏ tài khoản\].

Một khi bạn hủy bỏ tài khoản, bạn sẽ không thể sử dụng dịch vụ của sản phẩm TeraBox, vì thế bạn vui lòng thao tác thận trọng. Để bảo vệ quyền lợi hợp pháp của bạn và người khác, chúng tôi sẽ kết hợp với tình hình sử dụng của bạn để phán đoán xem có hỗ trợ yêu cầu hủy bỏ tài khoản của bạn hay không. Ví dụ như bạn có quyền lợi Premium chưa sử dụng, hoặc trong tài khoản của bạn vẫn còn tư liệu thì chúng tôi sẽ không hỗ trợ yêu cầu của bạn ngay được. Ngoại trừ việc pháp luật có quy định riêng, sau khi hủy bỏ tài khoản chúng tôi sẽ dừng cung cấp sản phẩm và dịch vụ cho bạn, đồng thời xóa thông tin cá nhân theo yêu cầu của bạn.

6.Quyền sao chép và quyền mang theo

Bạn có quyền sao chép thông tin cá nhân của bạn mà chúng tôi thu thập. Trong điều kiện quy định của pháp luật, đồng thời phù hợp với hướng dẫn và điều kiện cơ quan chủ quản liên quan quy định, nếu như kỹ thuật khả thi, bạn có thể yêu cầu chúng tôi đem thông tin cá nhân của bạn chuyển đến chủ thể khác mà bạn chỉ định.

Khi bạn thực hiện quyền lợi liên quan đến chủ thể thông tin cá nhân nêu trên, chúng tôi cũng sẽ đồng bộ với bên thứ ba liên quan sớm nhất có thể, đảm bảo quyền lợi nêu trên của bạn được thực hiện tuân theo quy định của pháp luật, yêu cầu giám sát, quản lý và kỹ thuật khả thi.

Khi yêu cầu của bạn rõ ràng không có lý do chính đáng hoặc vượt quá giới hạn cần thiết, đặc biệt là khi yêu cầu trùng lặp, chúng tôi có thể:

(a) Kết hợp với chi phí hành chính của việc cung cấp thông tin, giao lưu hoặc hành động tương ứng để thu một khoản phí hợp lý nhất định; hoặc

(b) Từ chối thực hiện đối với yêu cầu.

Bạn có thể kiểm soát thông tin cá nhân mà bạn đã lưu và cách thu thập, sử dụng, chia sẻ theo "Luật bảo vệ thông tin cá nhân Nhật Bản" ("Thông tin cá nhân đã lưu"). Ví dụ, bạn có thể:

a. Yêu cầu công bố thông tin cá nhân đã lưu và có thể nhận biết thân phận của bạn.

b. Khi nội dung thông tin cá nhân đã lưu để nhận biết cá nhân không phải sự thực, yêu cầu tiến hành chỉnh sửa, tăng thêm hoặc xóa bỏ nội dung thông tin cá nhân đã lưu.

c. Nếu chúng tôi dùng cách thức phi pháp để thu thập thông tin cá nhân mà bạn đã lưu, hoặc chúng tôi đang sử dụng thông tin cá nhân mà bạn đã lưu, vui lòng xóa bỏ hoặc dừng sử dụng thông tin cá nhân mà bạn đã lưu.

d. Nếu chúng tôi cung cấp thông tin cá nhân mà bạn đã lưu cho bên thứ 3 một cách bất hợp pháp, vui lòng dừng cung cấp thông tin cá nhân mà bạn đã lưu.

Thay đổi

Nếu tái cơ cấu, sáp nhập hoặc mua lại Flextech hoặc bán tài sản của chúng tôi, thông tin của bạn có thể sẽ chuyển giao lại cho đối tượng thực tế tồn tại sau đó, bên mua hoặc người kế thừa trong giao dịch này. Chúng tôi sẽ thông báo cho bạn bất kỳ kiểu giao dịch nào như thế (ví dụ, thông tin này sẽ được gửi đến địa chỉ email được liên kết với tài khoản của bạn), và sẽ khái quát lựa chọn của bạn trong sự việc này.

Chính sách bảo mật này có thể sẽ được sửa đổi liên tục. Chúng tôi sẽ công bố phiên bản mới nhất trên trang web của TeraBox. Nếu bất kể sửa đổi nào như vậy ảnh hưởng nghiêm trọng đến quyền của bạn, chúng tôi sẽ thông báo đến bạn.

Liên hệ chúng tôi:

Nếu bạn có bất kỳ câu hỏi hoặc lo lắng gì về TeraBox, quyền bảo mật và dịch vụ của chúng tôi, vui lòng liên hệ với chúng tôi qua [helpdesk@terabox.com](mailto:helpdesk@terabox.com).
